[
  {
    "question": "A 3-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111. Over the next 6 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111, 110. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "1",
    "answer": "[[111 -> 110 -> 101 -> 100 -> 011 -> 010]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "186"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-8 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 3 select lines: ['var4', 'var5', 'var3'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var4=1, var5=1, var3=0, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "2",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "367"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-8 multiplexer. The MUX has 3 select lines: ['var1', 'var2', 'var4'], and the following logic expressions for each output: var4, var0, var0, var0, var3, var5 \u2227 var3 \u2227 var1, var3 \u2227 var5 \u2227 var2, var1 \u2227 var0. Given the variable values: var0=0, var1=0, var2=1, var3=0, var4=0, var5=0, what is the output of the MUX? Please provide the output of the MUX in the format of [[0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "3",
    "answer": "[[0]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "400"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-4 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 2 select lines: ['var3', 'var2'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var3=0, var2=1, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "4",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 0, 0]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "351"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 2-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11. Over the next 4 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: . What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "5",
    "answer": "[[11 -> 10 -> 01 -> 00]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "177"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-16 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 4 select lines: ['var2', 'var3', 'var4', 'var6'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var2=0, var3=0, var4=1, var6=0, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "6",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "384"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given sets:\n  A = {1, 2}\n  B = {2, 3}\n\n We define the operation P(A) = {All subsets of A}, a set of all subsets of A. e.g., P({a,b}) = {{}, {a},{b},{a,b}}. Evaluate the set operation: P(A) & P(B) - P(A & B).",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "7",
    "answer": "[[{}]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "207"
  },
  {
    "question": "We define cartesian product as the set of all ordered pairs (a, b) where a is in A and b is in B, i.e. A x B =  a set that contains all the ordered pairs (a, b) where a is in A and b is in B. we define P(A) = {All subsets of A}, a set of all subsets of A. e.g., P({a,b}) = {{}, {a},{b},{a,b}}. We define the operation Symmetric Difference as the set of all elements that are in not in either of the two sets, i.e. Symmetric Difference of A and B = A - B union B - A.   Given sets A = {1, 2, 3}, B = {0, 4, 5} evaluate the Cartesian Product of the first term, (Union of P(A) and P(B)) and the second term, (Intersection of P(A) and P(B)).",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "8",
    "answer": "[[{({2}, {}), ({}, {}), ({0, 5}, {}), ({1}, {}), ({0}, {}), ({0, 4, 5}, {}), ({1, 2, 3}, {}), ({1, 3}, {}), ({1, 2}, {}), ({5}, {}), ({4}, {}), ({0, 4}, {}), ({3}, {}), ({4, 5}, {}), ({2, 3}, {})}]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "637"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 6-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111111. Over the next 12 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111111, 111110, 111101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "9",
    "answer": "[[111111 -> 111110 -> 111101 -> 111100 -> 111011 -> 111010 -> 111001 -> 111000 -> 110111 -> 110110 -> 110101 -> 110100]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "204"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "10",
    "answer": "[[A'B+C+D]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "1107"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-32 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 5 select lines: ['var5', 'var7', 'var4', 'var1', 'var2'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var5=1, var7=0, var4=0, var1=1, var2=0, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "11",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "400"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S3 | 0\nS0 | I01 | S2 | 0\nS0 | I10 | S5 | 7\nS0 | I11 | S5 | 5\nS1 | I00 | S0 | 0\nS1 | I01 | S4 | 1\nS1 | I10 | S0 | 1\nS1 | I11 | S5 | 0\nS2 | I00 | S1 | 4\nS2 | I01 | S4 | 1\nS2 | I10 | S5 | 4\nS2 | I11 | S1 | 0\nS3 | I00 | S5 | 2\nS3 | I01 | S3 | 1\nS3 | I10 | S4 | 3\nS3 | I11 | S0 | 6\nS4 | I00 | S2 | 5\nS4 | I01 | S1 | 4\nS4 | I10 | S0 | 3\nS4 | I11 | S5 | 1\nS5 | I00 | S4 | 0\nS5 | I01 | S0 | 6\nS5 | I10 | S3 | 0\nS5 | I11 | S0 | 3\nStarting from state S0, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I11 -> I01 -> I10 -> I01 -> I01, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "12",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 3 -> 0 -> 1]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "672"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D, E and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "13",
    "answer": "[[A'+B'C'+BDE]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "2230"
  },
  {
    "question": "A,B,C,D are subsets of N, i.e. A,B,C,D are sets of natural numbers. Given sets A = {1, 2, 7, 8}, B = {x | x^2 < 50}, C = {x | 0 <= x <= 20 and x is divisible by 3}, and D = {x | x = 2^k where k is a non-negative integer and 0 <= k <= 5}: We define A^C = {x | x is an element of A and x is a natural number}. Evaluate the set operation ((N - A) - (N - B)) union D.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "14",
    "answer": "[[{0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 8, 16, 32}]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "363"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given sets:\n  A = {1, 2, 3}\n  B = {2, 4}\n  C = {1, 2, 3, 4}\n\nWe define the operation P(A) = {All subsets of A}, a set of all subsets of A. e.g., P({a,b}) = {{}, {a},{b},{a,b}}. Evaluate the set operation: (P(A) - P(B)) - P(C - B).",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "15",
    "answer": "[[{{2, 3}, {1, 2}, {1, 2, 3}}]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "230"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S6 | 11\nS0 | I01 | S6 | 15\nS0 | I10 | S2 | 5\nS0 | I11 | S4 | 7\nS1 | I00 | S5 | 15\nS1 | I01 | S2 | 8\nS1 | I10 | S3 | 5\nS1 | I11 | S5 | 8\nS2 | I00 | S3 | 14\nS2 | I01 | S3 | 12\nS2 | I10 | S0 | 14\nS2 | I11 | S7 | 8\nS3 | I00 | S4 | 10\nS3 | I01 | S0 | 14\nS3 | I10 | S4 | 9\nS3 | I11 | S1 | 5\nS4 | I00 | S3 | 3\nS4 | I01 | S0 | 13\nS4 | I10 | S2 | 11\nS4 | I11 | S3 | 14\nS5 | I00 | S1 | 6\nS5 | I01 | S1 | 12\nS5 | I10 | S3 | 1\nS5 | I11 | S6 | 13\nS6 | I00 | S4 | 11\nS6 | I01 | S3 | 7\nS6 | I10 | S7 | 11\nS6 | I11 | S3 | 12\nS7 | I00 | S5 | 9\nS7 | I01 | S4 | 15\nS7 | I10 | S3 | 12\nS7 | I11 | S1 | 5\nStarting from state S5, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I10 -> I11 -> I10 -> I01 -> I01 -> I10, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "16",
    "answer": "[[12 -> 5 -> 5 -> 5 -> 14 -> 15 -> 11]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "841"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given sets:\n  A = {2, 3, 4}\n  B = {2, 4, 6, 8}\n  C = {x \u2208 \u2115 | x is prime and x < 10}\n  D = {2, {4, 6}}\n\n We define the operation P(A) = {All subsets of A}, a set of all subsets of A. e.g., P({a,b}) = {{}, {a},{b},{a,b}}. Evaluate the set operation: P(D) - P(A) & P(B & C).",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "17",
    "answer": "[[{{{4, 6}}, {2, {4, 6}}}]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "272"
  },
  {
    "question": "A,B,C,D are subsets of N, i.e. A,B,C,D are sets of natural numbers. Given sets A = {1, 2, 7, 8}, B = {x | x^2 < 50}, C = {x | 0 <= x <= 20 and x is divisible by 3}, and D = {x | x = 2^k where k is a non-negative integer and 0 <= k <= 5}: Evaluate the set operation A union (B union (C union D)).",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "18",
    "answer": "[[{0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 12, 15, 16, 18, 32}]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "295"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S0 | 4\nS0 | I01 | S6 | 44\nS0 | I10 | S11 | 55\nS0 | I11 | S1 | 53\nS1 | I00 | S10 | 49\nS1 | I01 | S11 | 21\nS1 | I10 | S11 | 23\nS1 | I11 | S6 | 1\nS2 | I00 | S3 | 48\nS2 | I01 | S3 | 11\nS2 | I10 | S8 | 51\nS2 | I11 | S3 | 48\nS3 | I00 | S10 | 47\nS3 | I01 | S9 | 24\nS3 | I10 | S6 | 46\nS3 | I11 | S7 | 42\nS4 | I00 | S6 | 56\nS4 | I01 | S8 | 28\nS4 | I10 | S10 | 63\nS4 | I11 | S9 | 18\nS5 | I00 | S2 | 12\nS5 | I01 | S10 | 4\nS5 | I10 | S7 | 48\nS5 | I11 | S11 | 45\nS6 | I00 | S9 | 44\nS6 | I01 | S0 | 12\nS6 | I10 | S3 | 33\nS6 | I11 | S5 | 18\nS7 | I00 | S7 | 13\nS7 | I01 | S6 | 25\nS7 | I10 | S2 | 62\nS7 | I11 | S11 | 8\nS8 | I00 | S7 | 28\nS8 | I01 | S0 | 20\nS8 | I10 | S8 | 63\nS8 | I11 | S10 | 56\nS9 | I00 | S3 | 32\nS9 | I01 | S10 | 6\nS9 | I10 | S7 | 46\nS9 | I11 | S11 | 42\nS10 | I00 | S1 | 41\nS10 | I01 | S10 | 1\nS10 | I10 | S1 | 38\nS10 | I11 | S2 | 35\nS11 | I00 | S2 | 7\nS11 | I01 | S5 | 10\nS11 | I10 | S2 | 60\nS11 | I11 | S8 | 23\nStarting from state S0, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I01 -> I00 -> I00 -> I01 -> I11 -> I00 -> I11 -> I11, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "19",
    "answer": "[[53 -> 21 -> 7 -> 48 -> 24 -> 42 -> 7 -> 48 -> 42]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "1187"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S2 | 21\nS0 | I01 | S5 | 10\nS0 | I10 | S4 | 27\nS0 | I11 | S9 | 5\nS1 | I00 | S2 | 17\nS1 | I01 | S1 | 15\nS1 | I10 | S0 | 27\nS1 | I11 | S1 | 18\nS2 | I00 | S8 | 16\nS2 | I01 | S8 | 23\nS2 | I10 | S6 | 15\nS2 | I11 | S8 | 16\nS3 | I00 | S9 | 23\nS3 | I01 | S2 | 9\nS3 | I10 | S3 | 14\nS3 | I11 | S2 | 18\nS4 | I00 | S4 | 13\nS4 | I01 | S9 | 19\nS4 | I10 | S1 | 26\nS4 | I11 | S5 | 9\nS5 | I00 | S2 | 19\nS5 | I01 | S1 | 3\nS5 | I10 | S7 | 7\nS5 | I11 | S8 | 22\nS6 | I00 | S5 | 26\nS6 | I01 | S1 | 22\nS6 | I10 | S5 | 19\nS6 | I11 | S7 | 0\nS7 | I00 | S1 | 26\nS7 | I01 | S2 | 22\nS7 | I10 | S9 | 11\nS7 | I11 | S1 | 29\nS8 | I00 | S1 | 8\nS8 | I01 | S1 | 28\nS8 | I10 | S8 | 16\nS8 | I11 | S6 | 30\nS9 | I00 | S4 | 5\nS9 | I01 | S3 | 5\nS9 | I10 | S6 | 28\nS9 | I11 | S6 | 30\nStarting from state S8, and given the input sequence: I00 -> I00 -> I00 -> I00 -> I01 -> I01 -> I10 -> I00, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "20",
    "answer": "[[8 -> 17 -> 16 -> 8 -> 15 -> 15 -> 27 -> 21]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "1005"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given sets A = {2, 3, 4}, B = {1, 2, 4}, we define cartesian product as the set of all ordered pairs (a, b) where a is in A and b is in B, i.e. A x B =  a set that contains all the ordered pairs (a, b) where a is in A and b is in B. we define P(A) = {All subsets of A}, a set of all subsets of A. e.g., P({a,b}) = {{}, {a},{b},{a,b}}. We define the operation Symmetric Difference as the set of all elements that are in not in either of the two sets, i.e. Symmetric Difference of A and B = A - B union B - A.  Given sets A = {0, 1, 2, 3}, B = {0, 1, 3, 4}, C = {0, 2, 3, 4},  evaluate the Intersection of the first term, (Symmetric Difference of P(A) and P(C)) and the second term, (Symmetric Difference of P(A) and P(C)).",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "21",
    "answer": "[[{{0, 3, 4}, {3, 4}, {2, 3, 4}, {0, 1, 2}, {1, 2}, {0, 2, 3, 4}, {0, 1}, {0, 4}, {0, 2, 4}, {1}, {2, 4}, {0, 1, 2, 3}, {1, 3}, {1, 2, 3}, {0, 1, 3}, {4}}]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "721"
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the Boolean expression: (\u00acB) \u2295 (B) \u2295 (A \u2228 B) \u2295 (A \u2228 B) \u2295 (A), given that A=1, B=0.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "22",
    "answer": "[[0]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "91"
  },
  {
    "question": "A,B,C,D are subsets of N, i.e. A,B,C,D are sets of natural numbers. Given sets A = {1, 2, 7, 8, 12}, B = {x | x^2 < 80}, C = {x | 5 <= x <= 35 and x is divisible by 2}, and D = {x | x = 2^k where k is a non-negative integer and 0 <= k <= 5}: Evaluate the set operation A union (B union (C union D)).",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "23",
    "answer": "[[{1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 10, 12, 14, 16, 18, 20, 22, 24, 26, 28, 30, 32, 34}]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "299"
  },
  {
    "question": "A,B,C,D are subsets of N, i.e. A,B,C,D are sets of natural numbers. Given sets A = {x | x  < 102}, B = {x | x^2 < 80}, C = {x | 5 <= x <= 35 and x is divisible by 2}, and D = {x | 2*x < 3^4}: Evaluate the set operation(A intersection D) union (B intersection (C union D)).",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "24",
    "answer": "[[{0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40}]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "272"
  },
  {
    "question": "A,B,C,D are subsets of N, i.e. A,B,C,D are sets of natural numbers. Given sets A = {1, 2, 7, 8, 12, 13, 14}, B = {x | x^3 < 180}, C = {x | 134 <= x <= 145 and x is divisible by 2}, and D = {x | x = 2^(2k-5) where k is a non-negative integer and 0 <= k <= 5}: Evaluate the set operation (A intersection D) union (B intersection (C union D)).",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "25",
    "answer": "[[{2, 8}]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "340"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given sets:\n  A = {x \u2208 \u2115+ | x < 5}\n  B = {3, 4, 5, 6}\n  C = {x \u2208 \u2115 | x is not prime and x < 10}\n  D = { {1},{4,6},1,3,4 }  \n\n We define the operation P(A) = {All subsets of A}, a set of all subsets of A. e.g., P({a,b}) = {{}, {a},{b},{a,b}}. Evaluate the set operation: D - (P(A) & P(B)) & P(C).",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "26",
    "answer": "[[{1, 3, 4, {1}, {4, 6}}]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "295"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-4 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 2 select lines: ['var3', 'var2'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var3=1, var2=0, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "27",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 1, 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "351"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-8 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 3 select lines: ['var1', 'var5', 'var4'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var1=0, var5=1, var4=1, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "28",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "367"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-4 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 2 select lines: ['var0', 'var2'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var0=1, var2=1, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "29",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "351"
  },
  {
    "question": "A, B, C, and D are subsets of N, the set of natural numbers. Given sets are as follows:\n\nA = {x | x is a natural number less than or equal to 50 and is either a prime number or divisible by 7} \nB = {x | x is a perfect square less than 200}\nC = {x | 10 <= x <= 100 and x is divisible by both 2 and 5}\nD = {x | x = 3^k where k is a non-negative integer and 0 <= k <= 6}\n\nEvaluate the set operation: (A union B) intersection (C union D union {x | x is a Fibonacci number less than 100}).\n\nExplain step-by-step how to compute the sets A, B, C, and D, and the final result of the set operation.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "30",
    "answer": "[[{1, 2, 3, 5, 9, 13, 21, 81, 100}]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "589"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-4 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 2 select lines: ['var2', 'var0'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var2=0, var0=1, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "31",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 0, 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "351"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-4 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 2 select lines: ['var1', 'var2'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var1=0, var2=1, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "32",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 0, 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "351"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the universal set U = {1, 2, \u2026, 500}.\nDefine:\n  X = {x \u2208 U | x has exactly 3 distinct factors} (Hint: these are squares of prime numbers),\n  Y = {x \u2208 U | x is a perfect square},\n  Z = {x \u2208 U | x is divisible by 5 but not by 10}.\n\nEvaluate the set expression: (X \u222a Y) - Z.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "33",
    "answer": "[[{1, 4, 9, 16, 36, 49, 64, 81, 100, 121, 144, 169, 196, 225, 256, 289, 324, 361, 400, 441, 484}]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "280"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-8 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 3 select lines: ['var0', 'var4', 'var2'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var0=0, var4=0, var2=0, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "34",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "367"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-4 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 2 select lines: ['var1', 'var2'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var1=1, var2=1, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "35",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "351"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given sets:\n  A = {x \u2208 \u2115+  | x < 6}\n  B = {x \u2208 \u2115+ | x is even and x \u2264 6}\n  C = {x \u2208 \u2115+ | x is prime and x < 10}\n\nWe define the operation P(A) = {All subsets of A}, a set of all subsets of A. e.g., P({a,b}) = {{}, {a},{b},{a,b}}. Evaluate the set operation:Evaluate the set operation: P(A) & P(B) - P(A & B) + P(A) & P(C) - P(A & C) + P(B) & P(C) - P(B & C).",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "36",
    "answer": "[[{}]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "357"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-4 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 2 select lines: ['var0', 'var2'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var0=0, var2=1, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "37",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 0, 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "351"
  },
  {
    "question": "Give sets A = {a_1, a_2, ..., a_n} , we define the operation op(A) = {a_i op a_j | 1 <= i <= j <= n}, a set of all results of the operation op applied to two elements of A. We define \\o(p)(a,b) = a*b mod p. If A = {1,2,2^2,2^3,...,2^1024}, Evaluate the set operation (\\o(120))^2025(A).",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "38",
    "answer": "[[{1, 2, 4, 8, 16, 32, 64}]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "285"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-8 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 3 select lines: ['var4', 'var0', 'var5'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var4=1, var0=1, var5=0, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "39",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "367"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-8 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 3 select lines: ['var3', 'var1', 'var5'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var3=0, var1=0, var5=0, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "40",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "367"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-16 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 4 select lines: ['var3', 'var4', 'var2', 'var5'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var3=1, var4=1, var2=1, var5=0, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "41",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "384"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-16 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 4 select lines: ['var5', 'var1', 'var2', 'var7'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var5=0, var1=0, var2=1, var7=1, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "42",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "384"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-16 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 4 select lines: ['var7', 'var2', 'var1', 'var0'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var7=0, var2=1, var1=1, var0=0, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "43",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "384"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-16 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 4 select lines: ['var1', 'var6', 'var0', 'var2'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var1=1, var6=0, var0=1, var2=1, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "44",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "384"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-16 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 4 select lines: ['var4', 'var3', 'var7', 'var2'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var4=0, var3=0, var7=0, var2=1, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "45",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "384"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-4 multiplexer. The MUX has 2 select lines: ['var_B', 'var_C'], and the following logic expressions for each output: (var_B) \u2227 (var_D), (var_A) \u2227 (var_D), (var_A) \u2227 (var_B), (var_B) \u2227 (var_D). Given the variable values: var_A=0, var_B=0, var_C=1, var_D=1, what is the output of the MUX? Please provide the output of the MUX in the format of [[0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "46",
    "answer": "[[0]]",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "375"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-4 multiplexer. The MUX has 2 select lines: ['var_B', 'var_C'], and the following logic expressions for each output: (var_B) \u2227 (var_C), (var_A) \u2227 (var_B), (var_B) \u2227 (var_A), (var_C) \u2227 (var_D). Given the variable values: var_A=0, var_B=0, var_C=1, var_D=1, what is the output of the MUX? Please provide the output of the MUX in the format of [[0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "47",
    "answer": "[[0]]",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "375"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-4 multiplexer. The MUX has 2 select lines: ['var_B', 'var_A'], and the following logic expressions for each output: (var_B) \u2227 (var_A), (var_A) \u2227 (var_D), (var_B) \u2227 (var_D), (var_D) \u2227 (var_C). Given the variable values: var_A=0, var_B=1, var_C=1, var_D=1, what is the output of the MUX? Please provide the output of the MUX in the format of [[1]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "48",
    "answer": "[[1]]",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "375"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-4 multiplexer. The MUX has 2 select lines: ['var_D', 'var_B'], and the following logic expressions for each output: (var_D) \u2227 (var_B), (var_B) \u2227 (var_D), (var_B) \u2227 (var_A), (var_D) \u2227 (var_A). Given the variable values: var_A=1, var_B=0, var_C=0, var_D=1, what is the output of the MUX? Please provide the output of the MUX in the format of [[0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "49",
    "answer": "[[0]]",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "375"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-4 multiplexer. The MUX has 2 select lines: ['var_A', 'var_D'], and the following logic expressions for each output: (var_B) \u2227 (var_C), (var_C) \u2227 (var_A), (var_B) \u2227 (var_C), (var_C) \u2227 (var_D). Given the variable values: var_A=1, var_B=1, var_C=0, var_D=0, what is the output of the MUX? Please provide the output of the MUX in the format of [[0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "50",
    "answer": "[[0]]",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "375"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-16 multiplexer. The MUX has 4 select lines: ['var_E', 'var_D', 'var_C', 'var_B'], and the following logic expressions for each output: (var_D) \u2227 (var_G) \u2227 (var_E), (var_G) \u2227 (var_B) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_F), (var_C) \u2227 (var_D) \u2227 (var_G), (var_G) \u2227 (var_C) \u2227 (var_D), (var_H) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_C) \u2227 (var_B), (var_F) \u2227 (var_H) \u2227 (var_A) \u2227 (var_D), (var_D) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_C), (var_D) \u2227 (var_F), (var_C) \u2227 (var_H), (var_F) \u2227 (var_C), (var_A) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_H), (var_H) \u2227 (var_B), (var_D) \u2227 (var_G), (var_B) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_D) \u2227 (var_F), (var_D) \u2227 (var_F), (var_F) \u2227 (var_A). Given the variable values: var_A=1, var_B=1, var_C=0, var_D=1, var_E=0, var_F=1, var_G=0, var_H=1, what is the output of the MUX? Please provide the output of the MUX in the format of [[1]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "51",
    "answer": "[[1]]",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "788"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-8 multiplexer. The MUX has 3 select lines: ['var_F', 'var_A', 'var_B'], and the following logic expressions for each output: (var_E) \u2227 (var_A), (var_F) \u2227 (var_B) \u2227 (var_A), (var_A) \u2227 (var_C), (var_F) \u2227 (var_C) \u2227 (var_B), (var_F) \u2227 (var_C), (var_F) \u2227 (var_D) \u2227 (var_B), (var_B) \u2227 (var_F), (var_C) \u2227 (var_D). Given the variable values: var_A=0, var_B=1, var_C=1, var_D=0, var_E=1, var_F=0, what is the output of the MUX? Please provide the output of the MUX in the format of [[0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "52",
    "answer": "[[0]]",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "508"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-32 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 5 select lines: ['var9', 'var8', 'var7', 'var4', 'var1'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var9=0, var8=0, var7=0, var4=1, var1=1, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "53",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "400"
  },
  {
    "question": "Give sets A = {a_1, a_2, ..., a_n} , we define the operation op(A) = {a_i op a_j | 1 <= i <= j <= n}, a set of all results of the operation op applied to two elements of A. We define \\o(p)(a,b) = a*b mod p. If A =  {1,2,3,5,8,12,13,21,34,55,89}, Evaluate the set operation (\\o(111))^25(A).",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "54",
    "answer": "[[{1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59, 60, 61, 62, 63, 64, 65, 66, 67, 68, 69, 70, 71, 72, 73, 75, 76, 77, 78, 79, 80, 81, 82, 83, 84, 85, 86, 87, 88, 89, 90, 91, 92, 93, 94, 95, 96, 97, 98, 99, 100, 101, 102, 103, 104, 105, 106, 107, 108, 109, 110}]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "289"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-32 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 5 select lines: ['var3', 'var6', 'var2', 'var4', 'var9'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var3=0, var6=0, var2=1, var4=0, var9=0, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "55",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "400"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-32 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 5 select lines: ['var7', 'var4', 'var8', 'var3', 'var2'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var7=1, var4=1, var8=0, var3=1, var2=0, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "56",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "400"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-32 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 5 select lines: ['var7', 'var1', 'var6', 'var5', 'var0'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var7=1, var1=1, var6=1, var5=0, var0=0, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "57",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "400"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-32 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 5 select lines: ['var3', 'var5', 'var9', 'var0', 'var4'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var3=1, var5=1, var9=1, var0=0, var4=0, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "58",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "400"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-32 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 5 select lines: ['var4', 'var7', 'var0', 'var1', 'var9'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var4=1, var7=1, var0=0, var1=1, var9=1, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "59",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "400"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-32 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 5 select lines: ['var4', 'var1', 'var9', 'var6', 'var7'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var4=0, var1=0, var9=1, var6=0, var7=0, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "60",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "400"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D, E, F, G and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "61",
    "answer": "[[A'G+B'C'F+ABDE]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "10236"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-32 multiplexer. The MUX has 5 select lines: ['var_D', 'var_H', 'var_J', 'var_C', 'var_A'], and the following logic expressions for each output: (var_H) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_I) \u2227 (var_A), (var_D) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_A), (var_D) \u2227 (var_J), (var_A) \u2227 (var_E), (var_C) \u2227 (var_A) \u2227 (var_F), (var_A) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_B) \u2227 (var_J), (var_E) \u2227 (var_C) \u2227 (var_I) \u2227 (var_H), (var_G) \u2227 (var_F), (var_F) \u2227 (var_D) \u2227 (var_G) \u2227 (var_C), (var_C) \u2227 (var_B) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_J) \u2227 (var_I), (var_D) \u2227 (var_I), (var_B) \u2227 (var_H) \u2227 (var_D) \u2227 (var_F), (var_F) \u2227 (var_G) \u2227 (var_C) \u2227 (var_E), (var_A) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_I) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_G), (var_A) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_H) \u2227 (var_F), (var_D) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_C) \u2227 (var_B) \u2227 (var_H), (var_C) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_J) \u2227 (var_B), (var_F) \u2227 (var_A), (var_A) \u2227 (var_J), (var_E) \u2227 (var_D) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_A), (var_G) \u2227 (var_H) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_D), (var_B) \u2227 (var_D) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_A) \u2227 (var_G), (var_C) \u2227 (var_D) \u2227 (var_B), (var_D) \u2227 (var_I), (var_C) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_F), (var_G) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_B) \u2227 (var_C), (var_F) \u2227 (var_B) \u2227 (var_I) \u2227 (var_D) \u2227 (var_E), (var_D) \u2227 (var_A) \u2227 (var_C) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_E), (var_H) \u2227 (var_B) \u2227 (var_J), (var_G) \u2227 (var_I) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_H), (var_F) \u2227 (var_E), (var_F) \u2227 (var_A) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_J) \u2227 (var_C). Given the variable values: var_A=0, var_B=1, var_C=0, var_D=0, var_E=1, var_F=1, var_G=1, var_H=1, var_I=1, var_J=0, what is the output of the MUX? Please provide the output of the MUX in the format of [[0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "62",
    "answer": "[[0]]",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "1519"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-64 multiplexer. The MUX has 6 select lines: ['var_A', 'var_E', 'var_F', 'var_K', 'var_D', 'var_B'], and the following logic expressions for each output: (var_L) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_A), (var_D) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_L) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_A), (var_G) \u2227 (var_J) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_K), (var_L) \u2227 (var_G) \u2227 (var_C), (var_J) \u2227 (var_G) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_H) \u2227 (var_I), (var_J) \u2227 (var_L) \u2227 (var_H) \u2227 (var_D), (var_E) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_D) \u2227 (var_I) \u2227 (var_L), (var_A) \u2227 (var_B) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_J), (var_F) \u2227 (var_C), (var_F) \u2227 (var_L) \u2227 (var_E), (var_D) \u2227 (var_I) \u2227 (var_G) \u2227 (var_L) \u2227 (var_H) \u2227 (var_E), (var_H) \u2227 (var_K) \u2227 (var_D), (var_A) \u2227 (var_H) \u2227 (var_C) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_I), (var_C) \u2227 (var_K) \u2227 (var_I) \u2227 (var_E), (var_B) \u2227 (var_C) \u2227 (var_D) \u2227 (var_A) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_E), (var_I) \u2227 (var_A) \u2227 (var_D) \u2227 (var_H), (var_L) \u2227 (var_H) \u2227 (var_B) \u2227 (var_K), (var_K) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_L) \u2227 (var_G) \u2227 (var_D), (var_L) \u2227 (var_J) \u2227 (var_I) \u2227 (var_G), (var_F) \u2227 (var_B) \u2227 (var_J), (var_D) \u2227 (var_A) \u2227 (var_K) \u2227 (var_L) \u2227 (var_H), (var_G) \u2227 (var_B), (var_F) \u2227 (var_C) \u2227 (var_B) \u2227 (var_J) \u2227 (var_H), (var_B) \u2227 (var_I) \u2227 (var_K), (var_B) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_E), (var_K) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_J) \u2227 (var_I), (var_H) \u2227 (var_L) \u2227 (var_A) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_I), (var_A) \u2227 (var_D) \u2227 (var_G) \u2227 (var_C) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_I), (var_B) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_C), (var_C) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_I) \u2227 (var_K), (var_F) \u2227 (var_A) \u2227 (var_H) \u2227 (var_I), (var_L) \u2227 (var_C) \u2227 (var_G) \u2227 (var_I) \u2227 (var_J), (var_B) \u2227 (var_I) \u2227 (var_C) \u2227 (var_K) \u2227 (var_L) \u2227 (var_H), (var_L) \u2227 (var_A) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_J) \u2227 (var_C) \u2227 (var_B), (var_J) \u2227 (var_B) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_A) \u2227 (var_I), (var_B) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_J) \u2227 (var_L), (var_C) \u2227 (var_B) \u2227 (var_K) \u2227 (var_J), (var_A) \u2227 (var_L) \u2227 (var_B) \u2227 (var_J) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_D), (var_D) \u2227 (var_A) \u2227 (var_I) \u2227 (var_G) \u2227 (var_H) \u2227 (var_K), (var_I) \u2227 (var_L), (var_L) \u2227 (var_B) \u2227 (var_D) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_G), (var_I) \u2227 (var_C), (var_I) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_D), (var_I) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_H), (var_J) \u2227 (var_H) \u2227 (var_G) \u2227 (var_I) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_C), (var_A) \u2227 (var_H) \u2227 (var_B) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_D) \u2227 (var_F), (var_K) \u2227 (var_H), (var_L) \u2227 (var_J) \u2227 (var_B) \u2227 (var_K) \u2227 (var_D), (var_K) \u2227 (var_A) \u2227 (var_C) \u2227 (var_I) \u2227 (var_L), (var_B) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_G) \u2227 (var_A), (var_E) \u2227 (var_G) \u2227 (var_A), (var_J) \u2227 (var_K) \u2227 (var_A) \u2227 (var_C) \u2227 (var_B) \u2227 (var_D), (var_G) \u2227 (var_D) \u2227 (var_L) \u2227 (var_H) \u2227 (var_K), (var_H) \u2227 (var_D), (var_A) \u2227 (var_B) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_H) \u2227 (var_D) \u2227 (var_I), (var_K) \u2227 (var_A) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_H) \u2227 (var_D) \u2227 (var_B), (var_C) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_G) \u2227 (var_L), (var_L) \u2227 (var_B) \u2227 (var_H), (var_J) \u2227 (var_L), (var_L) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_I) \u2227 (var_B) \u2227 (var_J) \u2227 (var_K), (var_E) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_I), (var_A) \u2227 (var_K) \u2227 (var_G) \u2227 (var_C) \u2227 (var_E), (var_C) \u2227 (var_K) \u2227 (var_E) \u2227 (var_F) \u2227 (var_A), (var_H) \u2227 (var_D) \u2227 (var_G) \u2227 (var_I) \u2227 (var_L). Given the variable values: var_A=1, var_B=1, var_C=0, var_D=0, var_E=1, var_F=0, var_G=0, var_H=1, var_I=1, var_J=1, var_K=1, var_L=1, what is the output of the MUX? Please provide the output of the MUX in the format of [[0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "63",
    "answer": "[[0]]",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "3074"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-32 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 5 select lines: ['var6', 'var7', 'var5', 'var2', 'var4'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var6=1, var7=0, var5=1, var2=1, var4=0, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "64",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "400"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "65",
    "answer": "[[A'+B+C]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "608"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "66",
    "answer": "[[A'B+C+D]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1107"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given sets A = {1, 2, 4, 5, 7}, B = {1, 2, 4, 5, 6}, C = {0, 1, 2, 4, 7}, D = {0, 1, 4, 5, 6}, we define cartesian product as the set of all ordered pairs (a, b) where a is in A and b is in B, i.e. A x B =  a set that contains all the ordered pairs (a, b) where a is in A and b is in B. We define Symmetric Difference as the set of all elements that are in not in either of the two sets, i.e. Symmetric Difference of A and B = A - B union B - A.  Evaluate the Symmetric Difference of the first term, (Symmetric Difference of P(C) and P(A)) and the second term, (Union of P(C) and P(A)).",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "67",
    "answer": "[[{{1, 4}, {1, 2, 4, 7}, {1}, {1, 4, 7}, {1, 7}, {1, 2, 7}, {2, 4}, {4, 7}, {2, 7}, {2, 4, 7}, {4}, {2}, {1, 2, 4}, {1, 2}, {7}, {}}]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "586"
  },
  {
    "question": "Give sets A = {a_1, a_2, ..., a_n} , we define the operation op(A) = {a_i op a_j | 1 <= i <= j <= n}, a set of all results of the operation op applied to two elements of A. We define \\o(p)(a,b) = a*b mod p. If A = {2,3,5,7}, Evaluate the set operation (\\o(121))^25(A).",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "68",
    "answer": "[[{1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 53, 54, 56, 57, 58, 59, 60, 61, 62, 63, 64, 65, 67, 68, 69, 70, 71, 72, 73, 74, 75, 76, 78, 79, 80, 81, 82, 83, 84, 85, 86, 87, 89, 90, 91, 92, 93, 94, 95, 96, 97, 98, 100, 101, 102, 103, 104, 105, 106, 107, 108, 109, 111, 112, 113, 114, 115, 116, 117, 118, 119, 120}]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "268"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "69",
    "answer": "[[A'+B+C]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "608"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "70",
    "answer": "[[A'+B+C]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "608"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "71",
    "answer": "[[A'+B+C]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "608"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "72",
    "answer": "[[A'B+C+D]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1107"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "73",
    "answer": "[[A'B+C+D]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1107"
  },
  {
    "question": "Give sets A = {a_1, a_2, ..., a_n} , we define the operation op(A) = {a_i op a_j | 1 <= i <= j <= n}, a set of all results of the operation op applied to two elements of A. We define \\o(p)(a,b) = a*b mod p. If A = {2,3,5,7}, Evaluate the set operation (\\o(33))^5(A).",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "74",
    "answer": "[[{1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32}]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "266"
  },
  {
    "question": "T flip-flops: Inputs TA=0, TB=0, Current states QA=0, QB=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "75",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "185"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=0, DB=0, Current states QA=1, QB=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "76",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "185"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "77",
    "answer": "[[A'B+C+D]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1107"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=1, DB=0, Current states QA=0, QB=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "78",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "185"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=1, DB=0, Current states QA=0, QB=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "79",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "185"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "80",
    "answer": "[[A'B+C+D]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1107"
  },
  {
    "question": "T flip-flops: Inputs TA=0, TB=1, Current states QA=0, QB=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "81",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "185"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D, E and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "82",
    "answer": "[[A'+B'C'+BDE]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "2230"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=0, DB=0, Current states QA=1, QB=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "83",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "185"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=1, KA=1, JB=0, KB=0, Current states QA=0, QB=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "84",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "198"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D, E and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "85",
    "answer": "[[A'+B'C'+BDE]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "2230"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D, E and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "86",
    "answer": "[[A'+B'C'+BDE]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "2230"
  },
  {
    "question": "T flip-flops: Inputs TA=1, TB=0, Current states QA=0, QB=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "87",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "185"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=0, KA=1, JB=0, KB=1, Current states QA=1, QB=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "88",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "198"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=0, DB=1, Current states QA=1, QB=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "89",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "185"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=0, KA=1, JB=1, KB=0, Current states QA=0, QB=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "90",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "198"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=0, KA=1, JB=0, KB=1, Current states QA=1, QB=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "91",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "198"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D, E and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "92",
    "answer": "[[A'+B'C'+BDE]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "2230"
  },
  {
    "question": "T flip-flops: Inputs TA=1, TB=1, Current states QA=1, QB=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "93",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "185"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D, E and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "94",
    "answer": "[[A'+B'C'+BDE]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "2230"
  },
  {
    "question": "Give sets A = {a_1, a_2, ..., a_n} , we define the operation op(A) = {a_i op a_j | 1 <= i <= j <= n}, a set of all results of the operation op applied to two elements of A. We define \\o(p)(a,b) = a*b mod p. If A = {1,2,4,24}, Evaluate the set operation (\\o(24))^5(A).",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "95",
    "answer": "[[{0, 1, 2, 4, 8, 16}]]",
    "difficulty": null,
    "length": "267"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=0, KA=1, JB=1, KB=1, Current states QA=0, QB=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "96",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "198"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=0, KA=1, JB=0, KB=1, Current states QA=0, QB=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "97",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "198"
  },
  {
    "question": "T flip-flops: Inputs TA=0, TB=0, TC=0, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "98",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=0, QC+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "197"
  },
  {
    "question": "T flip-flops: Inputs TA=1, TB=1, TC=1, Current states QA=1, QB=1, QC=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "99",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=0, QC+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "197"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=0, DB=0, DC=0, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "100",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=0, QC+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "197"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=0, DB=1, DC=0, Current states QA=0, QB=1, QC=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "101",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=1, QC+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "197"
  },
  {
    "question": "T flip-flops: Inputs TA=0, TB=0, TC=0, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "102",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=0, QC+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "197"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=1, KA=1, JB=1, KB=1, JC=0, KC=1, Current states QA=1, QB=1, QC=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "103",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=0, QC+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "216"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D, E, F and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "104",
    "answer": "[[A'+BC+DEF]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "4729"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=0, DB=0, DC=0, Current states QA=1, QB=1, QC=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "105",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=0, QC+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "197"
  },
  {
    "question": "T flip-flops: Inputs TA=1, TB=0, TC=1, Current states QA=0, QB=1, QC=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "106",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=1, QC+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "197"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=1, KA=0, JB=1, KB=0, JC=0, KC=0, Current states QA=1, QB=0, QC=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "107",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=1, QC+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "216"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=1, KA=1, JB=1, KB=1, JC=1, KC=0, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "108",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=1, QC+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "216"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=0, DB=0, DC=1, DD=0, Current states QA=1, QB=1, QC=1, QD=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "109",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=0, QC+=1, QD+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "209"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=0, DB=1, DC=1, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "110",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=1, QC+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "197"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=1, KA=1, JB=0, KB=1, JC=0, KC=0, Current states QA=0, QB=1, QC=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "111",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0, QC+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "216"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=0, KA=1, JB=1, KB=0, JC=1, KC=1, Current states QA=0, QB=1, QC=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "112",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=1, QC+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "216"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=1, KA=1, JB=1, KB=0, JC=0, KC=1, Current states QA=1, QB=0, QC=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "113",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=1, QC+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "216"
  },
  {
    "question": "T flip-flops: Inputs TA=1, TB=1, TC=0, TD=0, Current states QA=0, QB=1, QC=0, QD=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "114",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0, QC+=0, QD+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "209"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=0, DB=0, DC=1, DD=1, Current states QA=1, QB=0, QC=0, QD=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "115",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=0, QC+=1, QD+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "209"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=1, DB=1, DC=0, DD=1, Current states QA=0, QB=1, QC=0, QD=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "116",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=1, QC+=0, QD+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "209"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=0, DB=1, DC=0, DD=1, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=0, QD=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "117",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=1, QC+=0, QD+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "209"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=1, KA=1, JB=0, KB=1, JC=0, KC=0, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "118",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0, QC+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "216"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=0, DB=1, DC=1, DD=0, Current states QA=0, QB=1, QC=1, QD=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "119",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=1, QC+=1, QD+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "209"
  },
  {
    "question": "T flip-flops: Inputs TA=0, TB=0, TC=0, TD=0, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=1, QD=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "120",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=0, QC+=1, QD+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "209"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=1, DB=0, DC=0, DD=1, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=0, QD=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "121",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0, QC+=0, QD+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "209"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=0, DB=1, DC=1, DD=0, Current states QA=1, QB=0, QC=0, QD=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "122",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=1, QC+=1, QD+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "209"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=0, DB=1, DC=1, DD=1, Current states QA=0, QB=1, QC=0, QD=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "123",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=1, QC+=1, QD+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "209"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=1, DB=0, DC=1, DD=0, Current states QA=0, QB=1, QC=1, QD=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "124",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0, QC+=1, QD+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "209"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=1, DB=0, DC=1, DD=0, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=1, QD=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "125",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0, QC+=1, QD+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "209"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=1, KA=0, JB=1, KB=0, JC=0, KC=1, Current states QA=1, QB=1, QC=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "126",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=1, QC+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "216"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=1, KA=1, JB=0, KB=1, JC=0, KC=1, Current states QA=0, QB=1, QC=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "127",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0, QC+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "216"
  },
  {
    "question": "T flip-flops: Inputs TA=0, TB=0, TC=1, TD=1, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=1, QD=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "128",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=0, QC+=0, QD+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "209"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=0, DB=1, DC=0, DD=1, DE=1, Current states QA=1, QB=0, QC=0, QD=0, QE=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "129",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=1, QC+=0, QD+=1, QE+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "221"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=1, DB=1, DC=0, DD=0, DE=0, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=0, QD=1, QE=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "130",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=1, QC+=0, QD+=0, QE+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "221"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=1, DB=0, DC=0, DD=0, Current states QA=1, QB=1, QC=1, QD=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "131",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0, QC+=0, QD+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "209"
  },
  {
    "question": "T flip-flops: Inputs TA=1, TB=1, TC=0, TD=0, Current states QA=1, QB=0, QC=0, QD=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "132",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=1, QC+=0, QD+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "209"
  },
  {
    "question": "T flip-flops: Inputs TA=1, TB=0, TC=0, TD=1, TE=0, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=1, QD=1, QE=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "133",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0, QC+=1, QD+=0, QE+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "221"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=0, KA=1, JB=1, KB=0, JC=0, KC=1, JD=1, KD=1, Current states QA=1, QB=1, QC=0, QD=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "134",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=1, QC+=0, QD+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "234"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=0, KA=1, JB=1, KB=0, JC=1, KC=1, JD=1, KD=0, Current states QA=0, QB=1, QC=0, QD=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "135",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=1, QC+=1, QD+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "234"
  },
  {
    "question": "T flip-flops: Inputs TA=0, TB=0, TC=0, TD=1, TE=1, Current states QA=1, QB=0, QC=1, QD=1, QE=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "136",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0, QC+=1, QD+=0, QE+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "221"
  },
  {
    "question": "T flip-flops: Inputs TA=1, TB=0, TC=1, TD=1, TE=0, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=0, QD=0, QE=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "137",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0, QC+=1, QD+=1, QE+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "221"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=1, DB=1, DC=1, DD=1, DE=1, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=0, QD=0, QE=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "138",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=1, QC+=1, QD+=1, QE+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "221"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=1, DB=0, DC=0, DD=1, DE=0, Current states QA=1, QB=0, QC=1, QD=1, QE=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "139",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0, QC+=0, QD+=1, QE+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "221"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=0, KA=0, JB=1, KB=1, JC=0, KC=1, JD=1, KD=1, Current states QA=1, QB=0, QC=1, QD=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "140",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=1, QC+=0, QD+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "234"
  },
  {
    "question": "T flip-flops: Inputs TA=1, TB=0, TC=1, TD=0, TE=1, Current states QA=1, QB=1, QC=1, QD=1, QE=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "141",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=1, QC+=0, QD+=1, QE+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "221"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=1, KA=1, JB=1, KB=0, JC=1, KC=1, JD=0, KD=0, Current states QA=0, QB=1, QC=1, QD=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "142",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=1, QC+=0, QD+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "234"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D, E, F and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "143",
    "answer": "[[A'+BC+DEF]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "4729"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=1, DB=0, DC=1, DD=0, DE=0, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=0, QD=1, QE=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "144",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0, QC+=1, QD+=0, QE+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "221"
  },
  {
    "question": "T flip-flops: Inputs TA=0, TB=1, TC=0, TD=1, TE=0, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=1, QD=1, QE=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "145",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=1, QC+=1, QD+=0, QE+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "221"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=0, KA=0, JB=0, KB=0, JC=0, KC=1, JD=0, KD=1, JE=0, KE=1, Current states QA=0, QB=1, QC=0, QD=1, QE=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "146",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=1, QC+=0, QD+=0, QE+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "252"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=1, DB=0, DC=0, DD=0, DE=0, Current states QA=1, QB=0, QC=0, QD=0, QE=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "147",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0, QC+=0, QD+=0, QE+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "221"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=1, KA=0, JB=1, KB=0, JC=0, KC=1, JD=1, KD=0, JE=0, KE=1, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=0, QD=1, QE=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "148",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=1, QC+=0, QD+=1, QE+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "252"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=1, KA=0, JB=1, KB=0, JC=0, KC=0, JD=0, KD=1, JE=1, KE=1, Current states QA=0, QB=1, QC=0, QD=0, QE=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "149",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=1, QC+=0, QD+=0, QE+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "252"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=1, DB=0, DC=1, DD=0, DE=0, DF=0, Current states QA=1, QB=1, QC=0, QD=0, QE=0, QF=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "150",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0, QC+=1, QD+=0, QE+=0, QF+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "233"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D, E, F, G and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "151",
    "answer": "[[A'G+B'C'F+ABDE]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "10236"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=1, DB=0, DC=1, DD=1, DE=0, DF=0, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=0, QD=1, QE=1, QF=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "152",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0, QC+=1, QD+=1, QE+=0, QF+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "233"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D, E, F, G and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "153",
    "answer": "[[A'G+B'C'F+ABDE]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "10236"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=0, KA=1, JB=0, KB=1, JC=1, KC=1, JD=1, KD=1, JE=0, KE=0, Current states QA=0, QB=1, QC=0, QD=0, QE=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "154",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=0, QC+=1, QD+=1, QE+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "252"
  },
  {
    "question": "T flip-flops: Inputs TA=1, TB=0, TC=1, TD=1, TE=1, TF=0, Current states QA=1, QB=1, QC=0, QD=0, QE=1, QF=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "155",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=1, QC+=1, QD+=1, QE+=0, QF+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "233"
  },
  {
    "question": "T flip-flops: Inputs TA=0, TB=1, TC=1, TD=1, TE=0, TF=1, Current states QA=1, QB=1, QC=1, QD=1, QE=0, QF=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "156",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0, QC+=0, QD+=0, QE+=0, QF+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "233"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=0, DB=0, DC=1, DD=1, DE=0, DF=1, Current states QA=0, QB=1, QC=1, QD=1, QE=1, QF=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "157",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=0, QC+=1, QD+=1, QE+=0, QF+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "233"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=1, DB=0, DC=1, DD=1, DE=0, DF=0, Current states QA=0, QB=1, QC=1, QD=0, QE=1, QF=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "158",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0, QC+=1, QD+=1, QE+=0, QF+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "233"
  },
  {
    "question": "T flip-flops: Inputs TA=1, TB=1, TC=0, TD=0, TE=0, TF=1, Current states QA=1, QB=1, QC=0, QD=1, QE=0, QF=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "159",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=0, QC+=0, QD+=1, QE+=0, QF+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "233"
  },
  {
    "question": "T flip-flops: Inputs TA=0, TB=1, TC=1, TD=0, TE=0, TF=0, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=1, QD=0, QE=0, QF=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "160",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=1, QC+=0, QD+=0, QE+=0, QF+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "233"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=1, DB=0, DC=0, DD=0, DE=1, DF=1, Current states QA=0, QB=1, QC=1, QD=0, QE=1, QF=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "161",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0, QC+=0, QD+=0, QE+=1, QF+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "233"
  },
  {
    "question": "D flip-flops: Inputs DA=0, DB=1, DC=0, DD=1, DE=1, DF=1, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=1, QD=1, QE=0, QF=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "162",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=1, QC+=0, QD+=1, QE+=1, QF+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "233"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=1, KA=0, JB=1, KB=0, JC=1, KC=0, JD=1, KD=0, JE=0, KE=1, JF=1, KF=1, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=1, QD=0, QE=1, QF=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "163",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=1, QC+=1, QD+=1, QE+=0, QF+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "270"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=0, KA=0, JB=0, KB=1, JC=1, KC=0, JD=1, KD=1, JE=1, KE=0, JF=1, KF=0, Current states QA=1, QB=0, QC=1, QD=0, QE=0, QF=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "164",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0, QC+=1, QD+=1, QE+=1, QF+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "270"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 2-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11. Over the next 4 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: . What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "165",
    "answer": "[[11 -> 10 -> 01 -> 00]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "177"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 2-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11. Over the next 4 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: . What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "166",
    "answer": "[[11 -> 10 -> 01 -> 00]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "177"
  },
  {
    "question": "T flip-flops: Inputs TA=1, TB=0, TC=1, TD=1, TE=0, TF=1, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=1, QD=0, QE=0, QF=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "167",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0, QC+=0, QD+=1, QE+=0, QF+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "233"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 2-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11. Over the next 4 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: . What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "168",
    "answer": "[[11 -> 10 -> 01 -> 00]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "177"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 2-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11. Over the next 4 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: . What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "169",
    "answer": "[[11 -> 10 -> 01 -> 00]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "177"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 2-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11. Over the next 4 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: . What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "170",
    "answer": "[[11 -> 10 -> 01 -> 00]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "177"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 2-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11. Over the next 4 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: . What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "171",
    "answer": "[[11 -> 10 -> 01 -> 00]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "177"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=1, KA=0, JB=0, KB=1, JC=1, KC=1, JD=1, KD=1, JE=0, KE=0, JF=1, KF=1, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=1, QD=1, QE=0, QF=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "172",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0, QC+=0, QD+=0, QE+=0, QF+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "270"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 2-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11. Over the next 4 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: . What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "173",
    "answer": "[[11 -> 10 -> 01 -> 00]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "177"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 2-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11. Over the next 4 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: . What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "174",
    "answer": "[[11 -> 10 -> 01 -> 00]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "177"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 2-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11. Over the next 4 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: . What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "175",
    "answer": "[[11 -> 10 -> 01 -> 00]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "177"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 2-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11. Over the next 4 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: . What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "176",
    "answer": "[[11 -> 10 -> 01 -> 00]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "177"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 2-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11. Over the next 4 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: . What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "177",
    "answer": "[[11 -> 10 -> 01 -> 00]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "177"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 2-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11. Over the next 4 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: . What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "178",
    "answer": "[[11 -> 10 -> 01 -> 00]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "177"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=0, KA=0, JB=0, KB=0, JC=1, KC=0, JD=1, KD=1, JE=1, KE=1, JF=0, KF=1, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=1, QD=0, QE=0, QF=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "179",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=0, QC+=1, QD+=1, QE+=1, QF+=0]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "270"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 2-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11. Over the next 4 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: . What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "180",
    "answer": "[[11 -> 10 -> 01 -> 00]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "177"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 2-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11. Over the next 4 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: . What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "181",
    "answer": "[[11 -> 10 -> 01 -> 00]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "177"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 2-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11. Over the next 4 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: . What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "182",
    "answer": "[[11 -> 10 -> 01 -> 00]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "177"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 2-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11. Over the next 4 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: . What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "183",
    "answer": "[[11 -> 10 -> 01 -> 00]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "177"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 2-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11. Over the next 4 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: . What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "184",
    "answer": "[[11 -> 10 -> 01 -> 00]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "177"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 2-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11. Over the next 4 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: . What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "185",
    "answer": "[[11 -> 10 -> 01 -> 00]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "177"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 2-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11. Over the next 4 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: . What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "186",
    "answer": "[[11 -> 10 -> 01 -> 00]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "177"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 3-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111. Over the next 6 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111, 110. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "187",
    "answer": "[[111 -> 110 -> 101 -> 100 -> 011 -> 010]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "186"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 2-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11. Over the next 4 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: . What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "188",
    "answer": "[[11 -> 10 -> 01 -> 00]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "177"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 3-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111. Over the next 6 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111, 110. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "189",
    "answer": "[[111 -> 110 -> 101 -> 100 -> 011 -> 010]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "186"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 3-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111. Over the next 6 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111, 110. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "190",
    "answer": "[[111 -> 110 -> 101 -> 100 -> 011 -> 010]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "186"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D, E, F and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "191",
    "answer": "[[A'+BC+DEF]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "4729"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 3-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111. Over the next 6 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111, 110. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "192",
    "answer": "[[111 -> 110 -> 101 -> 100 -> 011 -> 010]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "186"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 3-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111. Over the next 6 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111, 110. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "193",
    "answer": "[[111 -> 110 -> 101 -> 100 -> 011 -> 010]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "186"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=0, KA=0, JB=0, KB=0, JC=0, KC=0, JD=0, KD=0, JE=0, KE=1, JF=1, KF=0, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=1, QD=0, QE=1, QF=1. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "194",
    "answer": "[[QA+=0, QB+=0, QC+=1, QD+=0, QE+=0, QF+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "270"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 3-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111. Over the next 6 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111, 110. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "195",
    "answer": "[[111 -> 110 -> 101 -> 100 -> 011 -> 010]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "186"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 3-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111. Over the next 6 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111, 110. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "196",
    "answer": "[[111 -> 110 -> 101 -> 100 -> 011 -> 010]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "186"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 3-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111. Over the next 6 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111, 110. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "197",
    "answer": "[[111 -> 110 -> 101 -> 100 -> 011 -> 010]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "186"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 3-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111. Over the next 6 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111, 110. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "198",
    "answer": "[[111 -> 110 -> 101 -> 100 -> 011 -> 010]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "186"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 3-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111. Over the next 6 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111, 110. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "199",
    "answer": "[[111 -> 110 -> 101 -> 100 -> 011 -> 010]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "186"
  },
  {
    "question": "JK flip-flops: Inputs JA=1, KA=0, JB=0, KB=0, JC=0, KC=1, JD=0, KD=0, JE=1, KE=0, JF=1, KF=1, Current states QA=0, QB=0, QC=1, QD=1, QE=0, QF=0. What are the next states after one clock pulse? Please provide the next states in the format of [[Q1+=?, Q2+=?, ...]], where ? means 1 or 0",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "200",
    "answer": "[[QA+=1, QB+=0, QC+=0, QD+=1, QE+=1, QF+=1]]",
    "difficulty": "1",
    "length": "270"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 3-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111. Over the next 6 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111, 110. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "201",
    "answer": "[[111 -> 110 -> 101 -> 100 -> 011 -> 010]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "186"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 3-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111. Over the next 6 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111, 110. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "202",
    "answer": "[[111 -> 110 -> 101 -> 100 -> 011 -> 010]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "186"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 3-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111. Over the next 6 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111, 110. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "203",
    "answer": "[[111 -> 110 -> 101 -> 100 -> 011 -> 010]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "186"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 3-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111. Over the next 6 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111, 110. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "204",
    "answer": "[[111 -> 110 -> 101 -> 100 -> 011 -> 010]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "186"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 3-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111. Over the next 6 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111, 110. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "205",
    "answer": "[[111 -> 110 -> 101 -> 100 -> 011 -> 010]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "186"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 3-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111. Over the next 6 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111, 110. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "206",
    "answer": "[[111 -> 110 -> 101 -> 100 -> 011 -> 010]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "186"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 3-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111. Over the next 6 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111, 110. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "207",
    "answer": "[[111 -> 110 -> 101 -> 100 -> 011 -> 010]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "186"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 3-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111. Over the next 6 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111, 110. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "208",
    "answer": "[[111 -> 110 -> 101 -> 100 -> 011 -> 010]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "186"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 3-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111. Over the next 6 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111, 110. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "209",
    "answer": "[[111 -> 110 -> 101 -> 100 -> 011 -> 010]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "186"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 3-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111. Over the next 6 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111, 110. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "210",
    "answer": "[[111 -> 110 -> 101 -> 100 -> 011 -> 010]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "186"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 3-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111. Over the next 6 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111, 110. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "211",
    "answer": "[[111 -> 110 -> 101 -> 100 -> 011 -> 010]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "186"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 4-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 1111. Over the next 8 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 1111, 1110, 1101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "212",
    "answer": "[[1111 -> 1110 -> 1101 -> 1100 -> 1011 -> 1010 -> 1001 -> 1000]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "195"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 4-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 1111. Over the next 8 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 1111, 1110, 1101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "213",
    "answer": "[[1111 -> 1110 -> 1101 -> 1100 -> 1011 -> 1010 -> 1001 -> 1000]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "195"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 4-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 1111. Over the next 8 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 1111, 1110, 1101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "214",
    "answer": "[[1111 -> 1110 -> 1101 -> 1100 -> 1011 -> 1010 -> 1001 -> 1000]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "195"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 4-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 1111. Over the next 8 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 1111, 1110, 1101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "215",
    "answer": "[[1111 -> 1110 -> 1101 -> 1100 -> 1011 -> 1010 -> 1001 -> 1000]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "195"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 4-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 1111. Over the next 8 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 1111, 1110, 1101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "216",
    "answer": "[[1111 -> 1110 -> 1101 -> 1100 -> 1011 -> 1010 -> 1001 -> 1000]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "195"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 4-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 1111. Over the next 8 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 1111, 1110, 1101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "217",
    "answer": "[[1111 -> 1110 -> 1101 -> 1100 -> 1011 -> 1010 -> 1001 -> 1000]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "195"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 4-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 1111. Over the next 8 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 1111, 1110, 1101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "218",
    "answer": "[[1111 -> 1110 -> 1101 -> 1100 -> 1011 -> 1010 -> 1001 -> 1000]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "195"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 4-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 1111. Over the next 8 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 1111, 1110, 1101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "219",
    "answer": "[[1111 -> 1110 -> 1101 -> 1100 -> 1011 -> 1010 -> 1001 -> 1000]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "195"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 4-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 1111. Over the next 8 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 1111, 1110, 1101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "220",
    "answer": "[[1111 -> 1110 -> 1101 -> 1100 -> 1011 -> 1010 -> 1001 -> 1000]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "195"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 4-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 1111. Over the next 8 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 1111, 1110, 1101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "221",
    "answer": "[[1111 -> 1110 -> 1101 -> 1100 -> 1011 -> 1010 -> 1001 -> 1000]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "195"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 4-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 1111. Over the next 8 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 1111, 1110, 1101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "222",
    "answer": "[[1111 -> 1110 -> 1101 -> 1100 -> 1011 -> 1010 -> 1001 -> 1000]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "195"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 4-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 1111. Over the next 8 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 1111, 1110, 1101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "223",
    "answer": "[[1111 -> 1110 -> 1101 -> 1100 -> 1011 -> 1010 -> 1001 -> 1000]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "195"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 4-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 1111. Over the next 8 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 1111, 1110, 1101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "224",
    "answer": "[[1111 -> 1110 -> 1101 -> 1100 -> 1011 -> 1010 -> 1001 -> 1000]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "195"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 5-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11111. Over the next 10 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 11111, 11110, 11101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "225",
    "answer": "[[11111 -> 11110 -> 11101 -> 11100 -> 11011 -> 11010 -> 11001 -> 11000 -> 10111 -> 10110]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "200"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 5-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11111. Over the next 10 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 11111, 11110, 11101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "226",
    "answer": "[[11111 -> 11110 -> 11101 -> 11100 -> 11011 -> 11010 -> 11001 -> 11000 -> 10111 -> 10110]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "200"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 5-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11111. Over the next 10 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 11111, 11110, 11101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "227",
    "answer": "[[11111 -> 11110 -> 11101 -> 11100 -> 11011 -> 11010 -> 11001 -> 11000 -> 10111 -> 10110]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "200"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 5-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11111. Over the next 10 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 11111, 11110, 11101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "228",
    "answer": "[[11111 -> 11110 -> 11101 -> 11100 -> 11011 -> 11010 -> 11001 -> 11000 -> 10111 -> 10110]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "200"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 5-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11111. Over the next 10 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 11111, 11110, 11101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "229",
    "answer": "[[11111 -> 11110 -> 11101 -> 11100 -> 11011 -> 11010 -> 11001 -> 11000 -> 10111 -> 10110]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "200"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 5-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11111. Over the next 10 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 11111, 11110, 11101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "230",
    "answer": "[[11111 -> 11110 -> 11101 -> 11100 -> 11011 -> 11010 -> 11001 -> 11000 -> 10111 -> 10110]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "200"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 5-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11111. Over the next 10 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 11111, 11110, 11101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "231",
    "answer": "[[11111 -> 11110 -> 11101 -> 11100 -> 11011 -> 11010 -> 11001 -> 11000 -> 10111 -> 10110]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "200"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 5-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11111. Over the next 10 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 11111, 11110, 11101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "232",
    "answer": "[[11111 -> 11110 -> 11101 -> 11100 -> 11011 -> 11010 -> 11001 -> 11000 -> 10111 -> 10110]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "200"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 5-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11111. Over the next 10 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 11111, 11110, 11101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "233",
    "answer": "[[11111 -> 11110 -> 11101 -> 11100 -> 11011 -> 11010 -> 11001 -> 11000 -> 10111 -> 10110]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "200"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 5-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11111. Over the next 10 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 11111, 11110, 11101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "234",
    "answer": "[[11111 -> 11110 -> 11101 -> 11100 -> 11011 -> 11010 -> 11001 -> 11000 -> 10111 -> 10110]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "200"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 5-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11111. Over the next 10 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 11111, 11110, 11101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "235",
    "answer": "[[11111 -> 11110 -> 11101 -> 11100 -> 11011 -> 11010 -> 11001 -> 11000 -> 10111 -> 10110]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "200"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 5-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11111. Over the next 10 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 11111, 11110, 11101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "236",
    "answer": "[[11111 -> 11110 -> 11101 -> 11100 -> 11011 -> 11010 -> 11001 -> 11000 -> 10111 -> 10110]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "200"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 5-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11111. Over the next 10 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 11111, 11110, 11101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "237",
    "answer": "[[11111 -> 11110 -> 11101 -> 11100 -> 11011 -> 11010 -> 11001 -> 11000 -> 10111 -> 10110]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "200"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 5-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11111. Over the next 10 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 11111, 11110, 11101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "238",
    "answer": "[[11111 -> 11110 -> 11101 -> 11100 -> 11011 -> 11010 -> 11001 -> 11000 -> 10111 -> 10110]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "200"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 6-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111111. Over the next 12 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111111, 111110, 111101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "239",
    "answer": "[[111111 -> 111110 -> 111101 -> 111100 -> 111011 -> 111010 -> 111001 -> 111000 -> 110111 -> 110110 -> 110101 -> 110100]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "204"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 5-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11111. Over the next 10 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 11111, 11110, 11101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "240",
    "answer": "[[11111 -> 11110 -> 11101 -> 11100 -> 11011 -> 11010 -> 11001 -> 11000 -> 10111 -> 10110]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "200"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 5-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 11111. Over the next 10 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 11111, 11110, 11101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "241",
    "answer": "[[11111 -> 11110 -> 11101 -> 11100 -> 11011 -> 11010 -> 11001 -> 11000 -> 10111 -> 10110]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "200"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 6-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111111. Over the next 12 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111111, 111110, 111101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "242",
    "answer": "[[111111 -> 111110 -> 111101 -> 111100 -> 111011 -> 111010 -> 111001 -> 111000 -> 110111 -> 110110 -> 110101 -> 110100]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "204"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 6-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111111. Over the next 12 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111111, 111110, 111101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "243",
    "answer": "[[111111 -> 111110 -> 111101 -> 111100 -> 111011 -> 111010 -> 111001 -> 111000 -> 110111 -> 110110 -> 110101 -> 110100]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "204"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 6-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111111. Over the next 12 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111111, 111110, 111101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "244",
    "answer": "[[111111 -> 111110 -> 111101 -> 111100 -> 111011 -> 111010 -> 111001 -> 111000 -> 110111 -> 110110 -> 110101 -> 110100]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "204"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 6-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111111. Over the next 12 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111111, 111110, 111101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "245",
    "answer": "[[111111 -> 111110 -> 111101 -> 111100 -> 111011 -> 111010 -> 111001 -> 111000 -> 110111 -> 110110 -> 110101 -> 110100]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "204"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 6-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111111. Over the next 12 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111111, 111110, 111101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "246",
    "answer": "[[111111 -> 111110 -> 111101 -> 111100 -> 111011 -> 111010 -> 111001 -> 111000 -> 110111 -> 110110 -> 110101 -> 110100]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "204"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 6-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111111. Over the next 12 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111111, 111110, 111101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "247",
    "answer": "[[111111 -> 111110 -> 111101 -> 111100 -> 111011 -> 111010 -> 111001 -> 111000 -> 110111 -> 110110 -> 110101 -> 110100]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "204"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 6-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111111. Over the next 12 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111111, 111110, 111101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "248",
    "answer": "[[111111 -> 111110 -> 111101 -> 111100 -> 111011 -> 111010 -> 111001 -> 111000 -> 110111 -> 110110 -> 110101 -> 110100]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "204"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 6-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111111. Over the next 12 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111111, 111110, 111101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "249",
    "answer": "[[111111 -> 111110 -> 111101 -> 111100 -> 111011 -> 111010 -> 111001 -> 111000 -> 110111 -> 110110 -> 110101 -> 110100]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "204"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 6-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111111. Over the next 12 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111111, 111110, 111101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "250",
    "answer": "[[111111 -> 111110 -> 111101 -> 111100 -> 111011 -> 111010 -> 111001 -> 111000 -> 110111 -> 110110 -> 110101 -> 110100]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "204"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 6-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111111. Over the next 12 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111111, 111110, 111101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "251",
    "answer": "[[111111 -> 111110 -> 111101 -> 111100 -> 111011 -> 111010 -> 111001 -> 111000 -> 110111 -> 110110 -> 110101 -> 110100]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "204"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 1, 0, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "252",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "270"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 6-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111111. Over the next 12 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111111, 111110, 111101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "253",
    "answer": "[[111111 -> 111110 -> 111101 -> 111100 -> 111011 -> 111010 -> 111001 -> 111000 -> 110111 -> 110110 -> 110101 -> 110100]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "204"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 1, 0, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "254",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "270"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 1, 0, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "255",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "270"
  },
  {
    "question": "A 6-bit binary ripple counter starts at state 111111. Over the next 12 clock cycles, the counter decreases in states. The first few states are: 111111, 111110, 111101. What is the full sequence of states?",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "256",
    "answer": "[[111111 -> 111110 -> 111101 -> 111100 -> 111011 -> 111010 -> 111001 -> 111000 -> 110111 -> 110110 -> 110101 -> 110100]]",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "204"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 1, 0, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "257",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "270"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 1, 0, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "258",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "270"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 1, 0, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "259",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "270"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 1, 0, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "260",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "270"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 0, 1, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "261",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "270"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 0, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "262",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "270"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 1, 0, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "263",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "270"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 1, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "264",
    "answer": "[[1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "270"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 1, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "265",
    "answer": "[[1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "270"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 0, 1, 0, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "266",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "279"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 1, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "267",
    "answer": "[[1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "270"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 1, 0, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "268",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "279"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D, E, F, G and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "269",
    "answer": "[[A'G+B'C'F+ABDE]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "10236"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 1, 1, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "270",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "279"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 1, 1, 0, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "271",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "279"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 1, 0, 1, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "272",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "279"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 1, 0, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "273",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "279"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 0, 1, 1, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "274",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "279"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 1, 1, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "275",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "279"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 0, 1, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "276",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "279"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 1, 1, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "277",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "279"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 1, 0, 0, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "278",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "279"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 0, 1, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "279",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "279"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 1, 0, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "280",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "279"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 1, 0, 1, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "281",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "279"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 1, 1, 0, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "282",
    "answer": "[[1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "279"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "283",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "288"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "284",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "288"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "285",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "288"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 0, 1, 1, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "286",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "279"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "287",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "288"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "288",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "297"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "289",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "297"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "290",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "288"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "291",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "297"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "292",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "297"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "293",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "288"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "294",
    "answer": "[[1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "288"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "295",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "297"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "296",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "297"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "297",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "297"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "298",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "297"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "299",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "297"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "300",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "297"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "301",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "297"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "302",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "297"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "303",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "306"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "304",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "297"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "305",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "297"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "306",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "306"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "307",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "297"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "308",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "297"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "309",
    "answer": "[[1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "306"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "310",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "306"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "311",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "306"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "312",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "306"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "313",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "306"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "314",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "306"
  },
  {
    "question": "A synchronous sequential circuit is described by the state transition table below:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S1 | 1\nS0 | I01 | S1 | 1\nS0 | I10 | S2 | 1\nS0 | I11 | S0 | 1\nS1 | I00 | S2 | 0\nS1 | I01 | S3 | 1\nS1 | I10 | S0 | 0\nS1 | I11 | S1 | 0\nS2 | I00 | S2 | 1\nS2 | I01 | S0 | 1\nS2 | I10 | S0 | 1\nS2 | I11 | S3 | 1\nS3 | I00 | S0 | 0\nS3 | I01 | S1 | 0\nS3 | I10 | S3 | 0\nS3 | I11 | S0 | 0\nStarting from state S1, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I00 -> I10 -> I00, determine the output sequence. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "315",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 1]]",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "604"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "316",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "306"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "317",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "306"
  },
  {
    "question": "A synchronous sequential circuit is described by the state transition table below:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S1 | 0\nS0 | I01 | S1 | 1\nS0 | I10 | S0 | 1\nS0 | I11 | S3 | 1\nS1 | I00 | S3 | 1\nS1 | I01 | S3 | 0\nS1 | I10 | S2 | 1\nS1 | I11 | S2 | 1\nS2 | I00 | S0 | 0\nS2 | I01 | S2 | 1\nS2 | I10 | S0 | 0\nS2 | I11 | S2 | 0\nS3 | I00 | S2 | 0\nS3 | I01 | S1 | 0\nS3 | I10 | S1 | 0\nS3 | I11 | S1 | 0\nStarting from state S0, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I00 -> I01 -> I01, determine the output sequence. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "318",
    "answer": "[[1 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "604"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "319",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "306"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "320",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "306"
  },
  {
    "question": "A synchronous sequential circuit is described by the state transition table below:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S2 | 1\nS0 | I01 | S3 | 0\nS0 | I10 | S0 | 0\nS0 | I11 | S4 | 1\nS1 | I00 | S2 | 0\nS1 | I01 | S3 | 1\nS1 | I10 | S3 | 1\nS1 | I11 | S3 | 1\nS2 | I00 | S3 | 0\nS2 | I01 | S0 | 1\nS2 | I10 | S2 | 0\nS2 | I11 | S2 | 0\nS3 | I00 | S2 | 1\nS3 | I01 | S5 | 0\nS3 | I10 | S4 | 0\nS3 | I11 | S4 | 0\nS4 | I00 | S3 | 0\nS4 | I01 | S5 | 1\nS4 | I10 | S5 | 0\nS4 | I11 | S2 | 0\nS5 | I00 | S2 | 1\nS5 | I01 | S2 | 1\nS5 | I10 | S3 | 1\nS5 | I11 | S3 | 0\nStarting from state S4, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I00 -> I01 -> I00 -> I00, determine the output sequence. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "321",
    "answer": "[[1 -> 1 -> 1 -> 1 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "755"
  },
  {
    "question": "A synchronous sequential circuit is described by the state transition table below:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S0 | 0\nS0 | I01 | S1 | 1\nS0 | I10 | S2 | 1\nS0 | I11 | S3 | 0\nS1 | I00 | S3 | 0\nS1 | I01 | S0 | 0\nS1 | I10 | S1 | 1\nS1 | I11 | S0 | 1\nS2 | I00 | S2 | 1\nS2 | I01 | S0 | 0\nS2 | I10 | S2 | 0\nS2 | I11 | S2 | 0\nS3 | I00 | S0 | 1\nS3 | I01 | S3 | 0\nS3 | I10 | S1 | 1\nS3 | I11 | S1 | 0\nStarting from state S1, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I10 -> I01 -> I00, determine the output sequence. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "322",
    "answer": "[[1 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "604"
  },
  {
    "question": "A synchronous sequential circuit is described by the state transition table below:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S3 | 0\nS0 | I01 | S5 | 0\nS0 | I10 | S3 | 0\nS0 | I11 | S4 | 1\nS1 | I00 | S1 | 1\nS1 | I01 | S1 | 1\nS1 | I10 | S3 | 0\nS1 | I11 | S5 | 0\nS2 | I00 | S4 | 0\nS2 | I01 | S4 | 0\nS2 | I10 | S1 | 1\nS2 | I11 | S1 | 0\nS3 | I00 | S4 | 0\nS3 | I01 | S3 | 1\nS3 | I10 | S1 | 0\nS3 | I11 | S2 | 0\nS4 | I00 | S0 | 0\nS4 | I01 | S4 | 0\nS4 | I10 | S2 | 1\nS4 | I11 | S3 | 0\nS5 | I00 | S1 | 1\nS5 | I01 | S4 | 1\nS5 | I10 | S3 | 0\nS5 | I11 | S0 | 0\nStarting from state S3, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I11 -> I01 -> I10 -> I00, determine the output sequence. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "323",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "755"
  },
  {
    "question": "A synchronous sequential circuit is described by the state transition table below:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S4 | 1\nS0 | I01 | S7 | 0\nS0 | I10 | S6 | 0\nS0 | I11 | S6 | 0\nS1 | I00 | S6 | 0\nS1 | I01 | S4 | 0\nS1 | I10 | S2 | 1\nS1 | I11 | S2 | 0\nS2 | I00 | S4 | 0\nS2 | I01 | S6 | 1\nS2 | I10 | S5 | 1\nS2 | I11 | S5 | 0\nS3 | I00 | S1 | 1\nS3 | I01 | S6 | 0\nS3 | I10 | S7 | 0\nS3 | I11 | S5 | 1\nS4 | I00 | S7 | 0\nS4 | I01 | S7 | 1\nS4 | I10 | S5 | 1\nS4 | I11 | S5 | 1\nS5 | I00 | S5 | 0\nS5 | I01 | S6 | 1\nS5 | I10 | S3 | 1\nS5 | I11 | S0 | 0\nS6 | I00 | S6 | 0\nS6 | I01 | S5 | 0\nS6 | I10 | S2 | 1\nS6 | I11 | S0 | 1\nS7 | I00 | S2 | 0\nS7 | I01 | S6 | 0\nS7 | I10 | S4 | 0\nS7 | I11 | S5 | 0\nStarting from state S5, and given the input sequence: I10 -> I11 -> I11 -> I11 -> I00 -> I11, determine the output sequence. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "324",
    "answer": "[[1 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1]]",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "906"
  },
  {
    "question": "A synchronous sequential circuit is described by the state transition table below:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S4 | 1\nS0 | I01 | S0 | 0\nS0 | I10 | S4 | 1\nS0 | I11 | S0 | 0\nS1 | I00 | S6 | 1\nS1 | I01 | S7 | 0\nS1 | I10 | S2 | 1\nS1 | I11 | S3 | 1\nS2 | I00 | S5 | 1\nS2 | I01 | S0 | 0\nS2 | I10 | S0 | 1\nS2 | I11 | S4 | 1\nS3 | I00 | S3 | 1\nS3 | I01 | S2 | 1\nS3 | I10 | S7 | 0\nS3 | I11 | S1 | 0\nS4 | I00 | S1 | 1\nS4 | I01 | S7 | 1\nS4 | I10 | S0 | 0\nS4 | I11 | S1 | 1\nS5 | I00 | S4 | 1\nS5 | I01 | S2 | 0\nS5 | I10 | S1 | 0\nS5 | I11 | S1 | 1\nS6 | I00 | S3 | 0\nS6 | I01 | S6 | 1\nS6 | I10 | S3 | 1\nS6 | I11 | S4 | 1\nS7 | I00 | S5 | 1\nS7 | I01 | S3 | 0\nS7 | I10 | S7 | 1\nS7 | I11 | S7 | 1\nStarting from state S3, and given the input sequence: I00 -> I11 -> I00 -> I11 -> I00 -> I10, determine the output sequence. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "325",
    "answer": "[[1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 1 -> 1 -> 1]]",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "906"
  },
  {
    "question": "A synchronous sequential circuit is described by the state transition table below:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S0 | 0\nS0 | I01 | S9 | 1\nS0 | I10 | S3 | 1\nS0 | I11 | S3 | 1\nS1 | I00 | S9 | 1\nS1 | I01 | S7 | 1\nS1 | I10 | S0 | 1\nS1 | I11 | S0 | 0\nS2 | I00 | S3 | 0\nS2 | I01 | S7 | 0\nS2 | I10 | S6 | 0\nS2 | I11 | S6 | 1\nS3 | I00 | S5 | 0\nS3 | I01 | S0 | 0\nS3 | I10 | S5 | 0\nS3 | I11 | S8 | 0\nS4 | I00 | S6 | 0\nS4 | I01 | S3 | 0\nS4 | I10 | S4 | 1\nS4 | I11 | S1 | 1\nS5 | I00 | S2 | 1\nS5 | I01 | S1 | 0\nS5 | I10 | S8 | 1\nS5 | I11 | S7 | 1\nS6 | I00 | S0 | 0\nS6 | I01 | S1 | 1\nS6 | I10 | S5 | 1\nS6 | I11 | S3 | 1\nS7 | I00 | S6 | 1\nS7 | I01 | S8 | 1\nS7 | I10 | S1 | 1\nS7 | I11 | S2 | 0\nS8 | I00 | S5 | 0\nS8 | I01 | S3 | 1\nS8 | I10 | S5 | 1\nS8 | I11 | S0 | 1\nS9 | I00 | S0 | 1\nS9 | I01 | S2 | 0\nS9 | I10 | S3 | 0\nS9 | I11 | S0 | 0\nStarting from state S3, and given the input sequence: I10 -> I11 -> I11 -> I00 -> I11 -> I10 -> I01, determine the output sequence. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "326",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "1057"
  },
  {
    "question": "A synchronous sequential circuit is described by the state transition table below:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S2 | 1\nS0 | I01 | S2 | 1\nS0 | I10 | S3 | 1\nS0 | I11 | S8 | 1\nS1 | I00 | S7 | 0\nS1 | I01 | S7 | 1\nS1 | I10 | S4 | 0\nS1 | I11 | S0 | 1\nS2 | I00 | S8 | 1\nS2 | I01 | S3 | 1\nS2 | I10 | S5 | 1\nS2 | I11 | S0 | 0\nS3 | I00 | S0 | 0\nS3 | I01 | S2 | 0\nS3 | I10 | S1 | 1\nS3 | I11 | S4 | 1\nS4 | I00 | S5 | 0\nS4 | I01 | S3 | 1\nS4 | I10 | S3 | 1\nS4 | I11 | S3 | 0\nS5 | I00 | S5 | 0\nS5 | I01 | S5 | 1\nS5 | I10 | S0 | 1\nS5 | I11 | S8 | 0\nS6 | I00 | S9 | 1\nS6 | I01 | S3 | 0\nS6 | I10 | S0 | 1\nS6 | I11 | S2 | 1\nS7 | I00 | S4 | 1\nS7 | I01 | S7 | 0\nS7 | I10 | S1 | 1\nS7 | I11 | S4 | 0\nS8 | I00 | S2 | 0\nS8 | I01 | S2 | 1\nS8 | I10 | S6 | 0\nS8 | I11 | S0 | 1\nS9 | I00 | S5 | 1\nS9 | I01 | S9 | 0\nS9 | I10 | S1 | 1\nS9 | I11 | S6 | 1\nStarting from state S6, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I10 -> I00 -> I01 -> I10 -> I00 -> I11, determine the output sequence. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "327",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "1057"
  },
  {
    "question": "A synchronous sequential circuit is described by the state transition table below:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S3 | 0\nS0 | I01 | S6 | 0\nS0 | I10 | S3 | 0\nS0 | I11 | S0 | 1\nS1 | I00 | S3 | 1\nS1 | I01 | S4 | 0\nS1 | I10 | S4 | 1\nS1 | I11 | S3 | 0\nS2 | I00 | S8 | 0\nS2 | I01 | S6 | 0\nS2 | I10 | S6 | 0\nS2 | I11 | S0 | 1\nS3 | I00 | S0 | 1\nS3 | I01 | S9 | 1\nS3 | I10 | S1 | 0\nS3 | I11 | S8 | 1\nS4 | I00 | S8 | 0\nS4 | I01 | S6 | 1\nS4 | I10 | S8 | 1\nS4 | I11 | S4 | 0\nS5 | I00 | S9 | 1\nS5 | I01 | S0 | 1\nS5 | I10 | S6 | 1\nS5 | I11 | S8 | 0\nS6 | I00 | S4 | 1\nS6 | I01 | S0 | 1\nS6 | I10 | S7 | 1\nS6 | I11 | S5 | 0\nS7 | I00 | S1 | 0\nS7 | I01 | S9 | 0\nS7 | I10 | S3 | 0\nS7 | I11 | S3 | 1\nS8 | I00 | S2 | 0\nS8 | I01 | S4 | 0\nS8 | I10 | S0 | 0\nS8 | I11 | S5 | 0\nS9 | I00 | S1 | 0\nS9 | I01 | S2 | 1\nS9 | I10 | S7 | 1\nS9 | I11 | S3 | 0\nStarting from state S8, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I10 -> I10 -> I10 -> I01 -> I00 -> I11, determine the output sequence. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "328",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "1057"
  },
  {
    "question": "A synchronous sequential circuit is described by the state transition table below:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S3 | 0\nS0 | I01 | S0 | 1\nS0 | I10 | S6 | 0\nS0 | I11 | S10 | 0\nS1 | I00 | S10 | 0\nS1 | I01 | S5 | 1\nS1 | I10 | S2 | 1\nS1 | I11 | S2 | 1\nS2 | I00 | S4 | 1\nS2 | I01 | S6 | 1\nS2 | I10 | S6 | 0\nS2 | I11 | S10 | 0\nS3 | I00 | S3 | 1\nS3 | I01 | S2 | 0\nS3 | I10 | S11 | 0\nS3 | I11 | S2 | 1\nS4 | I00 | S7 | 0\nS4 | I01 | S7 | 1\nS4 | I10 | S1 | 1\nS4 | I11 | S6 | 1\nS5 | I00 | S2 | 0\nS5 | I01 | S1 | 0\nS5 | I10 | S8 | 0\nS5 | I11 | S10 | 1\nS6 | I00 | S5 | 1\nS6 | I01 | S2 | 0\nS6 | I10 | S0 | 0\nS6 | I11 | S9 | 0\nS7 | I00 | S2 | 1\nS7 | I01 | S3 | 1\nS7 | I10 | S8 | 1\nS7 | I11 | S7 | 1\nS8 | I00 | S3 | 1\nS8 | I01 | S3 | 0\nS8 | I10 | S9 | 1\nS8 | I11 | S7 | 1\nS9 | I00 | S11 | 0\nS9 | I01 | S10 | 0\nS9 | I10 | S0 | 1\nS9 | I11 | S1 | 0\nS10 | I00 | S9 | 0\nS10 | I01 | S8 | 0\nS10 | I10 | S5 | 1\nS10 | I11 | S0 | 1\nS11 | I00 | S3 | 1\nS11 | I01 | S3 | 1\nS11 | I10 | S10 | 0\nS11 | I11 | S6 | 1\nStarting from state S9, and given the input sequence: I00 -> I01 -> I10 -> I11 -> I00 -> I01 -> I00 -> I11, determine the output sequence. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "329",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1]]",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "1224"
  },
  {
    "question": "A synchronous sequential circuit is described by the state transition table below:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S11 | 1\nS0 | I01 | S11 | 0\nS0 | I10 | S2 | 0\nS0 | I11 | S6 | 1\nS1 | I00 | S1 | 1\nS1 | I01 | S6 | 1\nS1 | I10 | S10 | 0\nS1 | I11 | S1 | 1\nS2 | I00 | S7 | 0\nS2 | I01 | S7 | 0\nS2 | I10 | S7 | 0\nS2 | I11 | S1 | 0\nS3 | I00 | S5 | 1\nS3 | I01 | S2 | 0\nS3 | I10 | S3 | 0\nS3 | I11 | S10 | 0\nS4 | I00 | S10 | 1\nS4 | I01 | S9 | 0\nS4 | I10 | S11 | 1\nS4 | I11 | S1 | 1\nS5 | I00 | S1 | 0\nS5 | I01 | S3 | 0\nS5 | I10 | S2 | 0\nS5 | I11 | S10 | 1\nS6 | I00 | S3 | 0\nS6 | I01 | S1 | 0\nS6 | I10 | S3 | 1\nS6 | I11 | S11 | 0\nS7 | I00 | S11 | 1\nS7 | I01 | S5 | 1\nS7 | I10 | S6 | 1\nS7 | I11 | S0 | 1\nS8 | I00 | S6 | 0\nS8 | I01 | S11 | 1\nS8 | I10 | S3 | 0\nS8 | I11 | S5 | 0\nS9 | I00 | S7 | 1\nS9 | I01 | S5 | 1\nS9 | I10 | S1 | 1\nS9 | I11 | S5 | 1\nS10 | I00 | S10 | 1\nS10 | I01 | S9 | 0\nS10 | I10 | S2 | 0\nS10 | I11 | S5 | 0\nS11 | I00 | S8 | 1\nS11 | I01 | S2 | 1\nS11 | I10 | S5 | 1\nS11 | I11 | S11 | 1\nStarting from state S11, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I10 -> I10 -> I11 -> I00 -> I10 -> I11 -> I00, determine the output sequence. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "330",
    "answer": "[[1 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "1229"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S0 | 2\nS0 | I01 | S0 | 1\nS0 | I10 | S1 | 0\nS0 | I11 | S3 | 3\nS1 | I00 | S0 | 1\nS1 | I01 | S0 | 0\nS1 | I10 | S1 | 2\nS1 | I11 | S0 | 3\nS2 | I00 | S2 | 0\nS2 | I01 | S3 | 1\nS2 | I10 | S0 | 2\nS2 | I11 | S1 | 3\nS3 | I00 | S2 | 3\nS3 | I01 | S2 | 3\nS3 | I10 | S1 | 3\nS3 | I11 | S2 | 0\nStarting from state S3, and given the input sequence: I00 -> I10 -> I01 -> I10 -> I01, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "331",
    "answer": "[[3 -> 2 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "521"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S0 | 3\nS0 | I01 | S0 | 1\nS0 | I10 | S0 | 2\nS0 | I11 | S0 | 1\nS1 | I00 | S0 | 3\nS1 | I01 | S3 | 1\nS1 | I10 | S1 | 0\nS1 | I11 | S3 | 3\nS2 | I00 | S1 | 1\nS2 | I01 | S1 | 1\nS2 | I10 | S0 | 0\nS2 | I11 | S3 | 1\nS3 | I00 | S3 | 0\nS3 | I01 | S0 | 3\nS3 | I10 | S0 | 2\nS3 | I11 | S2 | 1\nStarting from state S1, and given the input sequence: I00 -> I00 -> I10 -> I01 -> I00, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "332",
    "answer": "[[3 -> 3 -> 2 -> 1 -> 3]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "521"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S1 | 1\nS0 | I01 | S2 | 2\nS0 | I10 | S1 | 0\nS0 | I11 | S3 | 3\nS1 | I00 | S0 | 1\nS1 | I01 | S0 | 2\nS1 | I10 | S2 | 1\nS1 | I11 | S1 | 2\nS2 | I00 | S1 | 1\nS2 | I01 | S1 | 2\nS2 | I10 | S2 | 0\nS2 | I11 | S0 | 2\nS3 | I00 | S0 | 2\nS3 | I01 | S3 | 2\nS3 | I10 | S3 | 2\nS3 | I11 | S1 | 1\nStarting from state S2, and given the input sequence: I00 -> I11 -> I11 -> I11 -> I10, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "333",
    "answer": "[[1 -> 2 -> 2 -> 2 -> 1]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "521"
  },
  {
    "question": "A synchronous sequential circuit is described by the state transition table below:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S9 | 1\nS0 | I01 | S9 | 0\nS0 | I10 | S10 | 1\nS0 | I11 | S3 | 1\nS1 | I00 | S10 | 1\nS1 | I01 | S8 | 0\nS1 | I10 | S10 | 0\nS1 | I11 | S5 | 0\nS2 | I00 | S11 | 0\nS2 | I01 | S4 | 1\nS2 | I10 | S3 | 0\nS2 | I11 | S7 | 0\nS3 | I00 | S7 | 1\nS3 | I01 | S3 | 1\nS3 | I10 | S10 | 1\nS3 | I11 | S11 | 0\nS4 | I00 | S11 | 0\nS4 | I01 | S10 | 0\nS4 | I10 | S0 | 1\nS4 | I11 | S11 | 0\nS5 | I00 | S2 | 1\nS5 | I01 | S11 | 0\nS5 | I10 | S0 | 1\nS5 | I11 | S7 | 0\nS6 | I00 | S1 | 0\nS6 | I01 | S3 | 0\nS6 | I10 | S11 | 0\nS6 | I11 | S7 | 1\nS7 | I00 | S4 | 0\nS7 | I01 | S10 | 0\nS7 | I10 | S0 | 0\nS7 | I11 | S7 | 1\nS8 | I00 | S5 | 0\nS8 | I01 | S6 | 1\nS8 | I10 | S5 | 1\nS8 | I11 | S7 | 1\nS9 | I00 | S3 | 1\nS9 | I01 | S6 | 1\nS9 | I10 | S9 | 0\nS9 | I11 | S8 | 1\nS10 | I00 | S8 | 0\nS10 | I01 | S5 | 0\nS10 | I10 | S3 | 0\nS10 | I11 | S9 | 1\nS11 | I00 | S6 | 1\nS11 | I01 | S1 | 0\nS11 | I10 | S2 | 0\nS11 | I11 | S8 | 1\nStarting from state S1, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I11 -> I01 -> I00 -> I01 -> I10 -> I10 -> I10, determine the output sequence. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "334",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "1228"
  },
  {
    "question": "A synchronous sequential circuit is described by the state transition table below:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S9 | 1\nS0 | I01 | S8 | 1\nS0 | I10 | S6 | 1\nS0 | I11 | S10 | 0\nS1 | I00 | S7 | 0\nS1 | I01 | S3 | 1\nS1 | I10 | S8 | 0\nS1 | I11 | S7 | 0\nS2 | I00 | S3 | 1\nS2 | I01 | S10 | 1\nS2 | I10 | S3 | 1\nS2 | I11 | S10 | 1\nS3 | I00 | S4 | 0\nS3 | I01 | S4 | 1\nS3 | I10 | S3 | 1\nS3 | I11 | S9 | 1\nS4 | I00 | S6 | 1\nS4 | I01 | S4 | 0\nS4 | I10 | S9 | 1\nS4 | I11 | S2 | 0\nS5 | I00 | S8 | 1\nS5 | I01 | S0 | 0\nS5 | I10 | S10 | 1\nS5 | I11 | S7 | 1\nS6 | I00 | S5 | 0\nS6 | I01 | S2 | 0\nS6 | I10 | S3 | 1\nS6 | I11 | S10 | 0\nS7 | I00 | S3 | 1\nS7 | I01 | S4 | 0\nS7 | I10 | S11 | 1\nS7 | I11 | S5 | 0\nS8 | I00 | S4 | 0\nS8 | I01 | S5 | 0\nS8 | I10 | S0 | 0\nS8 | I11 | S10 | 1\nS9 | I00 | S3 | 1\nS9 | I01 | S1 | 1\nS9 | I10 | S10 | 1\nS9 | I11 | S0 | 0\nS10 | I00 | S5 | 0\nS10 | I01 | S6 | 1\nS10 | I10 | S0 | 0\nS10 | I11 | S5 | 1\nS11 | I00 | S0 | 0\nS11 | I01 | S10 | 0\nS11 | I10 | S11 | 0\nS11 | I11 | S3 | 1\nStarting from state S5, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I00 -> I01 -> I01 -> I01 -> I10 -> I01 -> I10, determine the output sequence. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "335",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 1 -> 1 -> 1 -> 1 -> 1 -> 1 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "1226"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S1 | 3\nS0 | I01 | S3 | 0\nS0 | I10 | S1 | 0\nS0 | I11 | S3 | 3\nS1 | I00 | S1 | 1\nS1 | I01 | S3 | 3\nS1 | I10 | S3 | 3\nS1 | I11 | S2 | 3\nS2 | I00 | S0 | 3\nS2 | I01 | S1 | 3\nS2 | I10 | S0 | 2\nS2 | I11 | S1 | 1\nS3 | I00 | S0 | 2\nS3 | I01 | S1 | 2\nS3 | I10 | S1 | 3\nS3 | I11 | S0 | 3\nStarting from state S1, and given the input sequence: I00 -> I10 -> I10 -> I00 -> I00, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "336",
    "answer": "[[1 -> 3 -> 3 -> 1 -> 1]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "521"
  },
  {
    "question": "A synchronous sequential circuit is described by the state transition table below:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S6 | 0\nS0 | I01 | S2 | 1\nS0 | I10 | S5 | 1\nS0 | I11 | S5 | 0\nS1 | I00 | S11 | 1\nS1 | I01 | S9 | 1\nS1 | I10 | S8 | 1\nS1 | I11 | S6 | 1\nS2 | I00 | S3 | 0\nS2 | I01 | S11 | 0\nS2 | I10 | S6 | 0\nS2 | I11 | S3 | 0\nS3 | I00 | S5 | 0\nS3 | I01 | S6 | 1\nS3 | I10 | S10 | 1\nS3 | I11 | S3 | 1\nS4 | I00 | S0 | 0\nS4 | I01 | S11 | 1\nS4 | I10 | S11 | 0\nS4 | I11 | S10 | 0\nS5 | I00 | S7 | 0\nS5 | I01 | S6 | 0\nS5 | I10 | S5 | 1\nS5 | I11 | S6 | 1\nS6 | I00 | S0 | 1\nS6 | I01 | S11 | 1\nS6 | I10 | S4 | 1\nS6 | I11 | S5 | 1\nS7 | I00 | S2 | 0\nS7 | I01 | S5 | 1\nS7 | I10 | S6 | 0\nS7 | I11 | S2 | 0\nS8 | I00 | S5 | 0\nS8 | I01 | S7 | 0\nS8 | I10 | S6 | 0\nS8 | I11 | S1 | 1\nS9 | I00 | S5 | 1\nS9 | I01 | S4 | 1\nS9 | I10 | S8 | 0\nS9 | I11 | S1 | 1\nS10 | I00 | S11 | 0\nS10 | I01 | S6 | 1\nS10 | I10 | S4 | 0\nS10 | I11 | S7 | 0\nS11 | I00 | S8 | 0\nS11 | I01 | S0 | 0\nS11 | I10 | S8 | 1\nS11 | I11 | S3 | 0\nStarting from state S3, and given the input sequence: I00 -> I11 -> I11 -> I11 -> I11 -> I11 -> I00 -> I01, determine the output sequence. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "337",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 1 -> 1 -> 1 -> 1 -> 1 -> 1 -> 1]]",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "1224"
  },
  {
    "question": "A synchronous sequential circuit is described by the state transition table below:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S3 | 1\nS0 | I01 | S0 | 0\nS0 | I10 | S7 | 0\nS0 | I11 | S7 | 1\nS1 | I00 | S8 | 1\nS1 | I01 | S4 | 0\nS1 | I10 | S10 | 1\nS1 | I11 | S5 | 0\nS2 | I00 | S6 | 1\nS2 | I01 | S4 | 0\nS2 | I10 | S11 | 0\nS2 | I11 | S10 | 1\nS3 | I00 | S1 | 1\nS3 | I01 | S6 | 1\nS3 | I10 | S5 | 0\nS3 | I11 | S6 | 0\nS4 | I00 | S6 | 0\nS4 | I01 | S7 | 1\nS4 | I10 | S7 | 1\nS4 | I11 | S10 | 0\nS5 | I00 | S6 | 0\nS5 | I01 | S4 | 0\nS5 | I10 | S7 | 0\nS5 | I11 | S4 | 1\nS6 | I00 | S5 | 0\nS6 | I01 | S2 | 1\nS6 | I10 | S11 | 0\nS6 | I11 | S3 | 1\nS7 | I00 | S3 | 0\nS7 | I01 | S8 | 1\nS7 | I10 | S7 | 0\nS7 | I11 | S5 | 1\nS8 | I00 | S2 | 1\nS8 | I01 | S9 | 1\nS8 | I10 | S6 | 0\nS8 | I11 | S6 | 0\nS9 | I00 | S6 | 1\nS9 | I01 | S4 | 1\nS9 | I10 | S1 | 1\nS9 | I11 | S3 | 0\nS10 | I00 | S4 | 0\nS10 | I01 | S1 | 0\nS10 | I10 | S5 | 1\nS10 | I11 | S11 | 1\nS11 | I00 | S7 | 1\nS11 | I01 | S8 | 0\nS11 | I10 | S1 | 0\nS11 | I11 | S3 | 1\nStarting from state S8, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I01 -> I11 -> I10 -> I10 -> I00 -> I10 -> I11, determine the output sequence. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "338",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 1 -> 1 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 1]]",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "1222"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S2 | 3\nS0 | I01 | S1 | 3\nS0 | I10 | S1 | 0\nS0 | I11 | S0 | 0\nS1 | I00 | S2 | 1\nS1 | I01 | S1 | 1\nS1 | I10 | S2 | 1\nS1 | I11 | S0 | 3\nS2 | I00 | S2 | 0\nS2 | I01 | S1 | 1\nS2 | I10 | S0 | 1\nS2 | I11 | S2 | 3\nS3 | I00 | S0 | 1\nS3 | I01 | S1 | 0\nS3 | I10 | S1 | 3\nS3 | I11 | S1 | 2\nStarting from state S3, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I01 -> I01 -> I01 -> I00, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "339",
    "answer": "[[2 -> 1 -> 1 -> 1 -> 1]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "521"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S0 | 3\nS0 | I01 | S1 | 0\nS0 | I10 | S3 | 1\nS0 | I11 | S2 | 0\nS1 | I00 | S1 | 2\nS1 | I01 | S3 | 0\nS1 | I10 | S3 | 2\nS1 | I11 | S1 | 1\nS2 | I00 | S1 | 1\nS2 | I01 | S0 | 0\nS2 | I10 | S2 | 0\nS2 | I11 | S3 | 1\nS3 | I00 | S3 | 0\nS3 | I01 | S2 | 3\nS3 | I10 | S0 | 3\nS3 | I11 | S3 | 1\nStarting from state S2, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I00 -> I01 -> I01 -> I11, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "340",
    "answer": "[[1 -> 0 -> 3 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "521"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S3 | 0\nS0 | I01 | S0 | 2\nS0 | I10 | S3 | 1\nS0 | I11 | S2 | 0\nS1 | I00 | S2 | 3\nS1 | I01 | S2 | 2\nS1 | I10 | S1 | 2\nS1 | I11 | S1 | 2\nS2 | I00 | S0 | 3\nS2 | I01 | S2 | 1\nS2 | I10 | S2 | 3\nS2 | I11 | S2 | 0\nS3 | I00 | S2 | 2\nS3 | I01 | S2 | 2\nS3 | I10 | S0 | 0\nS3 | I11 | S3 | 3\nStarting from state S0, and given the input sequence: I00 -> I00 -> I10 -> I01 -> I01, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "341",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 2 -> 3 -> 1 -> 1]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "521"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S0 | 0\nS0 | I01 | S2 | 3\nS0 | I10 | S2 | 1\nS0 | I11 | S1 | 2\nS1 | I00 | S3 | 0\nS1 | I01 | S2 | 1\nS1 | I10 | S3 | 3\nS1 | I11 | S1 | 1\nS2 | I00 | S3 | 0\nS2 | I01 | S1 | 3\nS2 | I10 | S2 | 0\nS2 | I11 | S0 | 3\nS3 | I00 | S0 | 2\nS3 | I01 | S3 | 2\nS3 | I10 | S0 | 2\nS3 | I11 | S0 | 0\nStarting from state S3, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I00 -> I11 -> I00 -> I01, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "342",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 2 -> 0 -> 2]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "521"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S0 | 0\nS0 | I01 | S1 | 3\nS0 | I10 | S1 | 3\nS0 | I11 | S2 | 0\nS1 | I00 | S0 | 1\nS1 | I01 | S1 | 0\nS1 | I10 | S3 | 1\nS1 | I11 | S3 | 2\nS2 | I00 | S3 | 0\nS2 | I01 | S0 | 2\nS2 | I10 | S0 | 1\nS2 | I11 | S1 | 1\nS3 | I00 | S0 | 0\nS3 | I01 | S1 | 2\nS3 | I10 | S3 | 1\nS3 | I11 | S2 | 3\nStarting from state S2, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I00 -> I00 -> I00 -> I01, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "343",
    "answer": "[[2 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 3]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "521"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S2 | 1\nS0 | I01 | S3 | 2\nS0 | I10 | S3 | 3\nS0 | I11 | S1 | 3\nS1 | I00 | S0 | 0\nS1 | I01 | S3 | 3\nS1 | I10 | S3 | 3\nS1 | I11 | S0 | 1\nS2 | I00 | S2 | 2\nS2 | I01 | S3 | 0\nS2 | I10 | S1 | 3\nS2 | I11 | S3 | 2\nS3 | I00 | S3 | 0\nS3 | I01 | S1 | 2\nS3 | I10 | S3 | 3\nS3 | I11 | S1 | 1\nStarting from state S1, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I00 -> I01 -> I10 -> I01, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "344",
    "answer": "[[3 -> 0 -> 2 -> 3 -> 2]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "521"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S3 | 3\nS0 | I01 | S2 | 7\nS0 | I10 | S3 | 5\nS0 | I11 | S0 | 5\nS1 | I00 | S0 | 2\nS1 | I01 | S3 | 4\nS1 | I10 | S3 | 7\nS1 | I11 | S2 | 3\nS2 | I00 | S2 | 1\nS2 | I01 | S4 | 7\nS2 | I10 | S3 | 1\nS2 | I11 | S3 | 0\nS3 | I00 | S5 | 2\nS3 | I01 | S1 | 4\nS3 | I10 | S1 | 4\nS3 | I11 | S0 | 2\nS4 | I00 | S1 | 1\nS4 | I01 | S4 | 2\nS4 | I10 | S3 | 2\nS4 | I11 | S0 | 1\nS5 | I00 | S2 | 2\nS5 | I01 | S3 | 4\nS5 | I10 | S3 | 4\nS5 | I11 | S5 | 3\nStarting from state S5, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I11 -> I01 -> I01 -> I00 -> I11, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "345",
    "answer": "[[4 -> 2 -> 7 -> 7 -> 1 -> 3]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "672"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S4 | 4\nS0 | I01 | S0 | 2\nS0 | I10 | S0 | 2\nS0 | I11 | S3 | 2\nS1 | I00 | S0 | 2\nS1 | I01 | S3 | 6\nS1 | I10 | S2 | 3\nS1 | I11 | S1 | 3\nS2 | I00 | S5 | 7\nS2 | I01 | S2 | 6\nS2 | I10 | S0 | 7\nS2 | I11 | S4 | 7\nS3 | I00 | S3 | 6\nS3 | I01 | S3 | 1\nS3 | I10 | S0 | 0\nS3 | I11 | S3 | 7\nS4 | I00 | S1 | 7\nS4 | I01 | S3 | 3\nS4 | I10 | S0 | 1\nS4 | I11 | S3 | 6\nS5 | I00 | S2 | 4\nS5 | I01 | S1 | 3\nS5 | I10 | S1 | 4\nS5 | I11 | S4 | 0\nStarting from state S4, and given the input sequence: I00 -> I01 -> I11 -> I11 -> I00 -> I00, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "346",
    "answer": "[[7 -> 6 -> 7 -> 7 -> 6 -> 6]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "672"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S0 | 3\nS0 | I01 | S0 | 0\nS0 | I10 | S2 | 0\nS0 | I11 | S0 | 1\nS1 | I00 | S0 | 7\nS1 | I01 | S2 | 4\nS1 | I10 | S2 | 5\nS1 | I11 | S4 | 7\nS2 | I00 | S1 | 5\nS2 | I01 | S3 | 6\nS2 | I10 | S5 | 5\nS2 | I11 | S5 | 7\nS3 | I00 | S1 | 1\nS3 | I01 | S0 | 2\nS3 | I10 | S5 | 7\nS3 | I11 | S0 | 3\nS4 | I00 | S0 | 3\nS4 | I01 | S4 | 2\nS4 | I10 | S4 | 2\nS4 | I11 | S3 | 0\nS5 | I00 | S5 | 3\nS5 | I01 | S4 | 7\nS5 | I10 | S5 | 6\nS5 | I11 | S0 | 6\nStarting from state S3, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I01 -> I01 -> I00 -> I11 -> I00, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "347",
    "answer": "[[2 -> 0 -> 0 -> 3 -> 1 -> 3]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "672"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S2 | 0\nS0 | I01 | S2 | 6\nS0 | I10 | S4 | 3\nS0 | I11 | S4 | 0\nS1 | I00 | S3 | 0\nS1 | I01 | S1 | 4\nS1 | I10 | S4 | 1\nS1 | I11 | S5 | 6\nS2 | I00 | S0 | 5\nS2 | I01 | S1 | 7\nS2 | I10 | S4 | 6\nS2 | I11 | S3 | 5\nS3 | I00 | S3 | 3\nS3 | I01 | S4 | 1\nS3 | I10 | S0 | 1\nS3 | I11 | S2 | 1\nS4 | I00 | S2 | 3\nS4 | I01 | S5 | 3\nS4 | I10 | S5 | 3\nS4 | I11 | S1 | 7\nS5 | I00 | S2 | 4\nS5 | I01 | S1 | 5\nS5 | I10 | S5 | 4\nS5 | I11 | S2 | 4\nStarting from state S3, and given the input sequence: I00 -> I00 -> I11 -> I11 -> I01 -> I10, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "348",
    "answer": "[[3 -> 3 -> 1 -> 5 -> 1 -> 3]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "672"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S0 | 3\nS0 | I01 | S0 | 2\nS0 | I10 | S2 | 6\nS0 | I11 | S3 | 6\nS1 | I00 | S2 | 7\nS1 | I01 | S2 | 0\nS1 | I10 | S5 | 7\nS1 | I11 | S1 | 4\nS2 | I00 | S1 | 3\nS2 | I01 | S2 | 1\nS2 | I10 | S1 | 3\nS2 | I11 | S2 | 0\nS3 | I00 | S4 | 2\nS3 | I01 | S5 | 0\nS3 | I10 | S0 | 7\nS3 | I11 | S0 | 1\nS4 | I00 | S2 | 6\nS4 | I01 | S1 | 4\nS4 | I10 | S3 | 0\nS4 | I11 | S0 | 5\nS5 | I00 | S1 | 5\nS5 | I01 | S4 | 4\nS5 | I10 | S5 | 5\nS5 | I11 | S1 | 3\nStarting from state S5, and given the input sequence: I10 -> I01 -> I00 -> I11 -> I00 -> I01, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "349",
    "answer": "[[5 -> 4 -> 6 -> 0 -> 3 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "672"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S1 | 0\nS0 | I01 | S0 | 1\nS0 | I10 | S3 | 6\nS0 | I11 | S2 | 4\nS1 | I00 | S1 | 6\nS1 | I01 | S2 | 1\nS1 | I10 | S3 | 7\nS1 | I11 | S2 | 2\nS2 | I00 | S1 | 6\nS2 | I01 | S4 | 1\nS2 | I10 | S5 | 3\nS2 | I11 | S1 | 4\nS3 | I00 | S2 | 5\nS3 | I01 | S1 | 4\nS3 | I10 | S5 | 4\nS3 | I11 | S2 | 1\nS4 | I00 | S5 | 5\nS4 | I01 | S2 | 2\nS4 | I10 | S0 | 7\nS4 | I11 | S0 | 5\nS5 | I00 | S0 | 4\nS5 | I01 | S5 | 5\nS5 | I10 | S3 | 5\nS5 | I11 | S2 | 3\nStarting from state S4, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I10 -> I01 -> I10 -> I10 -> I00, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "350",
    "answer": "[[5 -> 6 -> 4 -> 7 -> 4 -> 4]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "672"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S3 | 1\nS0 | I01 | S0 | 7\nS0 | I10 | S2 | 6\nS0 | I11 | S2 | 0\nS1 | I00 | S4 | 2\nS1 | I01 | S4 | 4\nS1 | I10 | S0 | 5\nS1 | I11 | S1 | 5\nS2 | I00 | S1 | 6\nS2 | I01 | S3 | 3\nS2 | I10 | S0 | 1\nS2 | I11 | S3 | 1\nS3 | I00 | S2 | 1\nS3 | I01 | S4 | 1\nS3 | I10 | S5 | 7\nS3 | I11 | S5 | 6\nS4 | I00 | S1 | 6\nS4 | I01 | S2 | 2\nS4 | I10 | S3 | 5\nS4 | I11 | S2 | 2\nS5 | I00 | S2 | 1\nS5 | I01 | S0 | 6\nS5 | I10 | S1 | 3\nS5 | I11 | S4 | 6\nStarting from state S4, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I00 -> I01 -> I10 -> I01 -> I00, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "351",
    "answer": "[[2 -> 6 -> 4 -> 5 -> 1 -> 6]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "672"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S5 | 5\nS0 | I01 | S1 | 6\nS0 | I10 | S0 | 7\nS0 | I11 | S3 | 5\nS1 | I00 | S0 | 7\nS1 | I01 | S1 | 4\nS1 | I10 | S4 | 3\nS1 | I11 | S1 | 3\nS2 | I00 | S4 | 4\nS2 | I01 | S1 | 7\nS2 | I10 | S4 | 2\nS2 | I11 | S0 | 4\nS3 | I00 | S4 | 3\nS3 | I01 | S5 | 7\nS3 | I10 | S1 | 5\nS3 | I11 | S1 | 6\nS4 | I00 | S2 | 0\nS4 | I01 | S1 | 2\nS4 | I10 | S5 | 1\nS4 | I11 | S0 | 4\nS5 | I00 | S3 | 1\nS5 | I01 | S3 | 1\nS5 | I10 | S3 | 2\nS5 | I11 | S1 | 2\nStarting from state S0, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I10 -> I11 -> I10 -> I01 -> I01, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "352",
    "answer": "[[5 -> 5 -> 3 -> 3 -> 2 -> 4]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "672"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S1 | 6\nS0 | I01 | S0 | 7\nS0 | I10 | S4 | 1\nS0 | I11 | S0 | 5\nS1 | I00 | S1 | 1\nS1 | I01 | S4 | 2\nS1 | I10 | S3 | 2\nS1 | I11 | S4 | 3\nS2 | I00 | S1 | 6\nS2 | I01 | S3 | 1\nS2 | I10 | S4 | 2\nS2 | I11 | S3 | 2\nS3 | I00 | S4 | 2\nS3 | I01 | S1 | 6\nS3 | I10 | S1 | 1\nS3 | I11 | S1 | 1\nS4 | I00 | S1 | 2\nS4 | I01 | S0 | 3\nS4 | I10 | S1 | 4\nS4 | I11 | S4 | 7\nS5 | I00 | S1 | 0\nS5 | I01 | S3 | 4\nS5 | I10 | S0 | 6\nS5 | I11 | S1 | 1\nStarting from state S1, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I00 -> I00 -> I11 -> I00 -> I00, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "353",
    "answer": "[[2 -> 2 -> 1 -> 3 -> 2 -> 1]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "672"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S1 | 5\nS0 | I01 | S4 | 6\nS0 | I10 | S5 | 0\nS0 | I11 | S5 | 7\nS1 | I00 | S3 | 2\nS1 | I01 | S3 | 1\nS1 | I10 | S1 | 2\nS1 | I11 | S3 | 5\nS2 | I00 | S0 | 4\nS2 | I01 | S3 | 2\nS2 | I10 | S2 | 4\nS2 | I11 | S4 | 0\nS3 | I00 | S3 | 7\nS3 | I01 | S1 | 7\nS3 | I10 | S3 | 2\nS3 | I11 | S1 | 0\nS4 | I00 | S3 | 4\nS4 | I01 | S3 | 7\nS4 | I10 | S2 | 5\nS4 | I11 | S2 | 7\nS5 | I00 | S3 | 0\nS5 | I01 | S1 | 5\nS5 | I10 | S5 | 6\nS5 | I11 | S0 | 6\nStarting from state S0, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I10 -> I01 -> I10 -> I10 -> I10, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "354",
    "answer": "[[7 -> 6 -> 5 -> 2 -> 2 -> 2]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "672"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S2 | 2\nS0 | I01 | S5 | 4\nS0 | I10 | S1 | 6\nS0 | I11 | S3 | 3\nS1 | I00 | S2 | 7\nS1 | I01 | S0 | 3\nS1 | I10 | S1 | 4\nS1 | I11 | S0 | 0\nS2 | I00 | S0 | 2\nS2 | I01 | S1 | 7\nS2 | I10 | S1 | 6\nS2 | I11 | S2 | 5\nS3 | I00 | S4 | 4\nS3 | I01 | S0 | 3\nS3 | I10 | S3 | 1\nS3 | I11 | S4 | 5\nS4 | I00 | S1 | 7\nS4 | I01 | S5 | 2\nS4 | I10 | S5 | 4\nS4 | I11 | S1 | 6\nS5 | I00 | S0 | 3\nS5 | I01 | S1 | 0\nS5 | I10 | S3 | 2\nS5 | I11 | S0 | 6\nStarting from state S4, and given the input sequence: I00 -> I10 -> I00 -> I00 -> I01 -> I11, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "355",
    "answer": "[[7 -> 4 -> 7 -> 2 -> 4 -> 6]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "672"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S0 | 3\nS0 | I01 | S2 | 6\nS0 | I10 | S5 | 3\nS0 | I11 | S5 | 0\nS1 | I00 | S2 | 5\nS1 | I01 | S5 | 1\nS1 | I10 | S3 | 6\nS1 | I11 | S2 | 6\nS2 | I00 | S0 | 6\nS2 | I01 | S1 | 0\nS2 | I10 | S4 | 2\nS2 | I11 | S3 | 5\nS3 | I00 | S2 | 5\nS3 | I01 | S3 | 4\nS3 | I10 | S3 | 1\nS3 | I11 | S3 | 1\nS4 | I00 | S5 | 3\nS4 | I01 | S5 | 6\nS4 | I10 | S3 | 7\nS4 | I11 | S1 | 1\nS5 | I00 | S4 | 6\nS5 | I01 | S0 | 7\nS5 | I10 | S2 | 3\nS5 | I11 | S2 | 1\nStarting from state S1, and given the input sequence: I10 -> I10 -> I01 -> I11 -> I11 -> I00, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "356",
    "answer": "[[6 -> 1 -> 4 -> 1 -> 1 -> 5]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "672"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S4 | 7\nS0 | I01 | S1 | 6\nS0 | I10 | S5 | 7\nS0 | I11 | S2 | 0\nS1 | I00 | S3 | 6\nS1 | I01 | S1 | 0\nS1 | I10 | S2 | 3\nS1 | I11 | S4 | 6\nS2 | I00 | S5 | 4\nS2 | I01 | S5 | 4\nS2 | I10 | S1 | 3\nS2 | I11 | S3 | 2\nS3 | I00 | S1 | 1\nS3 | I01 | S0 | 6\nS3 | I10 | S0 | 2\nS3 | I11 | S4 | 0\nS4 | I00 | S2 | 6\nS4 | I01 | S5 | 7\nS4 | I10 | S1 | 3\nS4 | I11 | S1 | 1\nS5 | I00 | S4 | 5\nS5 | I01 | S1 | 5\nS5 | I10 | S2 | 6\nS5 | I11 | S3 | 0\nStarting from state S1, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I00 -> I10 -> I01 -> I01 -> I10, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "357",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 6 -> 2 -> 6 -> 0 -> 3]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "672"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S3 | 4\nS0 | I01 | S5 | 7\nS0 | I10 | S2 | 0\nS0 | I11 | S0 | 1\nS1 | I00 | S3 | 2\nS1 | I01 | S3 | 4\nS1 | I10 | S5 | 6\nS1 | I11 | S5 | 5\nS2 | I00 | S2 | 5\nS2 | I01 | S4 | 4\nS2 | I10 | S3 | 5\nS2 | I11 | S3 | 4\nS3 | I00 | S2 | 5\nS3 | I01 | S2 | 3\nS3 | I10 | S1 | 0\nS3 | I11 | S5 | 0\nS4 | I00 | S5 | 6\nS4 | I01 | S1 | 6\nS4 | I10 | S0 | 0\nS4 | I11 | S2 | 2\nS5 | I00 | S0 | 7\nS5 | I01 | S4 | 1\nS5 | I10 | S1 | 7\nS5 | I11 | S5 | 1\nStarting from state S2, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I00 -> I01 -> I00 -> I11 -> I10, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "358",
    "answer": "[[4 -> 5 -> 4 -> 6 -> 1 -> 7]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "672"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S2 | 0\nS0 | I01 | S0 | 4\nS0 | I10 | S5 | 2\nS0 | I11 | S5 | 2\nS1 | I00 | S4 | 4\nS1 | I01 | S3 | 6\nS1 | I10 | S4 | 2\nS1 | I11 | S0 | 4\nS2 | I00 | S1 | 5\nS2 | I01 | S4 | 1\nS2 | I10 | S1 | 1\nS2 | I11 | S2 | 0\nS3 | I00 | S0 | 2\nS3 | I01 | S5 | 2\nS3 | I10 | S3 | 7\nS3 | I11 | S3 | 1\nS4 | I00 | S1 | 3\nS4 | I01 | S5 | 1\nS4 | I10 | S0 | 2\nS4 | I11 | S5 | 1\nS5 | I00 | S3 | 4\nS5 | I01 | S4 | 2\nS5 | I10 | S1 | 7\nS5 | I11 | S2 | 2\nStarting from state S3, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I10 -> I10 -> I00 -> I00 -> I11, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "359",
    "answer": "[[2 -> 7 -> 2 -> 3 -> 4 -> 1]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "672"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S3 | 6\nS0 | I01 | S3 | 0\nS0 | I10 | S4 | 6\nS0 | I11 | S5 | 4\nS1 | I00 | S1 | 5\nS1 | I01 | S0 | 6\nS1 | I10 | S1 | 5\nS1 | I11 | S3 | 7\nS2 | I00 | S2 | 2\nS2 | I01 | S3 | 4\nS2 | I10 | S1 | 0\nS2 | I11 | S4 | 2\nS3 | I00 | S3 | 1\nS3 | I01 | S5 | 1\nS3 | I10 | S3 | 4\nS3 | I11 | S3 | 2\nS4 | I00 | S5 | 3\nS4 | I01 | S1 | 3\nS4 | I10 | S4 | 1\nS4 | I11 | S2 | 2\nS5 | I00 | S5 | 6\nS5 | I01 | S4 | 6\nS5 | I10 | S2 | 5\nS5 | I11 | S0 | 2\nStarting from state S0, and given the input sequence: I10 -> I10 -> I01 -> I01 -> I01 -> I01, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "360",
    "answer": "[[6 -> 1 -> 3 -> 6 -> 0 -> 1]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "672"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S4 | 6\nS0 | I01 | S0 | 5\nS0 | I10 | S4 | 4\nS0 | I11 | S2 | 1\nS1 | I00 | S3 | 7\nS1 | I01 | S2 | 4\nS1 | I10 | S3 | 0\nS1 | I11 | S5 | 0\nS2 | I00 | S1 | 7\nS2 | I01 | S3 | 1\nS2 | I10 | S4 | 4\nS2 | I11 | S3 | 7\nS3 | I00 | S1 | 7\nS3 | I01 | S2 | 3\nS3 | I10 | S5 | 4\nS3 | I11 | S0 | 1\nS4 | I00 | S4 | 2\nS4 | I01 | S4 | 3\nS4 | I10 | S3 | 7\nS4 | I11 | S1 | 3\nS5 | I00 | S1 | 3\nS5 | I01 | S5 | 4\nS5 | I10 | S4 | 4\nS5 | I11 | S2 | 3\nStarting from state S3, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I10 -> I00 -> I00 -> I00 -> I00, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "361",
    "answer": "[[1 -> 4 -> 2 -> 2 -> 2 -> 2]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "672"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S5 | 9\nS0 | I01 | S7 | 3\nS0 | I10 | S5 | 12\nS0 | I11 | S7 | 15\nS1 | I00 | S4 | 11\nS1 | I01 | S2 | 8\nS1 | I10 | S7 | 12\nS1 | I11 | S5 | 8\nS2 | I00 | S3 | 15\nS2 | I01 | S4 | 7\nS2 | I10 | S6 | 1\nS2 | I11 | S1 | 14\nS3 | I00 | S4 | 2\nS3 | I01 | S0 | 8\nS3 | I10 | S7 | 10\nS3 | I11 | S5 | 1\nS4 | I00 | S3 | 13\nS4 | I01 | S0 | 14\nS4 | I10 | S6 | 0\nS4 | I11 | S6 | 14\nS5 | I00 | S7 | 13\nS5 | I01 | S4 | 13\nS5 | I10 | S6 | 11\nS5 | I11 | S4 | 8\nS6 | I00 | S3 | 3\nS6 | I01 | S4 | 12\nS6 | I10 | S2 | 6\nS6 | I11 | S7 | 15\nS7 | I00 | S4 | 4\nS7 | I01 | S2 | 5\nS7 | I10 | S2 | 6\nS7 | I11 | S1 | 1\nStarting from state S0, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I01 -> I00 -> I01 -> I10 -> I11 -> I01, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "362",
    "answer": "[[3 -> 5 -> 15 -> 8 -> 12 -> 8 -> 14]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "838"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S0 | 3\nS0 | I01 | S6 | 10\nS0 | I10 | S1 | 15\nS0 | I11 | S3 | 5\nS1 | I00 | S6 | 9\nS1 | I01 | S5 | 6\nS1 | I10 | S6 | 15\nS1 | I11 | S3 | 15\nS2 | I00 | S1 | 12\nS2 | I01 | S3 | 10\nS2 | I10 | S0 | 10\nS2 | I11 | S5 | 4\nS3 | I00 | S0 | 10\nS3 | I01 | S5 | 0\nS3 | I10 | S3 | 1\nS3 | I11 | S1 | 1\nS4 | I00 | S7 | 11\nS4 | I01 | S3 | 12\nS4 | I10 | S3 | 2\nS4 | I11 | S3 | 14\nS5 | I00 | S3 | 7\nS5 | I01 | S1 | 2\nS5 | I10 | S2 | 9\nS5 | I11 | S5 | 4\nS6 | I00 | S3 | 9\nS6 | I01 | S1 | 11\nS6 | I10 | S5 | 10\nS6 | I11 | S6 | 14\nS7 | I00 | S5 | 15\nS7 | I01 | S6 | 9\nS7 | I10 | S0 | 4\nS7 | I11 | S3 | 11\nStarting from state S5, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I01 -> I00 -> I10 -> I00 -> I10 -> I11, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "363",
    "answer": "[[2 -> 6 -> 7 -> 1 -> 10 -> 15 -> 15]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "839"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S2 | 3\nS0 | I01 | S6 | 13\nS0 | I10 | S2 | 5\nS0 | I11 | S6 | 8\nS1 | I00 | S7 | 8\nS1 | I01 | S2 | 13\nS1 | I10 | S4 | 0\nS1 | I11 | S2 | 14\nS2 | I00 | S1 | 15\nS2 | I01 | S3 | 10\nS2 | I10 | S4 | 5\nS2 | I11 | S7 | 8\nS3 | I00 | S3 | 11\nS3 | I01 | S2 | 5\nS3 | I10 | S3 | 13\nS3 | I11 | S4 | 15\nS4 | I00 | S2 | 1\nS4 | I01 | S1 | 10\nS4 | I10 | S6 | 11\nS4 | I11 | S0 | 11\nS5 | I00 | S0 | 0\nS5 | I01 | S6 | 11\nS5 | I10 | S3 | 12\nS5 | I11 | S3 | 4\nS6 | I00 | S3 | 1\nS6 | I01 | S7 | 12\nS6 | I10 | S0 | 14\nS6 | I11 | S5 | 14\nS7 | I00 | S5 | 9\nS7 | I01 | S3 | 4\nS7 | I10 | S1 | 15\nS7 | I11 | S0 | 5\nStarting from state S5, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I11 -> I00 -> I11 -> I10 -> I11 -> I00, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "364",
    "answer": "[[11 -> 14 -> 0 -> 8 -> 14 -> 8 -> 1]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "840"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S5 | 5\nS0 | I01 | S1 | 5\nS0 | I10 | S2 | 2\nS0 | I11 | S2 | 2\nS1 | I00 | S2 | 13\nS1 | I01 | S5 | 11\nS1 | I10 | S3 | 11\nS1 | I11 | S2 | 2\nS2 | I00 | S0 | 3\nS2 | I01 | S1 | 4\nS2 | I10 | S6 | 7\nS2 | I11 | S3 | 7\nS3 | I00 | S4 | 2\nS3 | I01 | S2 | 3\nS3 | I10 | S4 | 8\nS3 | I11 | S0 | 12\nS4 | I00 | S4 | 11\nS4 | I01 | S2 | 7\nS4 | I10 | S3 | 12\nS4 | I11 | S5 | 9\nS5 | I00 | S0 | 7\nS5 | I01 | S0 | 14\nS5 | I10 | S2 | 2\nS5 | I11 | S1 | 8\nS6 | I00 | S3 | 15\nS6 | I01 | S1 | 4\nS6 | I10 | S1 | 13\nS6 | I11 | S0 | 7\nS7 | I00 | S5 | 10\nS7 | I01 | S1 | 10\nS7 | I10 | S0 | 12\nS7 | I11 | S5 | 10\nStarting from state S1, and given the input sequence: I00 -> I00 -> I11 -> I01 -> I00 -> I01 -> I10, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "365",
    "answer": "[[13 -> 3 -> 2 -> 4 -> 13 -> 4 -> 11]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "836"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S5 | 6\nS0 | I01 | S2 | 9\nS0 | I10 | S7 | 14\nS0 | I11 | S0 | 12\nS1 | I00 | S4 | 4\nS1 | I01 | S1 | 7\nS1 | I10 | S0 | 9\nS1 | I11 | S4 | 15\nS2 | I00 | S4 | 0\nS2 | I01 | S2 | 2\nS2 | I10 | S3 | 4\nS2 | I11 | S7 | 2\nS3 | I00 | S5 | 6\nS3 | I01 | S6 | 12\nS3 | I10 | S1 | 13\nS3 | I11 | S4 | 8\nS4 | I00 | S4 | 12\nS4 | I01 | S5 | 0\nS4 | I10 | S2 | 10\nS4 | I11 | S3 | 11\nS5 | I00 | S4 | 11\nS5 | I01 | S1 | 8\nS5 | I10 | S6 | 11\nS5 | I11 | S3 | 4\nS6 | I00 | S2 | 0\nS6 | I01 | S2 | 4\nS6 | I10 | S3 | 13\nS6 | I11 | S7 | 7\nS7 | I00 | S1 | 5\nS7 | I01 | S5 | 13\nS7 | I10 | S0 | 7\nS7 | I11 | S0 | 9\nStarting from state S4, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I10 -> I01 -> I01 -> I00 -> I01 -> I01, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "366",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 11 -> 4 -> 2 -> 0 -> 0 -> 8]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "835"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S1 | 7\nS0 | I01 | S5 | 0\nS0 | I10 | S5 | 12\nS0 | I11 | S1 | 6\nS1 | I00 | S0 | 13\nS1 | I01 | S3 | 8\nS1 | I10 | S4 | 13\nS1 | I11 | S1 | 5\nS2 | I00 | S2 | 15\nS2 | I01 | S5 | 8\nS2 | I10 | S7 | 0\nS2 | I11 | S1 | 14\nS3 | I00 | S2 | 11\nS3 | I01 | S5 | 1\nS3 | I10 | S6 | 2\nS3 | I11 | S2 | 15\nS4 | I00 | S0 | 15\nS4 | I01 | S3 | 11\nS4 | I10 | S6 | 11\nS4 | I11 | S3 | 6\nS5 | I00 | S0 | 11\nS5 | I01 | S6 | 8\nS5 | I10 | S1 | 8\nS5 | I11 | S2 | 11\nS6 | I00 | S0 | 11\nS6 | I01 | S4 | 7\nS6 | I10 | S4 | 9\nS6 | I11 | S1 | 5\nS7 | I00 | S2 | 0\nS7 | I01 | S4 | 7\nS7 | I10 | S0 | 12\nS7 | I11 | S4 | 0\nStarting from state S5, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I01 -> I00 -> I00 -> I01 -> I11 -> I00, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "367",
    "answer": "[[8 -> 7 -> 15 -> 7 -> 8 -> 15 -> 15]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "837"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S5 | 7\nS0 | I01 | S2 | 2\nS0 | I10 | S5 | 10\nS0 | I11 | S3 | 12\nS1 | I00 | S2 | 13\nS1 | I01 | S1 | 4\nS1 | I10 | S4 | 0\nS1 | I11 | S4 | 8\nS2 | I00 | S2 | 1\nS2 | I01 | S5 | 10\nS2 | I10 | S1 | 11\nS2 | I11 | S6 | 9\nS3 | I00 | S1 | 11\nS3 | I01 | S3 | 1\nS3 | I10 | S3 | 13\nS3 | I11 | S7 | 13\nS4 | I00 | S3 | 1\nS4 | I01 | S1 | 8\nS4 | I10 | S4 | 10\nS4 | I11 | S1 | 15\nS5 | I00 | S3 | 14\nS5 | I01 | S1 | 1\nS5 | I10 | S3 | 5\nS5 | I11 | S3 | 3\nS6 | I00 | S6 | 9\nS6 | I01 | S7 | 9\nS6 | I10 | S2 | 14\nS6 | I11 | S0 | 1\nS7 | I00 | S6 | 1\nS7 | I01 | S3 | 10\nS7 | I10 | S0 | 7\nS7 | I11 | S3 | 7\nStarting from state S5, and given the input sequence: I10 -> I10 -> I01 -> I00 -> I10 -> I10 -> I11, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "368",
    "answer": "[[5 -> 13 -> 1 -> 11 -> 0 -> 10 -> 15]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "836"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S7 | 0\nS0 | I01 | S2 | 11\nS0 | I10 | S1 | 7\nS0 | I11 | S5 | 4\nS1 | I00 | S4 | 15\nS1 | I01 | S0 | 15\nS1 | I10 | S5 | 8\nS1 | I11 | S2 | 11\nS2 | I00 | S5 | 7\nS2 | I01 | S6 | 3\nS2 | I10 | S6 | 7\nS2 | I11 | S4 | 3\nS3 | I00 | S0 | 0\nS3 | I01 | S6 | 10\nS3 | I10 | S1 | 15\nS3 | I11 | S2 | 0\nS4 | I00 | S6 | 11\nS4 | I01 | S6 | 14\nS4 | I10 | S1 | 0\nS4 | I11 | S0 | 4\nS5 | I00 | S4 | 3\nS5 | I01 | S6 | 9\nS5 | I10 | S4 | 11\nS5 | I11 | S4 | 13\nS6 | I00 | S4 | 14\nS6 | I01 | S4 | 15\nS6 | I10 | S7 | 15\nS6 | I11 | S6 | 1\nS7 | I00 | S4 | 11\nS7 | I01 | S3 | 1\nS7 | I10 | S7 | 0\nS7 | I11 | S1 | 1\nStarting from state S4, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I01 -> I01 -> I01 -> I00 -> I11 -> I00, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "369",
    "answer": "[[14 -> 15 -> 14 -> 15 -> 11 -> 1 -> 14]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "837"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S7 | 3\nS0 | I01 | S6 | 12\nS0 | I10 | S4 | 3\nS0 | I11 | S6 | 12\nS1 | I00 | S3 | 9\nS1 | I01 | S6 | 9\nS1 | I10 | S3 | 10\nS1 | I11 | S0 | 9\nS2 | I00 | S1 | 1\nS2 | I01 | S4 | 10\nS2 | I10 | S5 | 6\nS2 | I11 | S0 | 11\nS3 | I00 | S0 | 14\nS3 | I01 | S4 | 13\nS3 | I10 | S0 | 15\nS3 | I11 | S7 | 10\nS4 | I00 | S3 | 2\nS4 | I01 | S5 | 3\nS4 | I10 | S2 | 13\nS4 | I11 | S0 | 5\nS5 | I00 | S2 | 8\nS5 | I01 | S7 | 3\nS5 | I10 | S2 | 6\nS5 | I11 | S3 | 10\nS6 | I00 | S7 | 7\nS6 | I01 | S5 | 4\nS6 | I10 | S6 | 15\nS6 | I11 | S3 | 15\nS7 | I00 | S7 | 3\nS7 | I01 | S3 | 8\nS7 | I10 | S4 | 14\nS7 | I11 | S4 | 15\nStarting from state S4, and given the input sequence: I00 -> I11 -> I00 -> I00 -> I00 -> I00 -> I01, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "370",
    "answer": "[[2 -> 10 -> 3 -> 3 -> 3 -> 3 -> 8]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "838"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S0 | 4\nS0 | I01 | S7 | 2\nS0 | I10 | S2 | 11\nS0 | I11 | S1 | 15\nS1 | I00 | S7 | 14\nS1 | I01 | S1 | 12\nS1 | I10 | S4 | 15\nS1 | I11 | S7 | 12\nS2 | I00 | S2 | 3\nS2 | I01 | S3 | 4\nS2 | I10 | S5 | 8\nS2 | I11 | S0 | 11\nS3 | I00 | S4 | 13\nS3 | I01 | S1 | 12\nS3 | I10 | S7 | 0\nS3 | I11 | S3 | 14\nS4 | I00 | S2 | 5\nS4 | I01 | S1 | 9\nS4 | I10 | S6 | 7\nS4 | I11 | S0 | 9\nS5 | I00 | S4 | 12\nS5 | I01 | S6 | 5\nS5 | I10 | S5 | 15\nS5 | I11 | S0 | 7\nS6 | I00 | S4 | 7\nS6 | I01 | S6 | 4\nS6 | I10 | S6 | 10\nS6 | I11 | S1 | 8\nS7 | I00 | S4 | 12\nS7 | I01 | S2 | 9\nS7 | I10 | S6 | 11\nS7 | I11 | S4 | 1\nStarting from state S4, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I11 -> I01 -> I00 -> I11 -> I00 -> I00, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "371",
    "answer": "[[9 -> 12 -> 9 -> 3 -> 11 -> 4 -> 4]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "838"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S5 | 1\nS0 | I01 | S7 | 10\nS0 | I10 | S3 | 8\nS0 | I11 | S2 | 15\nS1 | I00 | S7 | 0\nS1 | I01 | S5 | 3\nS1 | I10 | S1 | 2\nS1 | I11 | S7 | 0\nS2 | I00 | S7 | 4\nS2 | I01 | S0 | 6\nS2 | I10 | S6 | 10\nS2 | I11 | S2 | 10\nS3 | I00 | S4 | 8\nS3 | I01 | S7 | 5\nS3 | I10 | S5 | 15\nS3 | I11 | S2 | 13\nS4 | I00 | S4 | 1\nS4 | I01 | S6 | 7\nS4 | I10 | S4 | 10\nS4 | I11 | S0 | 3\nS5 | I00 | S1 | 0\nS5 | I01 | S6 | 8\nS5 | I10 | S2 | 5\nS5 | I11 | S6 | 14\nS6 | I00 | S7 | 13\nS6 | I01 | S1 | 7\nS6 | I10 | S0 | 3\nS6 | I11 | S0 | 2\nS7 | I00 | S2 | 10\nS7 | I01 | S1 | 4\nS7 | I10 | S1 | 1\nS7 | I11 | S1 | 13\nStarting from state S4, and given the input sequence: I00 -> I00 -> I00 -> I00 -> I00 -> I00 -> I11, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "372",
    "answer": "[[1 -> 1 -> 1 -> 1 -> 1 -> 1 -> 3]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "834"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S1 | 10\nS0 | I01 | S6 | 15\nS0 | I10 | S3 | 6\nS0 | I11 | S0 | 3\nS1 | I00 | S6 | 13\nS1 | I01 | S7 | 5\nS1 | I10 | S2 | 0\nS1 | I11 | S0 | 13\nS2 | I00 | S5 | 7\nS2 | I01 | S3 | 2\nS2 | I10 | S2 | 2\nS2 | I11 | S2 | 13\nS3 | I00 | S2 | 15\nS3 | I01 | S5 | 5\nS3 | I10 | S7 | 7\nS3 | I11 | S5 | 3\nS4 | I00 | S2 | 10\nS4 | I01 | S5 | 9\nS4 | I10 | S4 | 12\nS4 | I11 | S4 | 5\nS5 | I00 | S4 | 0\nS5 | I01 | S0 | 15\nS5 | I10 | S1 | 8\nS5 | I11 | S7 | 14\nS6 | I00 | S7 | 8\nS6 | I01 | S2 | 10\nS6 | I10 | S0 | 9\nS6 | I11 | S3 | 3\nS7 | I00 | S2 | 2\nS7 | I01 | S7 | 11\nS7 | I10 | S5 | 10\nS7 | I11 | S1 | 13\nStarting from state S1, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I00 -> I10 -> I00 -> I10 -> I10 -> I10, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "373",
    "answer": "[[13 -> 10 -> 0 -> 7 -> 8 -> 0 -> 2]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "837"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S6 | 12\nS0 | I01 | S6 | 7\nS0 | I10 | S3 | 4\nS0 | I11 | S4 | 8\nS1 | I00 | S5 | 14\nS1 | I01 | S1 | 3\nS1 | I10 | S4 | 14\nS1 | I11 | S5 | 6\nS2 | I00 | S2 | 9\nS2 | I01 | S3 | 12\nS2 | I10 | S1 | 11\nS2 | I11 | S6 | 6\nS3 | I00 | S3 | 15\nS3 | I01 | S1 | 6\nS3 | I10 | S6 | 12\nS3 | I11 | S3 | 13\nS4 | I00 | S3 | 10\nS4 | I01 | S5 | 4\nS4 | I10 | S7 | 5\nS4 | I11 | S1 | 5\nS5 | I00 | S6 | 13\nS5 | I01 | S1 | 2\nS5 | I10 | S2 | 2\nS5 | I11 | S6 | 12\nS6 | I00 | S0 | 4\nS6 | I01 | S7 | 14\nS6 | I10 | S2 | 8\nS6 | I11 | S4 | 10\nS7 | I00 | S1 | 11\nS7 | I01 | S1 | 9\nS7 | I10 | S3 | 9\nS7 | I11 | S4 | 12\nStarting from state S6, and given the input sequence: I00 -> I00 -> I01 -> I11 -> I00 -> I01 -> I10, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "374",
    "answer": "[[4 -> 12 -> 14 -> 12 -> 10 -> 6 -> 14]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "838"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S9 | 17\nS0 | I01 | S5 | 4\nS0 | I10 | S0 | 10\nS0 | I11 | S9 | 1\nS1 | I00 | S4 | 5\nS1 | I01 | S0 | 19\nS1 | I10 | S4 | 13\nS1 | I11 | S4 | 12\nS2 | I00 | S9 | 8\nS2 | I01 | S3 | 28\nS2 | I10 | S6 | 11\nS2 | I11 | S6 | 11\nS3 | I00 | S2 | 29\nS3 | I01 | S7 | 26\nS3 | I10 | S4 | 4\nS3 | I11 | S5 | 21\nS4 | I00 | S4 | 22\nS4 | I01 | S4 | 27\nS4 | I10 | S4 | 3\nS4 | I11 | S0 | 17\nS5 | I00 | S9 | 23\nS5 | I01 | S6 | 3\nS5 | I10 | S0 | 12\nS5 | I11 | S4 | 18\nS6 | I00 | S6 | 13\nS6 | I01 | S3 | 5\nS6 | I10 | S4 | 15\nS6 | I11 | S8 | 11\nS7 | I00 | S4 | 4\nS7 | I01 | S9 | 4\nS7 | I10 | S1 | 8\nS7 | I11 | S6 | 8\nS8 | I00 | S8 | 11\nS8 | I01 | S7 | 25\nS8 | I10 | S2 | 17\nS8 | I11 | S1 | 3\nS9 | I00 | S7 | 0\nS9 | I01 | S0 | 10\nS9 | I10 | S5 | 31\nS9 | I11 | S0 | 26\nStarting from state S5, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I01 -> I11 -> I01 -> I11 -> I00 -> I00 -> I00, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "375",
    "answer": "[[18 -> 27 -> 17 -> 4 -> 18 -> 22 -> 22 -> 22]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1000"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S1 | 5\nS0 | I01 | S8 | 2\nS0 | I10 | S0 | 17\nS0 | I11 | S4 | 20\nS1 | I00 | S4 | 28\nS1 | I01 | S3 | 6\nS1 | I10 | S4 | 16\nS1 | I11 | S1 | 11\nS2 | I00 | S1 | 4\nS2 | I01 | S7 | 19\nS2 | I10 | S6 | 19\nS2 | I11 | S8 | 20\nS3 | I00 | S2 | 11\nS3 | I01 | S3 | 8\nS3 | I10 | S6 | 17\nS3 | I11 | S5 | 18\nS4 | I00 | S9 | 31\nS4 | I01 | S3 | 3\nS4 | I10 | S0 | 5\nS4 | I11 | S7 | 28\nS5 | I00 | S8 | 19\nS5 | I01 | S6 | 22\nS5 | I10 | S1 | 4\nS5 | I11 | S3 | 30\nS6 | I00 | S5 | 10\nS6 | I01 | S9 | 9\nS6 | I10 | S6 | 25\nS6 | I11 | S3 | 8\nS7 | I00 | S9 | 3\nS7 | I01 | S0 | 24\nS7 | I10 | S2 | 26\nS7 | I11 | S7 | 21\nS8 | I00 | S4 | 13\nS8 | I01 | S0 | 13\nS8 | I10 | S8 | 19\nS8 | I11 | S8 | 17\nS9 | I00 | S0 | 15\nS9 | I01 | S0 | 16\nS9 | I10 | S4 | 15\nS9 | I11 | S3 | 14\nStarting from state S5, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I00 -> I00 -> I01 -> I01 -> I01 -> I01 -> I00, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "376",
    "answer": "[[22 -> 10 -> 19 -> 13 -> 2 -> 13 -> 2 -> 13]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1003"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S8 | 27\nS0 | I01 | S5 | 28\nS0 | I10 | S8 | 22\nS0 | I11 | S3 | 24\nS1 | I00 | S7 | 2\nS1 | I01 | S3 | 13\nS1 | I10 | S2 | 31\nS1 | I11 | S8 | 17\nS2 | I00 | S4 | 21\nS2 | I01 | S5 | 9\nS2 | I10 | S6 | 0\nS2 | I11 | S7 | 15\nS3 | I00 | S2 | 7\nS3 | I01 | S6 | 19\nS3 | I10 | S2 | 2\nS3 | I11 | S1 | 16\nS4 | I00 | S4 | 6\nS4 | I01 | S2 | 17\nS4 | I10 | S3 | 19\nS4 | I11 | S4 | 11\nS5 | I00 | S2 | 16\nS5 | I01 | S1 | 27\nS5 | I10 | S6 | 1\nS5 | I11 | S9 | 18\nS6 | I00 | S2 | 18\nS6 | I01 | S0 | 15\nS6 | I10 | S9 | 18\nS6 | I11 | S0 | 27\nS7 | I00 | S9 | 24\nS7 | I01 | S4 | 11\nS7 | I10 | S8 | 20\nS7 | I11 | S3 | 4\nS8 | I00 | S2 | 16\nS8 | I01 | S5 | 23\nS8 | I10 | S5 | 20\nS8 | I11 | S2 | 16\nS9 | I00 | S5 | 30\nS9 | I01 | S6 | 18\nS9 | I10 | S3 | 10\nS9 | I11 | S6 | 4\nStarting from state S0, and given the input sequence: I10 -> I10 -> I00 -> I00 -> I01 -> I11 -> I01 -> I10, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "377",
    "answer": "[[22 -> 20 -> 16 -> 21 -> 17 -> 15 -> 11 -> 19]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1005"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S9 | 26\nS0 | I01 | S5 | 2\nS0 | I10 | S9 | 5\nS0 | I11 | S2 | 19\nS1 | I00 | S3 | 24\nS1 | I01 | S9 | 3\nS1 | I10 | S5 | 24\nS1 | I11 | S0 | 3\nS2 | I00 | S1 | 5\nS2 | I01 | S8 | 10\nS2 | I10 | S1 | 9\nS2 | I11 | S0 | 4\nS3 | I00 | S3 | 12\nS3 | I01 | S8 | 24\nS3 | I10 | S0 | 13\nS3 | I11 | S1 | 9\nS4 | I00 | S0 | 16\nS4 | I01 | S4 | 28\nS4 | I10 | S0 | 10\nS4 | I11 | S7 | 6\nS5 | I00 | S9 | 25\nS5 | I01 | S9 | 13\nS5 | I10 | S0 | 29\nS5 | I11 | S5 | 6\nS6 | I00 | S6 | 20\nS6 | I01 | S0 | 31\nS6 | I10 | S7 | 21\nS6 | I11 | S8 | 25\nS7 | I00 | S3 | 29\nS7 | I01 | S0 | 12\nS7 | I10 | S5 | 15\nS7 | I11 | S8 | 31\nS8 | I00 | S9 | 9\nS8 | I01 | S8 | 18\nS8 | I10 | S2 | 3\nS8 | I11 | S9 | 31\nS9 | I00 | S7 | 0\nS9 | I01 | S3 | 4\nS9 | I10 | S1 | 28\nS9 | I11 | S4 | 11\nStarting from state S1, and given the input sequence: I00 -> I11 -> I01 -> I00 -> I00 -> I01 -> I01 -> I01, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "378",
    "answer": "[[24 -> 9 -> 3 -> 0 -> 29 -> 24 -> 18 -> 18]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1000"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S6 | 12\nS0 | I01 | S0 | 31\nS0 | I10 | S4 | 8\nS0 | I11 | S9 | 0\nS1 | I00 | S4 | 19\nS1 | I01 | S1 | 1\nS1 | I10 | S7 | 21\nS1 | I11 | S7 | 29\nS2 | I00 | S8 | 2\nS2 | I01 | S1 | 12\nS2 | I10 | S9 | 28\nS2 | I11 | S1 | 23\nS3 | I00 | S8 | 20\nS3 | I01 | S3 | 26\nS3 | I10 | S2 | 19\nS3 | I11 | S8 | 20\nS4 | I00 | S5 | 23\nS4 | I01 | S2 | 16\nS4 | I10 | S3 | 24\nS4 | I11 | S5 | 11\nS5 | I00 | S2 | 31\nS5 | I01 | S4 | 28\nS5 | I10 | S9 | 2\nS5 | I11 | S1 | 16\nS6 | I00 | S1 | 7\nS6 | I01 | S0 | 5\nS6 | I10 | S8 | 18\nS6 | I11 | S9 | 4\nS7 | I00 | S8 | 23\nS7 | I01 | S1 | 24\nS7 | I10 | S9 | 0\nS7 | I11 | S6 | 10\nS8 | I00 | S5 | 27\nS8 | I01 | S0 | 16\nS8 | I10 | S5 | 15\nS8 | I11 | S5 | 4\nS9 | I00 | S5 | 11\nS9 | I01 | S5 | 31\nS9 | I10 | S0 | 26\nS9 | I11 | S4 | 8\nStarting from state S0, and given the input sequence: I00 -> I10 -> I11 -> I10 -> I10 -> I01 -> I10 -> I10, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "379",
    "answer": "[[12 -> 18 -> 4 -> 2 -> 26 -> 31 -> 8 -> 24]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1003"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S9 | 12\nS0 | I01 | S0 | 6\nS0 | I10 | S8 | 1\nS0 | I11 | S9 | 18\nS1 | I00 | S6 | 10\nS1 | I01 | S4 | 15\nS1 | I10 | S7 | 27\nS1 | I11 | S9 | 8\nS2 | I00 | S6 | 11\nS2 | I01 | S5 | 7\nS2 | I10 | S8 | 4\nS2 | I11 | S5 | 27\nS3 | I00 | S1 | 23\nS3 | I01 | S2 | 16\nS3 | I10 | S6 | 14\nS3 | I11 | S2 | 26\nS4 | I00 | S5 | 20\nS4 | I01 | S3 | 8\nS4 | I10 | S1 | 17\nS4 | I11 | S1 | 12\nS5 | I00 | S3 | 23\nS5 | I01 | S7 | 13\nS5 | I10 | S8 | 17\nS5 | I11 | S1 | 1\nS6 | I00 | S9 | 11\nS6 | I01 | S3 | 30\nS6 | I10 | S5 | 6\nS6 | I11 | S8 | 28\nS7 | I00 | S0 | 9\nS7 | I01 | S8 | 22\nS7 | I10 | S4 | 16\nS7 | I11 | S4 | 21\nS8 | I00 | S9 | 24\nS8 | I01 | S8 | 6\nS8 | I10 | S6 | 0\nS8 | I11 | S7 | 13\nS9 | I00 | S6 | 25\nS9 | I01 | S7 | 1\nS9 | I10 | S1 | 17\nS9 | I11 | S9 | 19\nStarting from state S7, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I01 -> I00 -> I01 -> I00 -> I11 -> I00 -> I00, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "380",
    "answer": "[[21 -> 8 -> 23 -> 15 -> 20 -> 1 -> 10 -> 11]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1002"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S5 | 9\nS0 | I01 | S5 | 4\nS0 | I10 | S6 | 25\nS0 | I11 | S5 | 11\nS1 | I00 | S5 | 29\nS1 | I01 | S0 | 30\nS1 | I10 | S4 | 29\nS1 | I11 | S0 | 0\nS2 | I00 | S5 | 6\nS2 | I01 | S7 | 11\nS2 | I10 | S2 | 31\nS2 | I11 | S8 | 2\nS3 | I00 | S5 | 0\nS3 | I01 | S8 | 27\nS3 | I10 | S5 | 19\nS3 | I11 | S8 | 26\nS4 | I00 | S5 | 28\nS4 | I01 | S3 | 9\nS4 | I10 | S6 | 4\nS4 | I11 | S6 | 5\nS5 | I00 | S3 | 8\nS5 | I01 | S1 | 26\nS5 | I10 | S7 | 17\nS5 | I11 | S2 | 10\nS6 | I00 | S3 | 12\nS6 | I01 | S3 | 25\nS6 | I10 | S7 | 1\nS6 | I11 | S6 | 23\nS7 | I00 | S7 | 17\nS7 | I01 | S0 | 26\nS7 | I10 | S9 | 5\nS7 | I11 | S3 | 16\nS8 | I00 | S0 | 16\nS8 | I01 | S4 | 21\nS8 | I10 | S3 | 27\nS8 | I11 | S4 | 12\nS9 | I00 | S7 | 17\nS9 | I01 | S4 | 1\nS9 | I10 | S4 | 7\nS9 | I11 | S7 | 14\nStarting from state S3, and given the input sequence: I00 -> I10 -> I01 -> I00 -> I11 -> I01 -> I11 -> I11, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "381",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 17 -> 26 -> 9 -> 10 -> 11 -> 16 -> 26]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1000"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S9 | 19\nS0 | I01 | S6 | 27\nS0 | I10 | S8 | 23\nS0 | I11 | S8 | 6\nS1 | I00 | S2 | 23\nS1 | I01 | S2 | 2\nS1 | I10 | S3 | 10\nS1 | I11 | S3 | 3\nS2 | I00 | S1 | 10\nS2 | I01 | S8 | 24\nS2 | I10 | S3 | 3\nS2 | I11 | S6 | 22\nS3 | I00 | S9 | 17\nS3 | I01 | S6 | 0\nS3 | I10 | S2 | 12\nS3 | I11 | S4 | 19\nS4 | I00 | S9 | 0\nS4 | I01 | S9 | 30\nS4 | I10 | S6 | 2\nS4 | I11 | S2 | 2\nS5 | I00 | S2 | 0\nS5 | I01 | S6 | 15\nS5 | I10 | S8 | 2\nS5 | I11 | S7 | 16\nS6 | I00 | S1 | 26\nS6 | I01 | S3 | 2\nS6 | I10 | S6 | 14\nS6 | I11 | S2 | 9\nS7 | I00 | S2 | 4\nS7 | I01 | S0 | 24\nS7 | I10 | S8 | 18\nS7 | I11 | S1 | 19\nS8 | I00 | S1 | 9\nS8 | I01 | S0 | 7\nS8 | I10 | S4 | 10\nS8 | I11 | S5 | 11\nS9 | I00 | S4 | 8\nS9 | I01 | S7 | 21\nS9 | I10 | S8 | 23\nS9 | I11 | S4 | 12\nStarting from state S9, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I11 -> I10 -> I00 -> I00 -> I00 -> I11 -> I10, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "382",
    "answer": "[[12 -> 2 -> 3 -> 17 -> 8 -> 0 -> 12 -> 2]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "998"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S2 | 14\nS0 | I01 | S3 | 5\nS0 | I10 | S2 | 28\nS0 | I11 | S3 | 4\nS1 | I00 | S6 | 0\nS1 | I01 | S0 | 0\nS1 | I10 | S6 | 0\nS1 | I11 | S5 | 22\nS2 | I00 | S3 | 26\nS2 | I01 | S5 | 11\nS2 | I10 | S9 | 25\nS2 | I11 | S3 | 19\nS3 | I00 | S2 | 19\nS3 | I01 | S1 | 11\nS3 | I10 | S6 | 9\nS3 | I11 | S8 | 7\nS4 | I00 | S4 | 8\nS4 | I01 | S8 | 6\nS4 | I10 | S4 | 20\nS4 | I11 | S7 | 27\nS5 | I00 | S8 | 31\nS5 | I01 | S3 | 31\nS5 | I10 | S2 | 19\nS5 | I11 | S5 | 29\nS6 | I00 | S4 | 11\nS6 | I01 | S4 | 19\nS6 | I10 | S1 | 8\nS6 | I11 | S1 | 19\nS7 | I00 | S6 | 13\nS7 | I01 | S7 | 22\nS7 | I10 | S7 | 13\nS7 | I11 | S2 | 6\nS8 | I00 | S8 | 29\nS8 | I01 | S8 | 19\nS8 | I10 | S3 | 25\nS8 | I11 | S4 | 1\nS9 | I00 | S3 | 13\nS9 | I01 | S7 | 15\nS9 | I10 | S3 | 24\nS9 | I11 | S7 | 24\nStarting from state S4, and given the input sequence: I00 -> I10 -> I00 -> I01 -> I01 -> I11 -> I01 -> I11, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "383",
    "answer": "[[8 -> 20 -> 8 -> 6 -> 19 -> 1 -> 6 -> 1]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1002"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S8 | 18\nS0 | I01 | S3 | 25\nS0 | I10 | S6 | 15\nS0 | I11 | S6 | 11\nS1 | I00 | S4 | 12\nS1 | I01 | S3 | 7\nS1 | I10 | S5 | 13\nS1 | I11 | S2 | 23\nS2 | I00 | S3 | 23\nS2 | I01 | S0 | 8\nS2 | I10 | S2 | 21\nS2 | I11 | S5 | 12\nS3 | I00 | S2 | 1\nS3 | I01 | S4 | 9\nS3 | I10 | S2 | 30\nS3 | I11 | S7 | 10\nS4 | I00 | S4 | 0\nS4 | I01 | S6 | 30\nS4 | I10 | S0 | 4\nS4 | I11 | S0 | 17\nS5 | I00 | S6 | 14\nS5 | I01 | S2 | 18\nS5 | I10 | S9 | 2\nS5 | I11 | S4 | 24\nS6 | I00 | S7 | 2\nS6 | I01 | S0 | 1\nS6 | I10 | S2 | 19\nS6 | I11 | S9 | 31\nS7 | I00 | S1 | 1\nS7 | I01 | S9 | 25\nS7 | I10 | S7 | 24\nS7 | I11 | S6 | 28\nS8 | I00 | S0 | 24\nS8 | I01 | S3 | 1\nS8 | I10 | S5 | 20\nS8 | I11 | S6 | 31\nS9 | I00 | S2 | 9\nS9 | I01 | S4 | 17\nS9 | I10 | S7 | 10\nS9 | I11 | S4 | 3\nStarting from state S8, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I00 -> I00 -> I01 -> I11 -> I11 -> I11 -> I11, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "384",
    "answer": "[[31 -> 2 -> 1 -> 7 -> 10 -> 28 -> 31 -> 3]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1001"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S8 | 25\nS0 | I01 | S2 | 21\nS0 | I10 | S3 | 19\nS0 | I11 | S9 | 20\nS1 | I00 | S7 | 6\nS1 | I01 | S1 | 26\nS1 | I10 | S6 | 7\nS1 | I11 | S4 | 9\nS2 | I00 | S0 | 16\nS2 | I01 | S1 | 0\nS2 | I10 | S3 | 25\nS2 | I11 | S3 | 30\nS3 | I00 | S3 | 5\nS3 | I01 | S9 | 0\nS3 | I10 | S9 | 28\nS3 | I11 | S2 | 5\nS4 | I00 | S7 | 28\nS4 | I01 | S2 | 17\nS4 | I10 | S8 | 0\nS4 | I11 | S9 | 31\nS5 | I00 | S5 | 29\nS5 | I01 | S1 | 10\nS5 | I10 | S7 | 31\nS5 | I11 | S5 | 12\nS6 | I00 | S9 | 6\nS6 | I01 | S8 | 22\nS6 | I10 | S9 | 5\nS6 | I11 | S8 | 29\nS7 | I00 | S1 | 6\nS7 | I01 | S1 | 23\nS7 | I10 | S4 | 28\nS7 | I11 | S9 | 2\nS8 | I00 | S5 | 29\nS8 | I01 | S2 | 29\nS8 | I10 | S4 | 31\nS8 | I11 | S3 | 7\nS9 | I00 | S7 | 11\nS9 | I01 | S1 | 11\nS9 | I10 | S1 | 24\nS9 | I11 | S0 | 16\nStarting from state S4, and given the input sequence: I00 -> I11 -> I10 -> I01 -> I11 -> I11 -> I10 -> I00, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "385",
    "answer": "[[28 -> 2 -> 24 -> 26 -> 9 -> 31 -> 24 -> 6]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1001"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S9 | 22\nS0 | I01 | S7 | 20\nS0 | I10 | S6 | 9\nS0 | I11 | S1 | 18\nS1 | I00 | S1 | 22\nS1 | I01 | S1 | 19\nS1 | I10 | S4 | 13\nS1 | I11 | S1 | 22\nS2 | I00 | S5 | 29\nS2 | I01 | S6 | 1\nS2 | I10 | S9 | 11\nS2 | I11 | S7 | 21\nS3 | I00 | S5 | 12\nS3 | I01 | S9 | 8\nS3 | I10 | S8 | 5\nS3 | I11 | S9 | 14\nS4 | I00 | S2 | 4\nS4 | I01 | S0 | 15\nS4 | I10 | S2 | 12\nS4 | I11 | S1 | 21\nS5 | I00 | S6 | 10\nS5 | I01 | S8 | 8\nS5 | I10 | S3 | 18\nS5 | I11 | S8 | 0\nS6 | I00 | S4 | 4\nS6 | I01 | S7 | 1\nS6 | I10 | S5 | 26\nS6 | I11 | S2 | 7\nS7 | I00 | S8 | 4\nS7 | I01 | S6 | 15\nS7 | I10 | S5 | 0\nS7 | I11 | S4 | 15\nS8 | I00 | S2 | 9\nS8 | I01 | S9 | 9\nS8 | I10 | S7 | 9\nS8 | I11 | S7 | 17\nS9 | I00 | S2 | 10\nS9 | I01 | S3 | 10\nS9 | I10 | S6 | 4\nS9 | I11 | S6 | 3\nStarting from state S9, and given the input sequence: I00 -> I01 -> I00 -> I10 -> I11 -> I10 -> I10 -> I01, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "386",
    "answer": "[[10 -> 1 -> 4 -> 12 -> 21 -> 0 -> 18 -> 8]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "997"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S1 | 3\nS0 | I01 | S5 | 17\nS0 | I10 | S2 | 30\nS0 | I11 | S1 | 4\nS1 | I00 | S5 | 8\nS1 | I01 | S7 | 31\nS1 | I10 | S5 | 21\nS1 | I11 | S4 | 3\nS2 | I00 | S3 | 2\nS2 | I01 | S0 | 21\nS2 | I10 | S6 | 3\nS2 | I11 | S4 | 4\nS3 | I00 | S9 | 16\nS3 | I01 | S1 | 26\nS3 | I10 | S2 | 7\nS3 | I11 | S5 | 29\nS4 | I00 | S5 | 13\nS4 | I01 | S7 | 3\nS4 | I10 | S1 | 6\nS4 | I11 | S7 | 27\nS5 | I00 | S0 | 18\nS5 | I01 | S7 | 10\nS5 | I10 | S7 | 6\nS5 | I11 | S0 | 5\nS6 | I00 | S7 | 10\nS6 | I01 | S4 | 16\nS6 | I10 | S5 | 0\nS6 | I11 | S5 | 2\nS7 | I00 | S7 | 11\nS7 | I01 | S1 | 2\nS7 | I10 | S6 | 29\nS7 | I11 | S8 | 9\nS8 | I00 | S5 | 22\nS8 | I01 | S7 | 24\nS8 | I10 | S5 | 0\nS8 | I11 | S7 | 23\nS9 | I00 | S1 | 29\nS9 | I01 | S6 | 24\nS9 | I10 | S7 | 4\nS9 | I11 | S7 | 28\nStarting from state S6, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I11 -> I11 -> I01 -> I00 -> I10 -> I00 -> I10, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "387",
    "answer": "[[16 -> 27 -> 9 -> 24 -> 11 -> 29 -> 10 -> 29]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "996"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S8 | 6\nS0 | I01 | S9 | 9\nS0 | I10 | S3 | 25\nS0 | I11 | S2 | 13\nS1 | I00 | S4 | 18\nS1 | I01 | S6 | 6\nS1 | I10 | S0 | 13\nS1 | I11 | S6 | 13\nS2 | I00 | S2 | 22\nS2 | I01 | S5 | 24\nS2 | I10 | S5 | 3\nS2 | I11 | S2 | 29\nS3 | I00 | S3 | 14\nS3 | I01 | S0 | 31\nS3 | I10 | S1 | 20\nS3 | I11 | S6 | 28\nS4 | I00 | S4 | 4\nS4 | I01 | S3 | 16\nS4 | I10 | S0 | 4\nS4 | I11 | S0 | 16\nS5 | I00 | S8 | 11\nS5 | I01 | S6 | 19\nS5 | I10 | S8 | 28\nS5 | I11 | S4 | 8\nS6 | I00 | S5 | 23\nS6 | I01 | S1 | 6\nS6 | I10 | S0 | 19\nS6 | I11 | S1 | 5\nS7 | I00 | S4 | 20\nS7 | I01 | S1 | 25\nS7 | I10 | S7 | 27\nS7 | I11 | S4 | 25\nS8 | I00 | S7 | 6\nS8 | I01 | S1 | 11\nS8 | I10 | S1 | 21\nS8 | I11 | S1 | 14\nS9 | I00 | S9 | 9\nS9 | I01 | S8 | 16\nS9 | I10 | S5 | 3\nS9 | I11 | S6 | 1\nStarting from state S7, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I10 -> I00 -> I10 -> I11 -> I00 -> I00 -> I11, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "388",
    "answer": "[[25 -> 4 -> 6 -> 21 -> 13 -> 23 -> 11 -> 14]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1001"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S8 | 38\nS0 | I01 | S4 | 18\nS0 | I10 | S0 | 35\nS0 | I11 | S2 | 45\nS1 | I00 | S4 | 6\nS1 | I01 | S4 | 54\nS1 | I10 | S6 | 4\nS1 | I11 | S8 | 14\nS2 | I00 | S0 | 39\nS2 | I01 | S3 | 42\nS2 | I10 | S8 | 62\nS2 | I11 | S4 | 56\nS3 | I00 | S10 | 32\nS3 | I01 | S9 | 9\nS3 | I10 | S8 | 62\nS3 | I11 | S0 | 4\nS4 | I00 | S6 | 19\nS4 | I01 | S0 | 55\nS4 | I10 | S10 | 25\nS4 | I11 | S5 | 5\nS5 | I00 | S4 | 14\nS5 | I01 | S4 | 31\nS5 | I10 | S6 | 3\nS5 | I11 | S10 | 26\nS6 | I00 | S11 | 20\nS6 | I01 | S9 | 33\nS6 | I10 | S3 | 34\nS6 | I11 | S0 | 24\nS7 | I00 | S6 | 0\nS7 | I01 | S7 | 31\nS7 | I10 | S11 | 18\nS7 | I11 | S3 | 54\nS8 | I00 | S9 | 17\nS8 | I01 | S4 | 40\nS8 | I10 | S11 | 42\nS8 | I11 | S4 | 63\nS9 | I00 | S2 | 39\nS9 | I01 | S9 | 29\nS9 | I10 | S0 | 5\nS9 | I11 | S5 | 18\nS10 | I00 | S2 | 55\nS10 | I01 | S4 | 36\nS10 | I10 | S1 | 43\nS10 | I11 | S2 | 60\nS11 | I00 | S8 | 26\nS11 | I01 | S0 | 57\nS11 | I10 | S0 | 31\nS11 | I11 | S0 | 2\nStarting from state S0, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I01 -> I11 -> I01 -> I01 -> I11 -> I10 -> I00 -> I01, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "389",
    "answer": "[[45 -> 42 -> 4 -> 18 -> 55 -> 45 -> 62 -> 17 -> 29]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1178"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S6 | 53\nS0 | I01 | S7 | 48\nS0 | I10 | S0 | 12\nS0 | I11 | S0 | 11\nS1 | I00 | S0 | 54\nS1 | I01 | S9 | 60\nS1 | I10 | S4 | 4\nS1 | I11 | S11 | 17\nS2 | I00 | S5 | 14\nS2 | I01 | S6 | 10\nS2 | I10 | S8 | 34\nS2 | I11 | S9 | 61\nS3 | I00 | S0 | 28\nS3 | I01 | S6 | 39\nS3 | I10 | S1 | 61\nS3 | I11 | S2 | 24\nS4 | I00 | S2 | 62\nS4 | I01 | S5 | 44\nS4 | I10 | S8 | 52\nS4 | I11 | S8 | 44\nS5 | I00 | S10 | 31\nS5 | I01 | S10 | 31\nS5 | I10 | S11 | 62\nS5 | I11 | S6 | 8\nS6 | I00 | S3 | 38\nS6 | I01 | S5 | 37\nS6 | I10 | S4 | 5\nS6 | I11 | S9 | 60\nS7 | I00 | S0 | 53\nS7 | I01 | S6 | 13\nS7 | I10 | S5 | 36\nS7 | I11 | S8 | 45\nS8 | I00 | S2 | 35\nS8 | I01 | S0 | 41\nS8 | I10 | S6 | 7\nS8 | I11 | S0 | 5\nS9 | I00 | S2 | 2\nS9 | I01 | S8 | 28\nS9 | I10 | S7 | 10\nS9 | I11 | S7 | 22\nS10 | I00 | S2 | 61\nS10 | I01 | S9 | 31\nS10 | I10 | S5 | 56\nS10 | I11 | S3 | 14\nS11 | I00 | S0 | 10\nS11 | I01 | S7 | 42\nS11 | I10 | S2 | 62\nS11 | I11 | S4 | 34\nStarting from state S1, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I10 -> I10 -> I00 -> I10 -> I01 -> I11 -> I11 -> I11, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "390",
    "answer": "[[60 -> 10 -> 36 -> 31 -> 56 -> 31 -> 14 -> 24 -> 61]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1179"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S3 | 60\nS0 | I01 | S1 | 52\nS0 | I10 | S1 | 33\nS0 | I11 | S7 | 42\nS1 | I00 | S1 | 22\nS1 | I01 | S4 | 3\nS1 | I10 | S7 | 2\nS1 | I11 | S2 | 42\nS2 | I00 | S10 | 43\nS2 | I01 | S6 | 42\nS2 | I10 | S1 | 12\nS2 | I11 | S0 | 40\nS3 | I00 | S10 | 44\nS3 | I01 | S10 | 49\nS3 | I10 | S8 | 55\nS3 | I11 | S9 | 23\nS4 | I00 | S2 | 54\nS4 | I01 | S1 | 6\nS4 | I10 | S10 | 7\nS4 | I11 | S11 | 35\nS5 | I00 | S10 | 58\nS5 | I01 | S6 | 18\nS5 | I10 | S11 | 53\nS5 | I11 | S2 | 50\nS6 | I00 | S9 | 59\nS6 | I01 | S2 | 56\nS6 | I10 | S9 | 8\nS6 | I11 | S11 | 45\nS7 | I00 | S3 | 23\nS7 | I01 | S10 | 54\nS7 | I10 | S10 | 51\nS7 | I11 | S9 | 27\nS8 | I00 | S0 | 6\nS8 | I01 | S4 | 25\nS8 | I10 | S7 | 60\nS8 | I11 | S9 | 54\nS9 | I00 | S1 | 20\nS9 | I01 | S3 | 14\nS9 | I10 | S4 | 51\nS9 | I11 | S2 | 17\nS10 | I00 | S2 | 59\nS10 | I01 | S4 | 7\nS10 | I10 | S0 | 44\nS10 | I11 | S4 | 4\nS11 | I00 | S0 | 35\nS11 | I01 | S6 | 15\nS11 | I10 | S3 | 1\nS11 | I11 | S2 | 33\nStarting from state S1, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I01 -> I10 -> I00 -> I10 -> I11 -> I00 -> I01 -> I00, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "391",
    "answer": "[[3 -> 6 -> 2 -> 23 -> 55 -> 54 -> 20 -> 3 -> 54]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1182"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S6 | 43\nS0 | I01 | S7 | 63\nS0 | I10 | S10 | 44\nS0 | I11 | S11 | 57\nS1 | I00 | S1 | 51\nS1 | I01 | S2 | 46\nS1 | I10 | S3 | 23\nS1 | I11 | S4 | 60\nS2 | I00 | S6 | 43\nS2 | I01 | S5 | 11\nS2 | I10 | S1 | 23\nS2 | I11 | S8 | 18\nS3 | I00 | S7 | 2\nS3 | I01 | S4 | 43\nS3 | I10 | S4 | 42\nS3 | I11 | S8 | 33\nS4 | I00 | S3 | 53\nS4 | I01 | S11 | 36\nS4 | I10 | S8 | 14\nS4 | I11 | S11 | 0\nS5 | I00 | S6 | 42\nS5 | I01 | S3 | 36\nS5 | I10 | S5 | 53\nS5 | I11 | S6 | 39\nS6 | I00 | S11 | 57\nS6 | I01 | S8 | 38\nS6 | I10 | S6 | 50\nS6 | I11 | S6 | 16\nS7 | I00 | S4 | 22\nS7 | I01 | S5 | 60\nS7 | I10 | S1 | 33\nS7 | I11 | S9 | 43\nS8 | I00 | S10 | 21\nS8 | I01 | S3 | 37\nS8 | I10 | S6 | 1\nS8 | I11 | S9 | 0\nS9 | I00 | S6 | 55\nS9 | I01 | S6 | 23\nS9 | I10 | S0 | 38\nS9 | I11 | S10 | 63\nS10 | I00 | S4 | 44\nS10 | I01 | S11 | 22\nS10 | I10 | S11 | 10\nS10 | I11 | S10 | 51\nS11 | I00 | S9 | 57\nS11 | I01 | S3 | 15\nS11 | I10 | S7 | 1\nS11 | I11 | S8 | 52\nStarting from state S5, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I01 -> I10 -> I01 -> I11 -> I00 -> I00 -> I10 -> I11, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "392",
    "answer": "[[36 -> 43 -> 14 -> 37 -> 33 -> 21 -> 44 -> 14 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1186"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S5 | 1\nS0 | I01 | S9 | 15\nS0 | I10 | S5 | 26\nS0 | I11 | S6 | 7\nS1 | I00 | S3 | 11\nS1 | I01 | S3 | 23\nS1 | I10 | S0 | 8\nS1 | I11 | S1 | 13\nS2 | I00 | S3 | 20\nS2 | I01 | S5 | 7\nS2 | I10 | S5 | 1\nS2 | I11 | S3 | 18\nS3 | I00 | S3 | 31\nS3 | I01 | S8 | 7\nS3 | I10 | S4 | 16\nS3 | I11 | S0 | 10\nS4 | I00 | S6 | 22\nS4 | I01 | S2 | 13\nS4 | I10 | S5 | 20\nS4 | I11 | S1 | 3\nS5 | I00 | S6 | 27\nS5 | I01 | S2 | 19\nS5 | I10 | S7 | 24\nS5 | I11 | S9 | 14\nS6 | I00 | S8 | 27\nS6 | I01 | S2 | 7\nS6 | I10 | S3 | 27\nS6 | I11 | S9 | 29\nS7 | I00 | S8 | 5\nS7 | I01 | S0 | 21\nS7 | I10 | S4 | 27\nS7 | I11 | S1 | 12\nS8 | I00 | S2 | 28\nS8 | I01 | S0 | 31\nS8 | I10 | S8 | 15\nS8 | I11 | S1 | 8\nS9 | I00 | S3 | 3\nS9 | I01 | S8 | 17\nS9 | I10 | S6 | 24\nS9 | I11 | S2 | 18\nStarting from state S7, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I01 -> I10 -> I00 -> I01 -> I11 -> I00 -> I00, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "393",
    "answer": "[[21 -> 15 -> 24 -> 27 -> 31 -> 7 -> 27 -> 28]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1003"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S1 | 37\nS0 | I01 | S8 | 39\nS0 | I10 | S4 | 44\nS0 | I11 | S8 | 4\nS1 | I00 | S0 | 1\nS1 | I01 | S4 | 32\nS1 | I10 | S2 | 5\nS1 | I11 | S6 | 2\nS2 | I00 | S10 | 27\nS2 | I01 | S5 | 21\nS2 | I10 | S2 | 46\nS2 | I11 | S8 | 50\nS3 | I00 | S2 | 33\nS3 | I01 | S1 | 52\nS3 | I10 | S6 | 15\nS3 | I11 | S0 | 1\nS4 | I00 | S8 | 7\nS4 | I01 | S0 | 34\nS4 | I10 | S11 | 45\nS4 | I11 | S11 | 40\nS5 | I00 | S9 | 46\nS5 | I01 | S10 | 11\nS5 | I10 | S3 | 0\nS5 | I11 | S9 | 23\nS6 | I00 | S6 | 30\nS6 | I01 | S7 | 51\nS6 | I10 | S0 | 46\nS6 | I11 | S9 | 19\nS7 | I00 | S9 | 54\nS7 | I01 | S8 | 48\nS7 | I10 | S6 | 53\nS7 | I11 | S2 | 49\nS8 | I00 | S4 | 2\nS8 | I01 | S7 | 46\nS8 | I10 | S10 | 59\nS8 | I11 | S10 | 62\nS9 | I00 | S1 | 33\nS9 | I01 | S11 | 29\nS9 | I10 | S6 | 4\nS9 | I11 | S4 | 29\nS10 | I00 | S10 | 17\nS10 | I01 | S2 | 4\nS10 | I10 | S2 | 49\nS10 | I11 | S2 | 52\nS11 | I00 | S11 | 51\nS11 | I01 | S2 | 28\nS11 | I10 | S9 | 12\nS11 | I11 | S5 | 36\nStarting from state S8, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I00 -> I11 -> I10 -> I11 -> I00 -> I11 -> I10 -> I11, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "394",
    "answer": "[[62 -> 17 -> 52 -> 46 -> 50 -> 2 -> 40 -> 12 -> 29]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1180"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S6 | 57\nS0 | I01 | S7 | 57\nS0 | I10 | S11 | 13\nS0 | I11 | S7 | 12\nS1 | I00 | S0 | 24\nS1 | I01 | S4 | 29\nS1 | I10 | S7 | 13\nS1 | I11 | S3 | 34\nS2 | I00 | S4 | 17\nS2 | I01 | S8 | 38\nS2 | I10 | S1 | 53\nS2 | I11 | S7 | 21\nS3 | I00 | S5 | 12\nS3 | I01 | S0 | 46\nS3 | I10 | S11 | 28\nS3 | I11 | S6 | 6\nS4 | I00 | S6 | 21\nS4 | I01 | S10 | 53\nS4 | I10 | S11 | 41\nS4 | I11 | S6 | 28\nS5 | I00 | S11 | 52\nS5 | I01 | S11 | 46\nS5 | I10 | S10 | 31\nS5 | I11 | S4 | 40\nS6 | I00 | S7 | 27\nS6 | I01 | S5 | 56\nS6 | I10 | S11 | 9\nS6 | I11 | S6 | 49\nS7 | I00 | S3 | 49\nS7 | I01 | S4 | 54\nS7 | I10 | S9 | 62\nS7 | I11 | S10 | 2\nS8 | I00 | S11 | 18\nS8 | I01 | S3 | 11\nS8 | I10 | S5 | 46\nS8 | I11 | S4 | 48\nS9 | I00 | S10 | 49\nS9 | I01 | S4 | 53\nS9 | I10 | S0 | 52\nS9 | I11 | S11 | 40\nS10 | I00 | S5 | 15\nS10 | I01 | S8 | 40\nS10 | I10 | S5 | 61\nS10 | I11 | S1 | 23\nS11 | I00 | S6 | 31\nS11 | I01 | S2 | 27\nS11 | I10 | S5 | 57\nS11 | I11 | S6 | 10\nStarting from state S3, and given the input sequence: I00 -> I00 -> I10 -> I00 -> I10 -> I00 -> I10 -> I11 -> I10, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "395",
    "answer": "[[12 -> 52 -> 57 -> 52 -> 57 -> 52 -> 57 -> 40 -> 41]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1190"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S2 | 40\nS0 | I01 | S3 | 0\nS0 | I10 | S2 | 24\nS0 | I11 | S7 | 52\nS1 | I00 | S5 | 15\nS1 | I01 | S9 | 51\nS1 | I10 | S3 | 35\nS1 | I11 | S2 | 3\nS2 | I00 | S1 | 52\nS2 | I01 | S6 | 17\nS2 | I10 | S11 | 56\nS2 | I11 | S2 | 50\nS3 | I00 | S6 | 19\nS3 | I01 | S8 | 26\nS3 | I10 | S2 | 14\nS3 | I11 | S2 | 59\nS4 | I00 | S1 | 22\nS4 | I01 | S11 | 0\nS4 | I10 | S8 | 14\nS4 | I11 | S9 | 58\nS5 | I00 | S0 | 38\nS5 | I01 | S9 | 49\nS5 | I10 | S1 | 0\nS5 | I11 | S8 | 4\nS6 | I00 | S2 | 63\nS6 | I01 | S5 | 30\nS6 | I10 | S5 | 12\nS6 | I11 | S10 | 47\nS7 | I00 | S5 | 20\nS7 | I01 | S5 | 13\nS7 | I10 | S1 | 55\nS7 | I11 | S4 | 42\nS8 | I00 | S6 | 50\nS8 | I01 | S5 | 6\nS8 | I10 | S1 | 5\nS8 | I11 | S6 | 50\nS9 | I00 | S3 | 33\nS9 | I01 | S8 | 24\nS9 | I10 | S7 | 48\nS9 | I11 | S6 | 13\nS10 | I00 | S11 | 12\nS10 | I01 | S7 | 48\nS10 | I10 | S10 | 17\nS10 | I11 | S8 | 37\nS11 | I00 | S5 | 16\nS11 | I01 | S2 | 14\nS11 | I10 | S5 | 19\nS11 | I11 | S8 | 32\nStarting from state S3, and given the input sequence: I10 -> I10 -> I11 -> I10 -> I11 -> I01 -> I11 -> I10 -> I10, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "396",
    "answer": "[[14 -> 56 -> 32 -> 5 -> 3 -> 17 -> 47 -> 17 -> 17]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1179"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S4 | 57\nS0 | I01 | S7 | 53\nS0 | I10 | S10 | 3\nS0 | I11 | S9 | 54\nS1 | I00 | S3 | 23\nS1 | I01 | S6 | 56\nS1 | I10 | S7 | 34\nS1 | I11 | S6 | 49\nS2 | I00 | S4 | 47\nS2 | I01 | S1 | 27\nS2 | I10 | S8 | 62\nS2 | I11 | S6 | 58\nS3 | I00 | S5 | 13\nS3 | I01 | S9 | 36\nS3 | I10 | S11 | 26\nS3 | I11 | S2 | 49\nS4 | I00 | S10 | 49\nS4 | I01 | S0 | 25\nS4 | I10 | S11 | 32\nS4 | I11 | S4 | 10\nS5 | I00 | S2 | 17\nS5 | I01 | S1 | 57\nS5 | I10 | S4 | 29\nS5 | I11 | S3 | 61\nS6 | I00 | S5 | 55\nS6 | I01 | S10 | 23\nS6 | I10 | S8 | 21\nS6 | I11 | S3 | 23\nS7 | I00 | S8 | 29\nS7 | I01 | S8 | 6\nS7 | I10 | S9 | 60\nS7 | I11 | S11 | 63\nS8 | I00 | S6 | 43\nS8 | I01 | S0 | 40\nS8 | I10 | S5 | 16\nS8 | I11 | S7 | 43\nS9 | I00 | S10 | 25\nS9 | I01 | S10 | 41\nS9 | I10 | S4 | 40\nS9 | I11 | S10 | 61\nS10 | I00 | S7 | 35\nS10 | I01 | S0 | 58\nS10 | I10 | S9 | 42\nS10 | I11 | S5 | 59\nS11 | I00 | S7 | 33\nS11 | I01 | S8 | 11\nS11 | I10 | S11 | 20\nS11 | I11 | S7 | 42\nStarting from state S1, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I00 -> I01 -> I01 -> I11 -> I00 -> I01 -> I11 -> I01, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "397",
    "answer": "[[49 -> 55 -> 57 -> 56 -> 23 -> 13 -> 57 -> 49 -> 23]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1189"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S3 | 51\nS0 | I01 | S3 | 9\nS0 | I10 | S9 | 46\nS0 | I11 | S5 | 21\nS1 | I00 | S5 | 50\nS1 | I01 | S9 | 24\nS1 | I10 | S4 | 20\nS1 | I11 | S5 | 63\nS2 | I00 | S5 | 45\nS2 | I01 | S2 | 28\nS2 | I10 | S0 | 33\nS2 | I11 | S11 | 33\nS3 | I00 | S5 | 6\nS3 | I01 | S8 | 6\nS3 | I10 | S3 | 58\nS3 | I11 | S0 | 0\nS4 | I00 | S5 | 46\nS4 | I01 | S3 | 59\nS4 | I10 | S0 | 28\nS4 | I11 | S7 | 47\nS5 | I00 | S8 | 2\nS5 | I01 | S9 | 1\nS5 | I10 | S3 | 49\nS5 | I11 | S5 | 30\nS6 | I00 | S3 | 21\nS6 | I01 | S4 | 44\nS6 | I10 | S4 | 63\nS6 | I11 | S0 | 41\nS7 | I00 | S11 | 43\nS7 | I01 | S11 | 17\nS7 | I10 | S1 | 25\nS7 | I11 | S7 | 15\nS8 | I00 | S8 | 6\nS8 | I01 | S0 | 30\nS8 | I10 | S9 | 60\nS8 | I11 | S9 | 27\nS9 | I00 | S10 | 13\nS9 | I01 | S3 | 17\nS9 | I10 | S2 | 55\nS9 | I11 | S1 | 30\nS10 | I00 | S11 | 7\nS10 | I01 | S10 | 31\nS10 | I10 | S6 | 35\nS10 | I11 | S8 | 42\nS11 | I00 | S0 | 63\nS11 | I01 | S10 | 3\nS11 | I10 | S6 | 22\nS11 | I11 | S10 | 27\nStarting from state S8, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I10 -> I10 -> I10 -> I10 -> I11 -> I11 -> I00 -> I10, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "398",
    "answer": "[[27 -> 55 -> 33 -> 46 -> 55 -> 33 -> 27 -> 7 -> 22]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1180"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S5 | 46\nS0 | I01 | S8 | 19\nS0 | I10 | S2 | 47\nS0 | I11 | S2 | 54\nS1 | I00 | S9 | 27\nS1 | I01 | S8 | 4\nS1 | I10 | S9 | 20\nS1 | I11 | S10 | 3\nS2 | I00 | S10 | 17\nS2 | I01 | S11 | 54\nS2 | I10 | S5 | 28\nS2 | I11 | S10 | 38\nS3 | I00 | S0 | 43\nS3 | I01 | S6 | 24\nS3 | I10 | S11 | 60\nS3 | I11 | S7 | 9\nS4 | I00 | S9 | 57\nS4 | I01 | S8 | 6\nS4 | I10 | S9 | 43\nS4 | I11 | S2 | 12\nS5 | I00 | S4 | 43\nS5 | I01 | S8 | 49\nS5 | I10 | S5 | 60\nS5 | I11 | S2 | 19\nS6 | I00 | S0 | 58\nS6 | I01 | S6 | 21\nS6 | I10 | S8 | 32\nS6 | I11 | S1 | 35\nS7 | I00 | S9 | 61\nS7 | I01 | S0 | 32\nS7 | I10 | S0 | 36\nS7 | I11 | S7 | 45\nS8 | I00 | S9 | 6\nS8 | I01 | S9 | 45\nS8 | I10 | S8 | 18\nS8 | I11 | S5 | 52\nS9 | I00 | S7 | 39\nS9 | I01 | S8 | 23\nS9 | I10 | S7 | 61\nS9 | I11 | S5 | 53\nS10 | I00 | S10 | 46\nS10 | I01 | S9 | 11\nS10 | I10 | S5 | 48\nS10 | I11 | S9 | 9\nS11 | I00 | S2 | 49\nS11 | I01 | S11 | 30\nS11 | I10 | S7 | 32\nS11 | I11 | S8 | 31\nStarting from state S9, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I11 -> I01 -> I01 -> I11 -> I10 -> I01 -> I10 -> I10, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "399",
    "answer": "[[23 -> 52 -> 49 -> 45 -> 53 -> 60 -> 49 -> 18 -> 18]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1182"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S4 | 48\nS0 | I01 | S11 | 56\nS0 | I10 | S4 | 63\nS0 | I11 | S6 | 57\nS1 | I00 | S8 | 31\nS1 | I01 | S8 | 55\nS1 | I10 | S9 | 11\nS1 | I11 | S11 | 13\nS2 | I00 | S0 | 4\nS2 | I01 | S11 | 23\nS2 | I10 | S7 | 7\nS2 | I11 | S6 | 23\nS3 | I00 | S1 | 12\nS3 | I01 | S9 | 57\nS3 | I10 | S9 | 10\nS3 | I11 | S4 | 11\nS4 | I00 | S5 | 25\nS4 | I01 | S9 | 16\nS4 | I10 | S10 | 62\nS4 | I11 | S2 | 7\nS5 | I00 | S9 | 60\nS5 | I01 | S5 | 31\nS5 | I10 | S0 | 11\nS5 | I11 | S10 | 2\nS6 | I00 | S2 | 9\nS6 | I01 | S9 | 46\nS6 | I10 | S8 | 46\nS6 | I11 | S3 | 8\nS7 | I00 | S6 | 5\nS7 | I01 | S10 | 58\nS7 | I10 | S11 | 36\nS7 | I11 | S9 | 34\nS8 | I00 | S9 | 17\nS8 | I01 | S11 | 62\nS8 | I10 | S10 | 38\nS8 | I11 | S2 | 1\nS9 | I00 | S2 | 33\nS9 | I01 | S8 | 27\nS9 | I10 | S2 | 25\nS9 | I11 | S3 | 18\nS10 | I00 | S6 | 9\nS10 | I01 | S0 | 24\nS10 | I10 | S3 | 2\nS10 | I11 | S10 | 34\nS11 | I00 | S11 | 37\nS11 | I01 | S2 | 38\nS11 | I10 | S8 | 56\nS11 | I11 | S4 | 9\nStarting from state S7, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I01 -> I00 -> I11 -> I11 -> I10 -> I00 -> I01 -> I11, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "400",
    "answer": "[[58 -> 24 -> 48 -> 7 -> 23 -> 46 -> 17 -> 27 -> 1]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1181"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S0 | 49\nS0 | I01 | S4 | 18\nS0 | I10 | S10 | 28\nS0 | I11 | S8 | 23\nS1 | I00 | S7 | 0\nS1 | I01 | S9 | 17\nS1 | I10 | S11 | 4\nS1 | I11 | S7 | 2\nS2 | I00 | S1 | 24\nS2 | I01 | S2 | 5\nS2 | I10 | S3 | 35\nS2 | I11 | S9 | 46\nS3 | I00 | S7 | 58\nS3 | I01 | S4 | 36\nS3 | I10 | S7 | 25\nS3 | I11 | S9 | 4\nS4 | I00 | S6 | 14\nS4 | I01 | S2 | 62\nS4 | I10 | S2 | 54\nS4 | I11 | S5 | 15\nS5 | I00 | S0 | 30\nS5 | I01 | S6 | 43\nS5 | I10 | S3 | 23\nS5 | I11 | S7 | 38\nS6 | I00 | S3 | 47\nS6 | I01 | S11 | 63\nS6 | I10 | S1 | 58\nS6 | I11 | S8 | 2\nS7 | I00 | S8 | 51\nS7 | I01 | S6 | 34\nS7 | I10 | S10 | 43\nS7 | I11 | S0 | 63\nS8 | I00 | S0 | 51\nS8 | I01 | S7 | 48\nS8 | I10 | S9 | 36\nS8 | I11 | S9 | 21\nS9 | I00 | S5 | 51\nS9 | I01 | S6 | 60\nS9 | I10 | S1 | 40\nS9 | I11 | S9 | 19\nS10 | I00 | S9 | 53\nS10 | I01 | S11 | 42\nS10 | I10 | S8 | 28\nS10 | I11 | S4 | 4\nS11 | I00 | S4 | 61\nS11 | I01 | S5 | 12\nS11 | I10 | S4 | 55\nS11 | I11 | S0 | 15\nStarting from state S8, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I11 -> I01 -> I10 -> I10 -> I00 -> I11 -> I01 -> I00, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "401",
    "answer": "[[48 -> 63 -> 18 -> 54 -> 35 -> 58 -> 63 -> 18 -> 14]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1179"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S5 | 11\nS0 | I01 | S2 | 41\nS0 | I10 | S5 | 43\nS0 | I11 | S11 | 38\nS1 | I00 | S6 | 34\nS1 | I01 | S10 | 7\nS1 | I10 | S7 | 47\nS1 | I11 | S3 | 51\nS2 | I00 | S10 | 4\nS2 | I01 | S6 | 16\nS2 | I10 | S2 | 42\nS2 | I11 | S6 | 22\nS3 | I00 | S5 | 51\nS3 | I01 | S11 | 16\nS3 | I10 | S3 | 9\nS3 | I11 | S10 | 24\nS4 | I00 | S8 | 46\nS4 | I01 | S11 | 34\nS4 | I10 | S0 | 48\nS4 | I11 | S0 | 8\nS5 | I00 | S4 | 9\nS5 | I01 | S7 | 40\nS5 | I10 | S7 | 18\nS5 | I11 | S11 | 7\nS6 | I00 | S3 | 42\nS6 | I01 | S5 | 12\nS6 | I10 | S10 | 27\nS6 | I11 | S10 | 53\nS7 | I00 | S7 | 17\nS7 | I01 | S9 | 59\nS7 | I10 | S7 | 14\nS7 | I11 | S8 | 34\nS8 | I00 | S11 | 23\nS8 | I01 | S6 | 10\nS8 | I10 | S6 | 5\nS8 | I11 | S8 | 28\nS9 | I00 | S1 | 2\nS9 | I01 | S2 | 8\nS9 | I10 | S7 | 60\nS9 | I11 | S9 | 5\nS10 | I00 | S5 | 14\nS10 | I01 | S6 | 7\nS10 | I10 | S11 | 55\nS10 | I11 | S8 | 51\nS11 | I00 | S3 | 10\nS11 | I01 | S8 | 6\nS11 | I10 | S2 | 36\nS11 | I11 | S0 | 56\nStarting from state S0, and given the input sequence: I10 -> I11 -> I01 -> I11 -> I10 -> I00 -> I01 -> I10 -> I11, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "402",
    "answer": "[[43 -> 7 -> 6 -> 28 -> 5 -> 42 -> 16 -> 36 -> 22]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1180"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S0 | 50\nS0 | I01 | S4 | 62\nS0 | I10 | S8 | 30\nS0 | I11 | S7 | 25\nS1 | I00 | S5 | 62\nS1 | I01 | S2 | 8\nS1 | I10 | S8 | 8\nS1 | I11 | S8 | 10\nS2 | I00 | S4 | 22\nS2 | I01 | S5 | 16\nS2 | I10 | S5 | 37\nS2 | I11 | S8 | 17\nS3 | I00 | S3 | 11\nS3 | I01 | S9 | 11\nS3 | I10 | S7 | 51\nS3 | I11 | S7 | 46\nS4 | I00 | S6 | 16\nS4 | I01 | S11 | 6\nS4 | I10 | S2 | 20\nS4 | I11 | S9 | 24\nS5 | I00 | S4 | 2\nS5 | I01 | S2 | 11\nS5 | I10 | S5 | 10\nS5 | I11 | S5 | 10\nS6 | I00 | S3 | 12\nS6 | I01 | S7 | 4\nS6 | I10 | S1 | 37\nS6 | I11 | S11 | 48\nS7 | I00 | S5 | 1\nS7 | I01 | S10 | 37\nS7 | I10 | S9 | 20\nS7 | I11 | S3 | 62\nS8 | I00 | S5 | 11\nS8 | I01 | S11 | 18\nS8 | I10 | S9 | 60\nS8 | I11 | S11 | 13\nS9 | I00 | S2 | 55\nS9 | I01 | S11 | 1\nS9 | I10 | S6 | 38\nS9 | I11 | S2 | 14\nS10 | I00 | S1 | 62\nS10 | I01 | S0 | 34\nS10 | I10 | S8 | 11\nS10 | I11 | S0 | 16\nS11 | I00 | S7 | 39\nS11 | I01 | S7 | 4\nS11 | I10 | S7 | 15\nS11 | I11 | S7 | 30\nStarting from state S10, and given the input sequence: I00 -> I10 -> I01 -> I00 -> I01 -> I11 -> I10 -> I00 -> I11, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "403",
    "answer": "[[62 -> 8 -> 18 -> 39 -> 37 -> 16 -> 30 -> 11 -> 10]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1180"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S3 | 48\nS0 | I01 | S6 | 27\nS0 | I10 | S4 | 60\nS0 | I11 | S6 | 7\nS1 | I00 | S11 | 24\nS1 | I01 | S7 | 34\nS1 | I10 | S5 | 41\nS1 | I11 | S4 | 26\nS2 | I00 | S7 | 48\nS2 | I01 | S9 | 59\nS2 | I10 | S4 | 37\nS2 | I11 | S6 | 4\nS3 | I00 | S2 | 48\nS3 | I01 | S3 | 7\nS3 | I10 | S10 | 25\nS3 | I11 | S6 | 46\nS4 | I00 | S5 | 24\nS4 | I01 | S1 | 59\nS4 | I10 | S2 | 5\nS4 | I11 | S7 | 61\nS5 | I00 | S0 | 62\nS5 | I01 | S8 | 37\nS5 | I10 | S7 | 11\nS5 | I11 | S9 | 4\nS6 | I00 | S2 | 60\nS6 | I01 | S1 | 17\nS6 | I10 | S3 | 21\nS6 | I11 | S8 | 2\nS7 | I00 | S4 | 7\nS7 | I01 | S1 | 3\nS7 | I10 | S9 | 55\nS7 | I11 | S9 | 60\nS8 | I00 | S1 | 60\nS8 | I01 | S1 | 29\nS8 | I10 | S8 | 35\nS8 | I11 | S3 | 50\nS9 | I00 | S11 | 54\nS9 | I01 | S5 | 28\nS9 | I10 | S9 | 13\nS9 | I11 | S4 | 26\nS10 | I00 | S3 | 40\nS10 | I01 | S11 | 13\nS10 | I10 | S8 | 60\nS10 | I11 | S1 | 27\nS11 | I00 | S10 | 23\nS11 | I01 | S9 | 15\nS11 | I10 | S10 | 2\nS11 | I11 | S2 | 12\nStarting from state S8, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I11 -> I10 -> I00 -> I11 -> I00 -> I01 -> I01 -> I11, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "404",
    "answer": "[[29 -> 26 -> 5 -> 48 -> 60 -> 54 -> 15 -> 28 -> 4]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1178"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S2 | 6\nS0 | I01 | S5 | 38\nS0 | I10 | S0 | 57\nS0 | I11 | S2 | 34\nS1 | I00 | S6 | 1\nS1 | I01 | S0 | 37\nS1 | I10 | S11 | 5\nS1 | I11 | S8 | 59\nS2 | I00 | S3 | 5\nS2 | I01 | S0 | 31\nS2 | I10 | S8 | 28\nS2 | I11 | S9 | 29\nS3 | I00 | S7 | 32\nS3 | I01 | S9 | 36\nS3 | I10 | S11 | 54\nS3 | I11 | S2 | 16\nS4 | I00 | S2 | 47\nS4 | I01 | S1 | 30\nS4 | I10 | S1 | 26\nS4 | I11 | S7 | 9\nS5 | I00 | S4 | 56\nS5 | I01 | S8 | 59\nS5 | I10 | S5 | 57\nS5 | I11 | S11 | 35\nS6 | I00 | S0 | 11\nS6 | I01 | S7 | 11\nS6 | I10 | S3 | 54\nS6 | I11 | S8 | 0\nS7 | I00 | S8 | 36\nS7 | I01 | S9 | 28\nS7 | I10 | S2 | 33\nS7 | I11 | S6 | 14\nS8 | I00 | S9 | 30\nS8 | I01 | S9 | 32\nS8 | I10 | S8 | 18\nS8 | I11 | S7 | 28\nS9 | I00 | S1 | 59\nS9 | I01 | S7 | 2\nS9 | I10 | S0 | 54\nS9 | I11 | S3 | 6\nS10 | I00 | S9 | 20\nS10 | I01 | S9 | 15\nS10 | I10 | S8 | 5\nS10 | I11 | S6 | 11\nS11 | I00 | S11 | 14\nS11 | I01 | S9 | 25\nS11 | I10 | S9 | 20\nS11 | I11 | S9 | 24\nStarting from state S8, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I00 -> I11 -> I00 -> I00 -> I00 -> I01 -> I01 -> I01, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "405",
    "answer": "[[28 -> 36 -> 28 -> 36 -> 30 -> 59 -> 37 -> 38 -> 59]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1176"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S6 | 51\nS0 | I01 | S3 | 12\nS0 | I10 | S1 | 61\nS0 | I11 | S9 | 38\nS1 | I00 | S2 | 60\nS1 | I01 | S2 | 29\nS1 | I10 | S2 | 47\nS1 | I11 | S0 | 37\nS2 | I00 | S5 | 59\nS2 | I01 | S0 | 15\nS2 | I10 | S7 | 0\nS2 | I11 | S6 | 56\nS3 | I00 | S5 | 22\nS3 | I01 | S11 | 11\nS3 | I10 | S4 | 4\nS3 | I11 | S5 | 7\nS4 | I00 | S9 | 36\nS4 | I01 | S11 | 0\nS4 | I10 | S10 | 33\nS4 | I11 | S9 | 1\nS5 | I00 | S4 | 0\nS5 | I01 | S0 | 51\nS5 | I10 | S5 | 3\nS5 | I11 | S1 | 22\nS6 | I00 | S4 | 32\nS6 | I01 | S2 | 55\nS6 | I10 | S5 | 5\nS6 | I11 | S11 | 35\nS7 | I00 | S11 | 29\nS7 | I01 | S9 | 60\nS7 | I10 | S5 | 50\nS7 | I11 | S10 | 58\nS8 | I00 | S8 | 35\nS8 | I01 | S7 | 42\nS8 | I10 | S10 | 36\nS8 | I11 | S1 | 9\nS9 | I00 | S0 | 52\nS9 | I01 | S11 | 34\nS9 | I10 | S9 | 30\nS9 | I11 | S2 | 1\nS10 | I00 | S5 | 46\nS10 | I01 | S2 | 1\nS10 | I10 | S7 | 12\nS10 | I11 | S4 | 19\nS11 | I00 | S6 | 50\nS11 | I01 | S7 | 11\nS11 | I10 | S3 | 9\nS11 | I11 | S8 | 28\nStarting from state S5, and given the input sequence: I11 -> I00 -> I01 -> I11 -> I10 -> I10 -> I11 -> I11 -> I10, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "406",
    "answer": "[[22 -> 60 -> 15 -> 38 -> 30 -> 30 -> 1 -> 56 -> 5]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1177"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Mealy machine is defined by the following state transition table:\nCurrent State | Input | Next State | Output\nS0 | I00 | S2 | 62\nS0 | I01 | S11 | 55\nS0 | I10 | S4 | 43\nS0 | I11 | S4 | 41\nS1 | I00 | S6 | 15\nS1 | I01 | S8 | 61\nS1 | I10 | S2 | 23\nS1 | I11 | S7 | 55\nS2 | I00 | S1 | 63\nS2 | I01 | S11 | 56\nS2 | I10 | S3 | 35\nS2 | I11 | S7 | 62\nS3 | I00 | S2 | 48\nS3 | I01 | S1 | 41\nS3 | I10 | S6 | 17\nS3 | I11 | S5 | 13\nS4 | I00 | S1 | 4\nS4 | I01 | S11 | 26\nS4 | I10 | S4 | 23\nS4 | I11 | S6 | 43\nS5 | I00 | S8 | 43\nS5 | I01 | S11 | 35\nS5 | I10 | S2 | 30\nS5 | I11 | S4 | 19\nS6 | I00 | S3 | 49\nS6 | I01 | S2 | 60\nS6 | I10 | S2 | 40\nS6 | I11 | S7 | 54\nS7 | I00 | S1 | 16\nS7 | I01 | S3 | 24\nS7 | I10 | S2 | 52\nS7 | I11 | S0 | 6\nS8 | I00 | S2 | 27\nS8 | I01 | S1 | 1\nS8 | I10 | S3 | 40\nS8 | I11 | S2 | 44\nS9 | I00 | S11 | 38\nS9 | I01 | S1 | 22\nS9 | I10 | S5 | 56\nS9 | I11 | S3 | 20\nS10 | I00 | S3 | 0\nS10 | I01 | S4 | 16\nS10 | I10 | S8 | 45\nS10 | I11 | S0 | 33\nS11 | I00 | S6 | 29\nS11 | I01 | S3 | 35\nS11 | I10 | S5 | 7\nS11 | I11 | S7 | 29\nStarting from state S11, and given the input sequence: I01 -> I11 -> I01 -> I10 -> I01 -> I01 -> I10 -> I01 -> I10, determine the sequence of outputs.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "407",
    "answer": "[[35 -> 13 -> 35 -> 7 -> 35 -> 35 -> 17 -> 60 -> 35]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "1182"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D, E, F and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "408",
    "answer": "[[A'+BC+DEF]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "4729"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D, E, F, G and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "409",
    "answer": "[[A'G+B'C'F+ABDE]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "10236"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D, E, F, G and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "410",
    "answer": "[[A'G+B'C'F+ABDE]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "10236"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D, E, F, G and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "411",
    "answer": "[[A'G+B'C'F+ABDE]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "10236"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D, E, F, G and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "412",
    "answer": "[[A'G+B'C'F+ABDE]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "10236"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D, E, F, G and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1, 'G': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "413",
    "answer": "[[A'G+B'C'F+ABDE]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "10236"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D, E, F and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1, 'F': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "414",
    "answer": "[[A'+BC+DEF]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "4729"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D, E and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "415",
    "answer": "[[A'+B'C'+BDE]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "2230"
  },
  {
    "question": "Given the input variables A, B, C, D, E and the following output for each combination:\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 0, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 0, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 0, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 0, 'E': 1}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 0}, Output: 0\n  Inputs: {'A': 1, 'B': 1, 'C': 1, 'D': 1, 'E': 1}, Output: 1\nUse a Karnaugh map to find the simplified expression for the output. Please provide the simplified expression in the format of [[A+B'+C+D'(this is an example, try to use simplist form and use A' to indicate not A)]])]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "416",
    "answer": "[[A'+B'C'+BDE]]",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "2230"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-64 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 6 select lines: ['var11', 'var6', 'var8', 'var10', 'var1', 'var3'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var11=0, var6=1, var8=1, var10=0, var1=0, var3=1, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "417",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "420"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-64 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 6 select lines: ['var10', 'var8', 'var11', 'var3', 'var7', 'var4'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var10=1, var8=0, var11=0, var3=1, var7=1, var4=0, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "418",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "420"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-64 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 6 select lines: ['var3', 'var5', 'var11', 'var9', 'var4', 'var8'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var3=1, var5=1, var11=1, var9=1, var4=0, var8=1, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "419",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "418"
  },
  {
    "question": "A circuit consists of a 1-to-64 demultiplexer. The DEMUX has 6 select lines: ['var0', 'var11', 'var9', 'var2', 'var4', 'var7'], and the input variable input_var with value 1. Given the following select lines: var0=1, var11=1, var9=0, var2=0, var4=0, var7=1, what is the output for each output line? Please provide the output for each output line in the format of [[0,1,1,0,1]] if output 0~4 are 0,1,1,0,1 respectively.",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "420",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "418"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "421",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "306"
  },
  {
    "question": "A sequence detector is designed to detect the sequence '[1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1]' in a serial input stream. Given the input stream: [0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0], indicate the output sequence of the detector. Please provide the output sequence in the format of [[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 1 -> 0]].",
    "rule_id": "1",
    "idx": "422",
    "answer": "[[0 -> 1 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0 -> 0]]",
    "difficulty": "3",
    "length": "306"
  }
]